Chapter 603 – Team Group Chat

“It’s done.” Ye Xiu finally let out a sigh of relief. Little Cold Hands agreed to join the team. For clear-headed people, persuading them wasn’t an easy task, but it wasn’t difficult either. Beating around the bush or saying vague statements wouldn’t work on them, but if you clearly stated the pros and cons, they would naturally come to the choice you wanted. Of course, there was one requirement. The choice you wanted has to benefit them. If it doesn’t, then no matter how well you spoke, it would be hard to persuade rational people.

“In the future, you should be the one to do this!” Chen Guo felt a bit ashamed.

“I didn’t know that he would be that type of person!” Ye Xiu expressed his helplessness. He had only teamed up with Little Cold Hands for one dungeon and noticed that one of the Clerics on the team had a beautiful grasp of the tempo. However, in a team with multiple Clerics supporting a single tank, this type of beautiful playing could easily be covered up.

Only a God like Ye Xiu would barely be able to notice this special Cleric. After finding out this special Cleric was Little Cold Hands, he continued to observe him and also paid attention to his messages in chat.

In that team, Little Cold Hands was a very ordinary player. Even though his playing was beautiful, his weaknesses were also very obvious. Because of his slow reaction speed and slow hands, he was lacking in many areas. When he stood still and healed, he performed perfectly, but as soon as anything unexpected happened, such as the tank messing up the aggro, he was unable to react appropriately in those situations.

If an expert wanted to distinguish himself, the easiest way was to shine during crucial moments. However, Little Cold Hand’s weaknesses stopped him from performing well at these crucial moments. His strengths, such as healing at the correct time, only appeared when the situation was stable and everyone was standing still. However, the rest of the Clerics on the team covered him up, which was why no one had noticed anything abnormal about LIttle Cold Hands before.

In dungeon runs, Little Cold Hands just looked like another Cleric, so even though Ye Xiu paid attention to the chat, he couldn’t get much from his messages. Right now, Ye Xiu was quite happy that Little Cold Hands was a clear-headed and rational person. It was because Little Cold Hands was such a person that he didn’t have any enmity towards Ye Qiu’s identity, despite being a Tyranny fan. He only cared about the important issues with being a part of the team.

If Little Cold Hands had been someone like Chen Guo, who angrily left her guild for her idol, there probably wouldn’t have even been a discussion. Ye Xiu thought he might encounter such a person, so he called Chen Guo over to test him out. If the other side was someone like Chen Guo with strong opinions, tricking him wouldn’t work, because the truth would come out eventually.

However, someone clear-headed and rational wouldn’t be easy to deal with either. Like Little Cold Hands mentioned before, it was the issue of choosing other teams. He could ignore the conflict between Ye Qiu and Tyranny to join Ye Qiu’s team, meaning his emotions wouldn’t restrain his decisions, but this also meant that his loyalty to the team needed to be established through other means. Fame or other benefits could easily sway him into leaving their team for another.

In any case, being able to get someone like him to join the team was something worth celebrating.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything more because he had said everything he needed to say. Afterwards, he asked Little Cold Hands about a few more minor details.

Little Cold Hands wasn’t old. He was a university student. Ye Xiu had gotten this information when they had been running dungeons together. If he didn’t meet this age prerequisite, Ye Xiu wouldn’t have considered him. After all, normal players required time to grow, unlike someone with a deep foundation like Wei Chen. If he was too old, he would be too difficult to train and he wouldn’t be able to become a highly-skilled player. Only after learning about Little Cold Hand’s age did he begin doing a more detailed investigation.

Now that he was asking him personally, he verified his age.

Little Cold Hands was 20 years old. After the summer, he would be a third year university student. His real name was An Wenyi. Both his family and his school were in City B. Because of special circumstances, the two exchanged their phone and QQ numbers. As for how he was going to deal with his relationships in the game, school, and family, Ye Xiu didn’t ask. An Wenyi’s rational mind saved Ye Xiu a lot of worry about these aspects.

Chen Guo opened up her QQ and added An Wenyi as a friend. After that, she created a group called “Team Happy”. Ye Xiu was naturally the first to join. Then, she invited An Wenyi, Tang Rou, and Wei Chen to the group.

Their next conversation topic was no longer about the contract. Ye Xiu told An Wenyi about his observations and analyzed the issues that he had noticed when they played together. As for how to help him improve, Ye Xiu needed a better understanding first. He logged out of Unrivaled Super Hottie and logged onto Lord Grim. He partied up with Little Cold Hands and looked for a small five man dungeon to go into.

With just the two of them alone, along with situations that Ye Xiu created to test An Wenyi, Ye Xiu was able to quickly get a deeper understanding of An Wenyi’s skill level. As he cleared away monsters, he had already begun coaching him. As for the North Bridge, he had completely forgotten about it. At the North Bridge, with Dazzling Spring back and no one with the ability to stop him, Blossom Valley gathered together again and regained the upper hand. This time, there was no Unrivaled Super Hottie to disturb him. In the end, after many twists and turns, the North Bridge Mage still ended up in the hands of Blossom Valley.

Unrivaled Super Hottie’s mighty attack, the Cleric heal at the crucial moment, and the dirty commander of Samsara all became meaningless.

The guilds dispersed gloomily. Jiang You already looked like his soul had left his body.

He failed to win the wild boss that the team urgently needed. He still didn’t know the purpose of Ye Qiu spying on his guild for two weeks. These two problems constantly bothered him. Jiang You was doomed to have a sleepless night today.

“That’s basically your current situation right now. Later, I’ll help you sort out everything and devise a training routine for you!”

At a dungeon exit, there stood one person, who was the source of all of Jiang You’s troubles, and the other, who had Tyrannical Ambition’s tag next to his name. Right now, none of them showed an ounce of empathy towards Jiang You’s misery. After running the five man dungeon twice, Ye Xiu ended his session with An Wenyi and prepared to begin helping the others.

“Should I call Steamed Bun over?” Seeing that Ye Xiu was busy, Chen Guo gave a suggestion.

“Okay, invite him into the group!” Ye Xiu said. He and Steamed Bun Invasion had been in touch with each other since a long time ago, so he had a good understanding of his situation.

“What’s the situation? Where’s this?” Steamed Bun Invasion’s QQ name was also Steamed Bun Invasion. His profile picture was a photo of a grinning steamed bun. After accepting the invite, he joined the group and began blabbering away.

“Hm? Team Happy. What a coincidence! It has the same name as our guild!” Steamed Bun Invasion chattered.

“Steamed Bun, it’s me. Lord Grim.” Ye Xiu said.

“Senior!” Steamed Bun Invasion immediately greeted him.

“Did you see? Our guild is planning on forming a team. Would you like to join?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Of course.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“We’re going to sign up and participate in the Challenger League next season. Do you know what that is?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No idea.”

“There’s some information here.” Ye Xiu sent him a link.

“So many words……” Steamed Bun Invasion clicked on the link and an info page about the Challenger League on the Pro League’s website opened up. After five seconds, he let out a grumble.

“We’re going to join this competition. After winning, we’ll be able to enter the pro scene!” Ye Xiu said.

“The pro scene!” Steamed Bun Invasion sent out a shocked emoji.

“Do you know what that is?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Of course!” Steamed Bun Invasion hadn’t played Glory for all this time for nothing. He had a lot more knowledge about the game than before.

“We’ll go to the pro scene and win the championships! Doesn’t that sound fun?” Ye Xiu said.

“Awesome!” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Then it’s decided.” Ye Xiu said.

“When’s the competition?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“It’s still too early. We’ll have to wait until the summer, when the next season begins.” Ye Xiu said.

“But I can’t wait any longer. I’m already burning up!” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“That’s the spirit a young person should have!” Ye Xiu praised.

“You’re too right! I really should have my little bro listen to senior’s words.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Your brother?”

“Concealed Light! Senior, have you forgotten about him already? But then again, you’re right. He’s just a small character.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Oh, Concealed Light! Of course I remember him. How good is he now?’ Ye Xiu said.

“One word: he’s still a noob!” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

Ye Xiu didn’t point out that he had said four words because Steamed Bun Invasion quickly followed up: “But speaking of him, he’s quite hardworking. Senior, how about we give him a chance to feel the burning spirit of our team?”

“Oh, of course!” Ye Xiu said. He also had Concealed Light’s QQ. From the guides that Concealed Light had written up, he also had some talent. It was just that the difference between his theoretical knowledge and his actual ability to play was too incredible. Even though Ye Xiu had given him a few training methods, because of his extremely low starting point, Ye Xiu didn’t have high expectations for Concealed Light. If he had the perseverance to continue training, in the future, he had the potential to become an outstanding player, but right now, with his current strength, he was still way too weak to be one of his team’s members.

Chapter 604 – The Starting Six

Concealed Light was soon dragged into the QQ group. Ye Xiu and Chen Guo didn’t even get the chance to say anything , when Steamed Bun Invasion started lecturing him harshly: “Boy, you listen here. You being able to join such a high-end group is all thanks to my request to senior. You’d better cherish this opportunity and grasp your future. Don’t disgrace me, okay?”

“F*ck off f*ck off f*ck off f*ck off!!!” Concealed Light quickly replied to Steamed Bun Invasion, showing major improvement in his hand speed. He hated how this was a messaging chat, allowing Steamed Bun Invasion to send his messages all at once. If this had been a voice chat, Concealed Light would have interrupted Steamed Bun Invasion several times over already.

“Do you see where we are right now?! How can you have such bad manners!” Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly became angry.

“Let’s not argue now.” Ye Xiu could only step out and mediate.

“Did you hear what he said?! He said to stop arguing!” Steamed Bun Invasion quickly added.

Ye Xiu and Concealed Light clearly had a good understanding of Steamed Bun Invasion. Telling Steamed Bun Invasion not to argue was completely pointless, so they didn’t bother with this topic any longer. Concealed Light saw the name of the group and asked excitedly: “You’re going to create a team?”

“Yeah. Are you interested?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I can join too?” Concealed Light felt very uneasy.

“Of course not, but you can attempt if you want.”

Concealed Light was about to sincerely reply with “I’ll definitely try my hardest.” But when he realized that the person who had sent the message was Steamed Bun Invasion, his reply immediately changed to “F*ck off.”

“Uh, how have things been progressing?” Ye Xiu asked.

“He’s had a slight bit of improvement.” Steamed Bun Invasion spoke for Concealed Light.

Concealed Light: “......”

“What’s your current level?”

“Same as me.” Steamed Bun Invasion was still talking.

Concealed Light: “......”

“Our team will be registering for next season’s Challenger League and will try to earn the chance to advance into the pro scene.” Ye Xiu spoke seriously. He needed to make this point clear for all potential recruits.

“That’s a must.” Steamed Bun Invasion.

Concealed Light: “......”

“How about it? Have you ever thought about becoming a pro player?” Ye Xiu continued.

“In my dreams.” Steamed Bun Invasion quickly replied.

Concealed Light was starting to become uncertain after being annoyed to such a point: “You’re talking to me, right?”

“Yeah……” Ye Xiu had to call out names: “Steamed Bun, don’t interrupt for now!”

“Sure!” Steamed Bun Invasion replied, “Concealed Light, if Senior asks something, you should answer for yourself. What’s there to be afraid of?”

Concealed Light typed a giant block of emojis, which were all smashing their heads against a wall.

“Good, let’s go back to what I previously said. Are you interested in becoming a pro player?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I can become one too?” Concealed Light was somewhat excited, but was also somewhat uneasy. Even though he a lot of game knowledge and theory, his practical ability was very low. Concealed Low wouldn’t even dare to call himself an expert.

“If you’re determined, nothing is impossible. ‘Ye Xiu said.

“Then allow me to try!” Concealed Light expressed.

“Then you’re going to have to work even harder!” Ye Xiu said. He had gotten to know Concealed Light’s skill level long ago and because he had a few special characteristics, he had observed Concealed Light further. In terms of mechanical skill, Concealed Light didn’t have any foundation like Steamed Bun Invasion or Tang Rou did. He pretty much needed to learn from scratch. However, from his guides, he could tell that Concealed Light was someone who worked hard and studied meticulously. This type of studious spirit was Ye Xiu’s reason for having confidence in him. He believed that even though Concealed Light would need more time to develop, as long as there was a direction and he persevered, he definitely had the potential to become a pro. As for how much he would be able to accomplish, that would depend on himself and luck.

“Yes yes, I’ll definitely try hard!” Concealed Light agreed excitedly once he confirmed that Ye Xiu was speaking to him.

‘Good luck!” Ye Xiu sent a “fighting” emoji.

“Nooo! There’s no competition taking place right now! It’s making me impatient. I need to go back to the game and show my strength. I’ll be going!” Steamed Bun Invasion sent a roaring emoji and quickly returned to the game.

“F*ck, so noisy……” Concealed Light finally obtained a peaceful and quiet environment.

“Ha ha…..” Apart from a laugh, Ye Xiu really didn’t know what to say.

“Is there anything else? If not, I’ll be going back to the game too.” Concealed Light said.

“Uh, how about leaving your contact info? It will be more convenient for us to contact you if we need something.” Chen Guo said.

Chen Guo’s QQ name was also Chasing Haze, so Concealed Light immediately recognized who she was. After Lord Grim had gone to the Heavenly Domain, a character called Chasing Haze often showed up to deal with matters in the tenth server’s Guild Happy. Even though she wasn’t the guild leader in name, she was essentially Happy’s guild leader. She had practically the same authority as one, so Concealed Light obviously knew who she was.

‘Sure.” Concealed Light said, while giving her his phone number. He also asked: “Do you need my credentials or anything like that? For when we register?”

The official organizer for the Pro Alliance would definitely need proof of identity. It seemed like Concealed Light was the type of person to forget stuff, so he wanted to get it done with as quickly as possible.

“It’s still too early for us to register. It will have to be after the season ends, but you can give it to me now if you’d like. ‘Ye Xiu said.

Concealed LIght immediately sent his information over, such as his ID.

Concealed Light, real name Luo Ji, 18 years old. He was a second year mathematics major at Famous University in City T.

“Famous University! Wow! 18 years old and already a second year?” Chen Guo was amazed.

“You flatter me.” Concealed Light replied modestly.

“Math major…… are you a good student?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Hello? He’s a student at Famous University! Do you even know what that means?” Chen Guo said. She had dropped out of high school in order to manage the Internet Cafe. As for the person next to her, from her knowledge of his career, he had probably left his home to play videogames after graduating from middle school. Chen Guo felt like with their educational backgrounds, they should deeply respect a student from a place like Famous University.

“Study well. It’s very useful.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you know?” Chen Guo said with disdain.

“From a gaming perspective, math is a very very very important subject. If you study it well, it will certainly be helpful.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was speechless. This guy was telling him to study well from a gaming perspective? If his major hadn’t been a very very very important subject from a gaming perspective, he wouldn’t tell him to straight up switch majors would he…….

“Yeah, I know.” Concealed Light said. As a math major, he knew how useful mathematics was.

“I have some data here. You can try to study it.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?”

Ye Xiu private messaged Concealed Light and sent him some of the data.

“These are from the normal server. Once you get to the Heavenly Domain, there’ll be a lot more.” Ye Xiu said. He gave Concealed Light the results of Wei Chen’s research on skill books. Now that he knew about Concealed Light’s identity, he felt like giving these to Concealed Light might produce new findings and advances. Wei Chen was from a rough background. After retiring for so many years, he probably wasn’t someone who could become successful just by studying by himself. His research was from experience, intuition, and experiments in order to reach a conclusion. Only someone as knowledgeable as Concealed Light would be able to deconstruct the difference factors involved in finding skill book drops.

Even though he was only a second year university student, Ye Xiu firmly believed that his friend Wei Chen’s education had probably stopped at third year in middle school. Life experiences might be able to increase his knowledge, but an advanced skill like math wasn’t something that could be obtained in such a way.

“Ah, this……” Concealed Light had played for a long time. How could he not know about the value of skill books? After flipping through a few pages of data, he felt greatly shocked.

“It’s classified information!” Ye Xiu said.

“Of course!” Concealed Light replied.

“If you’ve got time, make sure you take a look!” Ye Xiu said.

“Sure sure…….” Concealed Light replied. He seemed like he couldn’t wait any longer.

Chen Guo was a bit hesitant though. After all, Concealed Light was someone they had met online. He said he would join the team, but it was just an oral agreement. There wasn’t an actual contract or anything between them, and Ye Xiu had given him something so important…….

Chen Guo thought this was a bit too rash, but seeing that Ye Xiu trusted Concealed Light, she felt a bit embarrassed to cut in. After all, the data had already been handed over. Even if she said it now, it was too late. It would be better to place more trust in this talent from Famous University.

“Do you know about Steamed Bun’s situation?” Chen Guo had neatly organized the information on Little Cold Hands and Concealed Light, but she didn’t have time to gather any about Steamed Bun Invasion.

“Apart from his name, I have a general understanding of his situation!” Ye Xiu said. He had known Steamed Bun Invasion for awhile now and had gleaned some information from his conversations with him. He was very similar to Concealed Light. Ye Xiu already knew that he was young.

He had gotten Steamed Bun Invasion’s phone number a long time ago. As for what he did…… from their conversations together, he had revealed that he was a guard at an Internet Cafe. In that case, he had a similar background as Wei Chen. Both of them were ruffians! What would it be like if the two met each other….

“Steamed Bun has never said his real name before?” Chen Guo organized everyone’s information. Steamed Bun Invasion’s name was the only space left blank for now though.

“He’s never talked about it. I’ll ask him in a sec.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay. Then currently we have you, Little Tang, Old Wei, Little Cold Hands, Steamed Bun, and Concealed Light. We have six already!” Chen Guo was excited.

Six players was the minimum number of players required for a team. It was the number required for a team competition. However, the rules in the Alliance weren’t fixed. If the team didn’t meet the minimum requirements, it wouldn’t mean that their qualifications would be nulled. The team could still participate, but the team would just be at a disadvantage.

For example, if a team had five players. The team would have to give up on one round of the individual competition, or play the group competition as a 2v3.

In addition to that, for the team competition, the team would only have five players and no substitutes.

This ruling was because of the difficult start in the early years of the pro scene. At that time, there were too many teams and not enough players. Teams only had the minimum six players. If any one of them had some sort of accident, it would become awkward. If they automatically lost, too many matches would be cancelled, which was why this rule had been created.

However, even though they could still register and participate in the competition without six players, they wouldn’t be able to win. Now that Team Happy had six players gathered, none of which were randomly chosen, they were progressing quite well.

Chapter 605 – Times Have Changed

Translator: Editor:

Seeing how excited Chen Guo was, Ye Xiu didn’t want to pour any cold water on her mood. In reality, only he and Wei Chen were ready to go out on stage at any time. And even though Tang Rou and Steamed Bun Invasion were talented and improved quickly, Tang Rou wasn’t just new to Glory, but new to gaming as well. It would be hard to avoid playing inconsistently. As for Steamed Bun Invasion, even though he was new to Glory, he clearly had prior experience in gaming. However, this guy had plenty of other stupid issues apart from Glory. His playing was even more inconsistent than Tang Rou’s.

As for Little Cold Hands and Concealed Light, both of them had clear weaknesses and strengths. Their weaknesses limited their strengths too. If they couldn’t overcome these weaknesses, neither of them had the qualifications to even step onstage. The Challenger League obviously wouldn’t be as difficult as the Professional League, but they would still meet a few strong opponents. With their current skill, they definitely wouldn’t be able to handle it.

Fortunately, there was still plenty of time before the Challenger League began. Moreover, the Challenger League had both fish and dragons mixed together. There would be strong opponents, but most of the participating players could be dealt with by Ye Xiu alone. After the teams, that were there just for the fun of it, were completely eliminated, there would be some time in between. During this time, Little Cold Hands and Concealed Light could continue to develop. Ye Xiu could only hope that these two could truly perform well when he needed them to. He didn’t expect them to immediately start shining as soon as they entered the Challenge League.

In short, their team lacked relatively experienced players. Ye Xiu could only feel regret towards Zhang Jiale. He wasn’t just someone who could be described as “relatively experienced”. If Zhang Jiale actually joined their team, Ye Xiu reckoned that with just him, Zhang Jiale, Wei Chen, Tang Rou, and Steamed Bun Invasion, they were more than enough to steamroll their way through the Challenger League. It was just too bad. Saying that they could steamroll through the Challenger League wouldn’t be able to persuade Zhang Jiale though. Who cares if they could sweep the Challenger League? At best, they would be able to easily earn a spot in the Professional League, but what did Zhang JIale want? To be the champion! What Ye Xiu could promise and what Zhang Jiale wanted were way too far off.

Ye Xiu thought about this to himself. He didn’t splash any cold water on Chen Guo’s happy mood, but this time, Chen Guo showed clear-headedness. After organizing the information on the members of their team, she reviewed the team: “With six players, we have enough people, but our chances of winning doesn’t seem too high, no?”

Seeing that Chen Guo had thought of it herself, Ye Xiu nodded his head: “Yeah! That Concealed Light isn’t even better than you right now!”

“What then? Do you know any other retired experts like Old Wei?” Chen Guo said.

“I do know a few. However, besides the question of whether or not they’ve even touched Glory recently, they have to be interested in joining our team. Relying on a team of these players gathered together would be enough to deal with a vast majority of opponents we will face in Challenger League, but that’s not our goal. We want to return to the Professional League and win the championships. If our team is made up of old fellows, there won’t be much room to improve…..” Ye Xiu sighed.

“What do we do then? Continue switching accounts and find potential recruits?” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu shook his head: “The players who are found through this method will be just like Little Cold Hands or Concealed Light. They have talent, but they also have major flaws that weaken their strength. Anyone outstanding would have been discovered already. We’re not planning on becoming a training camp. Little Cold Hands and Concealed Light are enough. We need players who can go up on stage at anytime, or players like Little Tang and Steamed Bun Invasion, who already have a solid foundation and improve quickly. These types of players can’t be found in the Heavenly Domain. They have already been discovered. It would be better to pay more attention to the tenth server. There are definitely still players like Little Tang or Steamed Bun Invasion amongst the new players. In addition, they probably haven’t been noticed by the big guilds yet.”

“But even though they haven’t noticed any yet, doesn’t mean that they’re not paying attention, right?” Chen Guo said.

“Right.” Ye Xiu sighed, “And we don’t have any advantage over them. This is something that can only be encountered by chance. To be able to pick up a Steamed Bun was already very lucky.”

“Uh oh, shouldn’t we hurry and talk with Steamed Bun about the contract? It would be terrible if another guild took him away!” Chen Guo suddenly remembered.

“This…… I don’t think it’ll happen.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why not?”

“Because of Steamed Bun’s personality and because…… from a certain perspective, Steamed Bun also has a big weakness that protects him……” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s better to be careful!” Chen Guo erred on the side of caution.

“That’s fine too.” Ye Xiu thought about it and felt like since they had already gone this far, they might as well start being more careful. Similar to how Wang Jiexi tried to recruit Tang Rou before, if Tang Rou didn’t have special circumstances, an incredible seedling would have been taken away just like that.

The current champion team! Compared with a newly created team that wasn’t even sure if they could make it through the Challenger League yet, it was too huge of a chasm.

Chen Guo acted swiftly. With the plan set, she immediately logged into the tenth server Chasing Haze and called out to Steamed Bun Invasion.

“What?” Steamed Bun Invasion replied.

“Steamed Bun, you left too quickly! We weren’t finished discussing yet!” Chen Guo said.

‘Oh oh, what else did senior have to say?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“We’re creating a team to participate in an official competition, so we will need your information. We’re also going to need you to sign a contract for it later.” Chen Guo said.

“Ooh okay, then should I come over in person?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“That would be good!” Chen Guo smiled.

“Where do I find you guys?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“We’re in City H. Tell me when you’re available and I can come pick you up.” Chen Guo arranged.

“Sure. I’ll go buy a ticket.” Steamed Bun Invasion said and then disappeared.

Chen Guo was left there hanging. After two minutes of staring blankly, she turned around and said to Ye Xiu: “I admire Steamed Bun very much.”

“Why?” Ye Xiu wasn’t like Chen Guo who spent most of her time watching someone else play.

“Steamed Bun went to buy a ticket. He’ll be coming over directly.” Chen Guo said.

Steamed Bun Invasion’s spirit was something even Tang Rou couldn’t help but be awed by: “That Steamed Bun…… really is……”

“That’s too decisive. How are you going to accommodate for him when he arrives? Don’t tell me he’ll be sleeping on the sofa?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Mm, that’ll be an issue. Not just Steamed Bun. Later, when the team officially forms. Everyone will need to be together. We’ll definitely have to figure out how to accommodate for them. Hand this matter over to me!” Chen Guo nodded her head. Pro teams usually had 10-12 players. They couldn’t just be squeezed into such a small room in the Internet Cafe. Chen Guo seemed to have been influenced by Steamed Bun Invasion. She moved swiftly and decisively. She immediately went online and started looking up housing locations near Joyful Flourish Internet Cafe.

Chen Guo hadn’t moved from this stretch of land in the past thirty years. Even the neighboring Club Excellent Era was something that Chen Guo had watched as it developed and was built. Chen Guo was very familiar with this part of town. Which surrounding areas were convenient, close to the Internet Cafe, in a nice area, etc. She could close her eyes and talk about them all. She naturally found apartments for rent very quickly and started calling.

As she called them, she took notes. Soon, she had an entire page of information. Chen Guo looked at the page and felt like she had enough information for now. She turned her head towards Ye Xiu and Tang Rou: “Who wants to go house hunting?”

“Obviously, you should be the one to go!” Ye Xiu said.

“Nonsense. I’m saying apart from me, who else wants to go?” Chen Guo called.

“I’ll go with you.” Tang Rou smiled as she stood up.

“Little Tang, you don’t need to move out. We can continue to stay here and live.” Chen Guo said.

“Mm, I’ll just go out for a walk with you then.” Tang Rou said.

“What about you? Would you like to go and take a walk?” Chen Guo said. Ye Xiu was still living in that little storage room. Speaking of which, Chen Guo felt quite embarrassed. Now that they were looking for apartments, Chen Guo wanted to make up for it.“It doesn’t matter for me. You can do what you want!” Ye Xiu waved his hands. He clearly wasn’t planning on spending much time choosing a comfortable living environment.

Chen Guo was helpless. She and Tang Rou left. Before leaving, she talked about the issue of everyone needing to live together and her plans on renovating the second floor of the Internet Cafe.

They quickly chose an apartment. Chen Guo had naturally already seen the appearances of the rooms before contacting the owner. As for the prices, Chen Guo was very familiar with this part of town. The prices were around a thousand or so yuan and she happily negotiated. Soon, they found a terraced house with six rooms in a small area called Forest Park. It had a balcony at the top, a garden at the bottom, two stories, and six rooms. Chen Guo was planning on having two people to a room. On the first floor, there were two living rooms connected together. Chen Guo felt like she could set up a circle of computers here, so they wouldn’t need to use the Internet Cafe. The team could directly eat, sleep, and practice together here.

Good! Chen Guo was so satisfied that she and Tang Rou even talked about moving over from the Internet Cafe to live here.

After paying the initial deposit, she was like a general returning home after a victory. Ye Xiu was naturally still at his computer playing Glory. Chen Guo told him the good news. Ye Xiu also looked at her with wide eyes.

“So luxurious!!!” Ye Xiu was deeply moved. He couldn’t help but think about the year he had left home. Having food and a bed was quite nice already. What type of housing condition hadn’t he been in? Ye Xiu already felt lucky to be able to live in the storage room. It was small, but it was still his own personal living space. And now? He was about to move into a villa to play games. How the times have changed.

Chapter 606 – Gathering

Chen Guo had lived in the area around Happy Internet Cafe for close to thirty years and was incredibly familiar with it. However, Ye Xiu had only been here for about seven years too, so he wasn’t too unfamiliar with it. Even though he seldom went out during those seven years, Ye Xiu still knew about the Forest Park neighborhood.

Forest Park was considered an upper-middle class neighborhood. Quite a few people from Club Excellent Era lived here. The boss Tao Xuan had property in this neighborhood and had once invited the entire team over during a vacation period for a party. In the blink of an eye, the things stayed the same, but the people have changed. Ye Xiu couldn’t help but let out a sigh.

“The contract starts in April. Why don’t you take a look, pick a room, and give some ideas on how to arrange everything?” Chen Guo pulled the sighing Ye Xiu back to reality.

“Oh, me? It doesn’t matter. We can talk about it when the time comes!” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was helpless. Clothing, food, housing, and transport were basic human needs. In most people’s eyes, shouldn’t this have been an urgent issue? But for Ye Xiu, all of these were unimportant. Chen Guo reckoned that he would probably be more nervous over discovering that he had no cigarettes left.

“When will Steamed Bun be coming over?” Chen Guo asked.

“Didn’t he buy a ticket to come?” Ye Xiu said.

“You haven’t gotten any messages from him?” Chen Guo and Tang Rou had spent the entire day looking for housing.

“None!” Ye Xiu said.

“Maybe he already bought the ticket and is already on his way here?” Chen Guo wondered.

“Mm, if it’s Steamed Bun. It’s definitely possible.” Ye Xiu said.

“These guys……” Chen Guo looked up at the ceiling. She suddenly realized that she was carrying a lot of weight on her shoulder.

“Should we also call over Old Wei over?” Ye Xiu asked his boss.

“Sure sure. Call over anyone you’d like. We’ve already have the housing settled. Let’s not put it to waste.” Chen Guo remembered the reminder Tang Rou had given her that afternoon: the house rent was expensive and it was very likely much of the money would go to waste because they didn’t have enough people to fill the house yet. Steamed Bun Invasion could throw down whatever he was doing and buy a ticket to come over, but Little Cold Hands and Concealed Light were university students. They probably didn’t have the luxury to do that. They most likely needed to stay on school grounds.

Unfortunately, Chen Guo was too happy with the suite. She had barely stepped into the suite and she made a deal immediately out of impulse. The deal went so quickly that the real estate agent almost laughed. From Tang Rou’s logical point of view, it was extremely likely much of the money for rent would go to waste, when Chen Guo thought about her contribution to the team, she still felt satisfied with the decision. As for money, Chen Guo didn’t place too much value on it. If everything was prepared well, recruits would be more willing to join. If she had to hurry and make emergency arrangements, wouldn’t that be too abnormal? Thinking about it this way, Chen Guo felt like the money spent was well worth it.

Meanwhile, as soon as Ye Xiu got the nod, he contacted Wei Chen.

“Oh? So it’s like that? It’s not too inconvenient for me, but I have a bunch of brothers that I usually hang out with too.” Wei Chen was a bit hesitant, but he was just a bit regretful. He clearly knew that if they were going to create a team, everyone would need to be together in one place. No matter how much he loved his friends, he couldn’t demand that his friends come to the pro scene with him.

“Okay. I’ll make some arrangements and I’ll be over there soon.” Wei Chen was a decisive person and quickly gave his answer.

‘Okay, I’ll be waiting.” Ye Xiu didn’t say anymore.

Over the next few days, Ye Xiu didn’t use his Unrivaled Super Hottie account. Instead, he used Lord Grim and continued to level. With Unrivaled Super Hottie gone, Jiang You, as well as the other core members of Tyrannical Ambition, knew why, but the other normal players didn’t know the reason. The players of all the branch guilds were still waiting for the incredible tank to help them pass through any difficulties in their way, but suddenly, he vanished. Many of their players were very upset.

However, this was a game. If someone suddenly disappeared, it wasn’t too weird. Unrivaled Super Hottie was only deeply missed because of the abnormal amount of attention they had placed onto him. After being gone for a few days, everyone slowly forgot about his existence.

Ye Xiu’s leveling with Lord Grim was going smoothly. Apart from the loads of experience from dungeons, he didn’t need to worry about the big guilds bothering him anymore. Even though it had been a good while since Lord Grim had entered the Heavenly Domain, Ye Xiu had no idea what policies the big guilds had towards him. In short, he would do what he could to defend himself. Dungeons were naturally safe places for him to be. As long as he went into one, he wouldn’t need to be afraid of anyone bothering him.

The number of Heavenly Domain dungeons were as numerous as there were hairs on cows. If the dungeons were as numerous as cow hairs, dungeon entrances were even more numerous. Guarding the dungeon entrances and waiting for him to come like they could in the normal servers was impossible here. Ye Xiu cleared dungeons all day and Lord Grim’s experience shot up.

His leveling speed was even faster than it had been in the normal servers. The rewards in the Heavenly Domain were far greater than they were in the normal server. This was the same for experience and money.

However, his Level 50-55 leveling had been too bumpy of a journey. Ye Xiu’s fast leveling these past few days wasn’t even close to catching up to the highest leveled players in the tenth server, who were already Level 67 and pushing for Level 70. Players like Tang Rou’s Soft Mist used to be among the highest leveled players in the server, but after some time, they had been slowly tossed behind. After all, they couldn’t level their characters 24/7 like guilds characters could. This time advantage couldn’t be made up for by Tang Rou’s advantage in player skill.

None of this mattered though. After Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim entered the Heavenly Domain, their battle had shifted. In the normal servers, even though there were valuable resources to be competed for, in the Heavenly Domain, normal server items became cheaper. It wasn’t worth spending most of his effort on the tenth server. What’s more, their strength hadn’t really come together yet. With limited resources, it would be better to place more importance on the Heavenly Domain. Even if they had to trade the items that they earned for items from normal servers, it would still be worth it.

As for what to compete for? Currently, Ye Xiu needed to complete his Thousand Chance Umbrella and Wei Chen’s Death Hand. With a goal, the two knew what needed to be done.

If they could get anything else along the way, they would take it. After all, relying on two Silver weapons to strike the heavens down wasn’t realistic. Their other equipment would need to be complete too. The other members of the team would need suitable equipment too. There was no such thing as having too many materials. If they weren’t useful, they could be traded for money.

Ye Xiu was just leveling these past few days, so he didn’t have much else to do. As for Wei Chen, after making arrangements to come over, he continued to swim around in Samsara.

His journey to the top of the guild was essentially the same as Ye Xiu’s Unrivaled Super Hottie. However, he wasn’t as dramatic as Unrivaled Super Hottie, who rose all the way up in just a few days. During the two weeks that Unrivaled Super Hottie shone his way up in Tyrannical Ambition, he slowly worked his way up in Samsara from a newly joined member to an elite.

After all, his skill level was there. The big guilds wouldn’t ignore such a talent. However, even though he was an elite, he was still far away from being a core member.

It was similar to Unrivaled Super Hottie’s situation in Tyrannical Ambition. Even if Jiang You hadn’t seen through Ye Xiu’s identity, someone who had only just joined could only do hard work at first. To become a core member of the guild, skill wasn’t important. Trust was.

This was the hardest part about being a spy. If all you need was skill to become a core member, then the guilds would just send one of their experts to immediately become a spy. Speaking of which, it wasn’t the first time guilds had exploited experts like Unrivaled Super Hottie. Many spies that had been compromised were intentionally ignored by the guild and used as hard labor instead. The spies didn’t know that they had been caught and were doing their best to win the favor of the guild. Their skill was good, so they were very confident. When the crucial moment came and the spy was misinformed, nothing could be more tragic for that spy then.

Wei Chen had played Glory for so many years. There was nothing that he didn’t know about. During his time in Samsara, he showed his skill, but he didn’t dare to be too outstanding. If anyone showed ridiculous skill like Unrivaled Super Hottie did, with the current situation in the Heavenly Domain, there was only one label that could be put on him: Ye Qiu.

As a result, Wei Chen had counted the many times that Ye Xiu had failed to be a spy. His commotion made everyone’s work that much harder.

However, with Wei Chen’s ability, he just needed to casually play and he had more than enough skill to stand out among other players. With too much skill, he would be suspicious, but he would also gain a lot of attention. It was a double-edged sword. If he didn’t rely on displaying his skill, then it would take too long to climb up the guild’s ladder. Other spies had the time, but he and Ye Xiu didn’t. Thus, Wei Chen went around brandishing his double-edged sword.

At the fight for the North Bridge Mage, Wei Chen was amongst the Samsara’s elite troops. He wasn’t a core member of Samsara, but his current status was already enough for Ye Xiu’s purposes. Maybe Samsara was still suspicious of Wei Chen’s identity and was using him as a helper for now, but it didn’t matter to him.

Because in terms of power, their guild couldn’t compare to the club guilds. The various club guilds need to receive information multiple times to confirm it, but for Ye Xiu and the others, this was too much work. If they could directly participate in these battles, it was equivalent to knowing the situation.

If not, with just Ye Xiu and the others alone, how could they find wild bosses that randomly spawned every week?

“I’ll come over tomorrow. Send me the address.” At 8:00 PM on April 1, Wei Chen suddenly messaged Ye Xiu over QQ.

Fifteen minutes later, Steamed Bun Invasion’s steamed bun icon suddenly up: “Senior! I bought my ticket. I’m on the train. I’ll be there soon!”

“Steamed Bun, you’ve used the same ticket for the past few days?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chapter 607 – A Special Day

The successive messages from Wei Chen and Steamed Bun Invasion, along with the fact that it was April 1st, made Ye Xiu very suspicious, but then again, Wei Chen had asked for the address, so he himself could come over. It didn’t seem like an April Fool’s joke. Could he be thinking that they were going to host a huge welcome celebration for him and it would be funny if he didn’t show up? Even though Wei Chen was very shameless, he wasn’t stupid.

Ye Xiu was more doubtful about Steamed Bun Invasion though. This guy immediately decided to go buy a ticket over here. Then, he suddenly told him that he was on the train today. The several day gap didn’t conform with common sense. However, this was Steamed Bun Invasion! He wasn’t a normal person. Using common sense to figure him out would be a mistake. As a result, Ye Xiu asked Steamed Bun Invasion what he had been doing these past few days.

“Sigh. Nothing I could do.” Steamed Bun Invasion replied quickly. QQ indicated that Steamed Bun Invasion was using the app on his cellphone. Typing on the phone limited his typing speed.

“I bought the ticket that very day, but when my friends heard I was going to become a pro player, they wanted to give me a goodbye party. Today, we’ll party. Tomorrow, we’ll party. The next day, we’ll party. We partied for several days. I had to keep on changing my tickets until today.” Steamed Bun Invasion explained.

“Wow, I’m sorry for troubling you……” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s okay. I’ll be there soon! Senior, where am I headed?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

Ye Xiu saw that Steamed Bun was asking him for directions. It didn’t seem like an April Fool’s joke, so he gave him his address, just like he did for Wei Chen.

‘Can you find it?” Ye Xiu sent the address over to Steamed Bun Invasion and asked.

“Relax!” Steamed Bun Invasion was very confident.

“If you can’t find it, just give me a call.” Ye Xiu gave Chen Guo’s cellphone number to Steamed Bun Invasion.

“I think the probability of me using this phone number will definitely be zero.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“I hope so!” Ye Xiu said.

After giving the two people the address, Ye Xiu went to find Chen Guo and told her the news, but Chen Guo looked at him warily. After starting at Ye Xiu for several seconds, she finally asked: “Are you serious?”

Ye Xiu was helpless. It was a special day after all. You always had to be cautious. Ye Xiu put on his serious face and said: “I’m serious. Think of it this way, today is April Fool’s Day, but wouldn’t using this sort of joke be too lame?”

Chen Guo listened, but didn’t let her guard down. She actually became even more wary and nervously asked: “Then what do you plan on doing?”

“How old am I? Do you think I have something planned?” Ye Xiu looked at her in disdain and left.

Speaking of which, Chen Guo wasn’t usually afraid of April Fool’s Day. In the morning, Tang Rou and several other employees had pulled a small prank on her. Most people wouldn’t be too excessive with it. However, the God in her Internet Cafe could summon storms in game. Chen Guo was actually quite afraid of what type of shameless prank he might play on her. Seeing Ye Xiu look at her with disdain and walk away, Chen Guo wasn’t angry. She actually felt quite relieved.

The rest of the day went on like normal. It was just April Fool’s Day. It wasn’t a holiday or anything. Glory didn’t prepare anything special for today either. However, in the competitive scene, today was a competition day and April was an important period for the pros.

The Professional Alliance usually held competitive matches every week. If there were any big holidays or other special occasions on those days, the schedule would be adjusted accordingly. The season usually started in the middle of August and ended on the first third of May the next year. The middle third of May would be the playoffs, where the top eight teams would enter an elimination style tournament until the champion was crowned.

April meant that the season was coming to an end. Teams with outstanding records or extremely terrible records might already know their general placings.

For example, in this eighth season, April 1st was a Saturday, a match day. April had five Saturdays and May had two Saturdays for a total of seven match days until the season ended. This was a few days more than other seasons. Usually, when April came, there would only be five or six match days left.

At this point, the placements of a few teams were already determined. For example, Blue Rain, Samsara, Tiny Herb, Tyranny were way ahead of the rest. They had already been guaranteed a spot in the playoffs. The remaining seven matches would determine their seedings. Currently, after the All Star Weekend, Samsara had shot past Tiny Herb and grasped the number two spot. These seven matches would be a competition between Samsara and Blue Rain to see who would take first in the regular season. Unfortunately, none of the remaining matches matched Samsara and Blue Rain in a direct confrontation.

This situation put less pressure on the teams, but the Alliance didn’t like it too much. In Glory, they often called these situations “Killer Matches”.

In these remaining seven matches, these four teams wouldn’t care as much because they had already locked in their playoff spots, so there would usually be less highlights in these matches. In addition to that, these four teams were without a doubt some of the most popular teams in the Alliance. If their matches were less suspenseful, the number of viewers would drastically decrease.

At this stage, the media stopped placing importance on these popular teams and spent more time reporting the other teams fighting for the remaining four playoff spots.

Misty Rain, Void, Wind Howl, 301, Thunderclap, Hundred Blossoms, and Royal Style.

These seven teams were currently the focal point of the media and the only teams with the possibility of grabbing a playoff spot.

Misty Rain and Void had steady positions and led the pack. Wind Howl and 301 were under a lot of pressure. If the three teams behind them wanted to move up, the three teams would need to step over their corpses. Team Thunderclap was currently in ninth place, just outside the top eight. However, their seven remaining matches were against easy teams, so their chances of making it into the playoffs were highly likely.

Before Zhang Jiale’s retirement, let alone the playoffs, Team Hundred Blossoms were frequently in the finals. However, this season, their team had been thrown into disorder and their record wasn’t very stable. They kept on bouncing back and forth between the door to the playoffs. It was very likely that they wouldn’t be able to make it into the playoffs, making the fans very nervous.

Team Royal Style was in the worst spot of these seven teams. Not only was it in last compared to the rest of the seven teams, the next few matches for them wouldn’t be easy. However, since the top four teams had guaranteed their spot in the playoffs, it might not be so bad. The next matches would be difficult because Team Royal Style needed to face all of the top four teams, but since the top four had guaranteed their spot, they would be much more relaxed in their matches and Royal Style might be able to pull off a win against them.

The probability of which of the seven teams would earn a playoff spot had been analyzed by all sorts of professionals and fans, but because today was a special day, the headlines weren’t about these seven teams.

The headline: Excellent Era is out! Is this an April Fool’s Day joke??

Correct, Excellent Era continued to perform poorly. After the All Star Weekend, they had returned back to the brink of relegations. They were only one point higher than the second to last place team.

One point!

It was very likely that after today’s match, Team Excellent Era would drop into the relegation zone. And with their current morale, if they dropped, whether they would actually be able to come back was a very big issue.

The media and fans had criticized Team Excellent Era for over a month now. Team Excellent Era kept on expressing their stance on their record, but nothing worked. Their placing kept on dropping. They would occasionally show moments of brilliance in the individual and group arena competitions, but over the past three months, Excellent Era had yet to win a single team competition.

The fans couldn’t help but think of the team’s glorious moments in the past and they kept on bringing up the retired team captain Ye Qiu. If Ye Qiu were still there, the team would still be such and such. This type of question would often come up in these sorts of moments. Many people happily forgot that Ye Qiu had led the team and they weren’t performing well either. These were the same people that had criticized him then.

Team Excellent Era’s match had become a focal point in the competition too. As a result, like before, Chen Guo didn’t avoid playing Excellent Era’s matches when they were a highlight of the day. Tonight, Happy Internet Cafe had arranged to broadcast Excellent Era’s match.

After a period of time, Happy Internet Cafe had gotten used to not playing Excellent Era’s matches every time. Gradually, the weekend broadcasts became popular again.

City H had many Excellent Era fans, but that didn’t mean everybody was one. Even the area near Club Excellent Era wouldn’t only have Excellent Era fans.

Happy Internet Cafe’s broadcasts suited the appetites of fans, who supported other teams or only wanted to watch the big branded teams play, so these fans happily came over on the weekends to watch. However, without everyone supporting the same team, the atmosphere wasn’t as passionate as before.

Even so, for those who had never seen this type of Internet Cafe before, it was still quite impressive.

“What’s going on? Are people protesting?”

A person stood at the entrance of Happy Internet Cafe. Half his face was covered by his long hair. The other half of his face showed his youthfulness. At this moment, he was holding onto his cellphone. He looked at Happy Internet Cafe very seriously before walking in. The huge crowd of people inside made him very surprised.

However, he didn’t show any fear towards the crowd. He calmly walked towards the front desk and flipped his long hair aside. He was just about to say something, when he suddenly stopped. He took out his cellphone, while calling out to the sister in charge of the cash register: “Hold on. I forgot the word.”

Chapter 608 – An Unimaginable Matter

While the girl working the cashier looked at him in confusion, the long-haired youth glanced at his phone and repeatedly said “oh oh oh”. Then, he lifted his head and asked with a grin: “Chen Guo?”

“Steamed Bun!” Someone called out from near the register. Ye Xiu and Chen Guo were standing there! When the Internet Cafe broadcasted a popular match, the two wouldn’t go to the front and steal a good seat from a customer. They usually sat far away and watched from the cash register.

“Yes?” This youth responded and turned his head around. He saw a male and a female nearby, smiling at him.

“Lord Grim, Chasing Haze.” Ye Xiu took out his account ID and introduced himself and Chen Guo.

“Oh oh, I’m Steamed Bun Invasion. I’m here!” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“I can see that.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“What’s going on? Is someone making a ruckus? I’ll help you out!!” Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t shy with strangers and quickly blended in as a Happy Internet Cafe employee. He had already begun rolling up his sleeves.

“No no, a match is being broadcast!” Chen Guo hastily stopped him. She was afraid Steamed Bun Invasion would start pulling a mob.

“Match? There usually aren’t any matches at this time! La Liga or Serie A?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked in wonder.

“It’s a Glory Alliance match...” Chen Guo said.

“Glory Alliance match….. Oh oh!” Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly understood what was going on and then said seriously: “You’re right. We’re going to be entering the Professional Alliance, so we have to watch more competitive matches in order to understand our opponents. Who will we be watching today?”

Right when he said this, the broadcast host began speaking. The most important match today, between Team Excellent Era and Team Void, was about to begin.

“Oh, Excellent Era, Void. These two teams. We have to watch them carefully.” Steamed Bun Invasion said seriously.

“Then let’s watch……” Ye Xiu said.

“Of course!” Steamed Bun Invasion turned his head, maintaining his pose as a cash register. His eyes began focusing on the match.

“I’m 100% certain that this person is Steamed Bun Invasion.” Chen Guo whispered to Ye Xiu.

“In any case, he’s definitely not Old Wei.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?” Chen Guo asked.

Ye Xiu turned his head: “I’d recognize Old Wei.”

“Oh……” Chen Guo had to admit that she had asked a very stupid question.

The match soon began. Because it was an Excellent Era match, there were many Excellent Era fans squeezed into the Internet Cafe today. As soon as it started, there were lots of cheering and sounds of worry. Right now, the fans were very concerned with the team’s current situation.

“Huh! It seems like there’s a lot of support for Excellent Era? Team Void shouldn’t have any less fans than them!” Steamed Bun Invasion watched the match, but commentated on the Internet Cafe’s audience. He didn’t hear any Void fans competing against Excellent Era fans like he had expected. The noise from the Excellent Era fans covered up everything.

“Void has no energy! It looks to me like they’ll be losing tonight!” Steamed Bun Invasion came to this conclusion.

“Let’s watch the match, Steamed Bun……” Ye Xiu said.

“Roger that!” Steamed Bun Invasion respected Ye Xiu’s wishes and continued to pay attention to the match.

As the match progressed, more and more angry shouts were coming from the Excellent Era fans. The three Excellent Era players who came out to compete for the individual competition lost all three rounds, making the Excellent Era fans in Happy Internet Cafe very upset. Even Steamed Bun Invasion saw the result and whispered with wide eyes: “No way! How could it be like this?” It seemed like he had been very confident in his previous prediction.

Amidst the cursing, the group arena competition began. There were many twists and turns, causing everyone to be on edge, but in the end, Excellent Era managed to win the group arena and earned two points. The Excellent Era fans relaxed a bit and began nervously paying attention to the most important team competition.

“What’s your predictions?” Chen Guo liked to listen to Ye Xiu’s predictions of every match. Even though he didn’t predict every single match’s outcome correctly, his analysis was very knowledgeable. Chen Guo felt that her skill in Glory wouldn’t improve much from his analysis in terms of mechanical skill, but her theoretical knowledge improved greatly. Now, she was gradually learning and sometimes even looked down on the comments made by the commentator and analyst.

“It’s obvious.” Ye Xiu shook his head. He expression didn’t look too good.

“Excellent Era will lose?” Chen Guo saw the look on Ye Xiu’s face and stopped herself from stealing a laugh. Right now, she hoped Excellent Era would fail. However, seeing Ye Xiu’s mood, it wouldn’t be good to be too excessive. She could empathize with Ye Xiu’s feelings towards the team. As a result, at this moment, in order to hold back her laugh, she thought about Su Mucheng and how she would also fail alongside the team. By doing this, she wouldn’t say anything out loud about Excellent Era’s misfortune.

“Excellent Era is a disaster right now.” Ye Xiu said.

“The outside world is analyzing the reasons, but I think it’s mainly because of that one time.” Chen Guo said. When she said “that one time”, she was referring to when Excellent Era sent out their starting lineup into the game only to end up being smashed by Ye Xiu and a group of players. From then on, Team Excellent Era’s playing only got worse and worse.

“It’s not only because of that time. The current Excellent Era has too many holes. No one in the team cares enough to try and fix them.” Ye Xiu said.

“How terrible! It’s such a waste for Mumu to continue being on that team. Is there any way to get her to leave early?” Chen Guo suggested. If Su Mucheng was no longer a part of the team, she could be at ease cursing Excellent Era to death.

But Ye Xiu didn’t reply to her question: “If this continues, Excellent Era might even get relegated this season.”

“Really? Wouldn’t that be tragic for Mumu?”

“Another thing. If Excellent Era is relegated, then they will be our opponents in the Challenger League. With Excellent Era participating in the Challenger League, things will be very difficult!” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah…….” Chen Guo didn’t think about this point. Now that Ye Xiu mentioned it, she suddenly understood. Don’t look at how terribly Excellent Era was doing this season. They still had the Battle God One Autumn Leaf and Sun Xiang. Their recognition wasn’t without a reason. If they didn’t have this sort of strong foundation, Excellent Era’s relegation would never have been reported as an April Fool’s joke. Clearly, such a strong team like Excellent Era being relegated was something unimaginable by fans and the media alike.

However, nothing in this world is absolute. This unimaginable occurrence was happening right now.

The team competition soon began. Even Chen Guo shook her head upon seeing the confrontation between the two sides. Excellent Era tried to coordinate, but their coordination was too mechanical. They didn’t seem to make any adjustments according to their opponent’s moves. It was as if they were following a script, executing it one line at a time.

Every single player executed their lines perfectly, but the problem was that their opponents weren’t blocks of wood. As soon as Void made adjustments, Excellent Era’s moves clearly stopped being effective. Soon afterwards, Void’s Ghostblade duo, Li Xuan and Wu Yuce, showed their might and completely gained control of the battle. Excellent Era quickly fell into a losing battle. Even the analyst and commentator could point out all of Excellent Era’s issues.

The team members of Excellent Era were losing so badly, they no longer had any confidence left. They knew that they needed to make adjustments according to the situation, but none of them dared to make them. All of them were afraid of being the ones to blame if they lost the match. As a result, they simply followed the tactical guidelines word for word.

It could be said that Excellent Era’s team was following the guidelines too well. This was a PvP competitive match. Following each step precisely was what players did in PvE situations. If they took that to a pro match, how could they not lose?

When the match between Team Excellent Era and Team Void finished, several other matches had finished as well. Among these was Team Bright Green, which had only been one point lower than Excellent Era. All of the fans checked the points tally. Fortunately, Team Bright Green gave them a thread of consolation because Team Bright Green also performed extremely poorly. Just like Team Excellent Era, they had only received 2 points. Team Excellent Era still had a one point advantage.

The teams already in the relegation zone wasn’t having it easy either. They were in just as tragic a position as Team Excellent Era. Speaking of which, even though Excellent Era had recently been declining, from the recent points earned, they couldn’t compare to Bright Green. Even so, the majority of people still favored Excellent Era.

After all, Excellent Era still had their resources. Their team’s strength was still there. As for Bright Green? Their team’s strength and record were their real strength. Bright Green couldn’t be used as an April Fool’s joke like Excellent Era could.

When the match ended, the Excellent Era fans were already numb to Team Excellent Era’s disastrous results. They didn’t curse or shout angrily. All of them felt dispirited as if their spirits had floated away.

“To think Excellent Era would actually lose so badly. It was totally contrary to my expectations. Tsk tsk tsk.” Steamed Bun Invasion sighed. He still believed the louder voice would have win. As for actual analysis of the match, he couldn’t compare to Chen Guo.

“Okay, stop reflecting on it.” Ye Xiu patted him on the back and turned his head towards Chen Guo: “Let’s get a late-night snack as a welcome gift for Steamed Bun.”

“Sure.” Chen Guo nodded his head and called over Tang Rou.

“Hi, Steamed Bun!” Tang Rou hadn’t squeezed into the crowd to watch the match. Only now did she come down. After hearing that Steamed Bun Invasion had arrived, she also ran over to call out to him.

“Soft Mist.” Ye Xiu introduced her by her game ID.

“Ah! It’s you! Amazing! You’re fierce in game and you look fierce too.” Steamed Bun Invasion was deeply moved.

“You look fierce….. Is that a compliment?” Tang Rou smiled.

“Of course of course.” Steamed Bun Invasion nodded his head.

“Okay, let’s go!” Chen Guo raised her boss voice and left the Internet Cafe together with them. After that, she took them to a place. Ye Xiu looked and sighed. He was also familiar with this place! When he was still in Excellent Era, he had been here many times to grab a late-night snack. However, at that time, the people he usually ate with…...

Hm?

Ye Xiu walked in, while looking back on his memories. Suddenly, he saw the person whom he had just been thinking about. He was sitting in his usual spot too.

Excellent Era’s boss, Tao Xuan.

Chapter 609 – Unexpectedly Here

Tao Xuan wasn’t the only person sitting here. Next to him was Club Excellent Era’s director, Cui Li.

These two people were, without a doubt, the two top executives of Club Excellent Era. For them to show up together here was already very surprising to Ye Xiu because today was Team Excellent Era’s away match. Moreover, this match would decide whether or not Team Excellent Era would drop into relegations. However, these two executives apparently didn’t go to support their team. Not long after the match ended, they came over here for a late night snack. It was very unusual.

Cui Li was sitting, facing the entrance. After seeing Ye Xiu, he signalled in front of him. Tao Xuan turned around and the two looked at Ye Xiu.

“What a coincidence! To think that we would bump into each other here.” Ye Xiu greeted.

Chen Guo was still choosing a seat and hadn’t been paying attention to her surroundings. When she heard Ye Xiu say something, she turned her gaze over and saw the two sitting there. She quickly recognized them. Cui Li frequently showed up in the news and Tao Xuan had personally come to visit the Internet Cafe.

“Ah!” Chen Guo suddenly felt the atmosphere become awkward, but after examining them for awhile, she realized none of them felt awkward at all. The three guys were acting very comfortable, as if this wasn’t an uncomfortable situation. Seeing their friendly smiles, the scene looked more like friends unexpectedly bumping into each other. It definitely didn’t look like there were any existing conflict between the three.

Chen Guo deeply felt like she had said enough. The other side also had people who could talk. Cui Li replied to Ye Xiu: “Yeah, what a coincidence!”

“I won’t keep bothering you guys then.” Ye Xiu clearly didn’t plan on conversing with the other side too much.

However, Cui Li was very interested in their group. He laughed: “You’re not bothering us at all. Are these fellows with you your future team members? How about introducing them to us? In the future, we’ll certainly be interacting with each other anyways.”

Chen Guo was the boss of an Internet Cafe and she often made deals with people. She immediately heard the deeper intent in Cui Li’s words. Right when she was about to reply, Steamed Bun Invasion actually responded faster than her. He jumped out and said: “Ah! So you’re also someone in this profession? How lucky! This little bro is Steamed Bun Invasion. My friends call me Steamed Bun. What’s your name?”

“Ha ha.” Cui Li smiled: “Cui Li, Club Excellent Era’s director. Some might call me a leader. This is our boss.”

“Oh oh oh oh!” Steamed Bun Invasion repeated “Oh” four times and then asked: “What’s that?”

“HA HA HA HA!!” Chen Guo laughed so hard that one of the waiters was startled. Tang Rou could control herself, but she was clearly having a hard time holding herself back. Only when Ye Xiu explained to Steamed Bun Invasion in a serious tone did he understand: “The director is someone who manages the Club in most situations. The boss is the owner of everything in the Club. He manages the Club behind the scenes.”

“Oh oh, very senior?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked.

“Of course. They’re much more senior than us.” Ye Xiu said.

“Age?” Steamed Bun Invasion looked at the two of them and asked.

“You were asking about their age?” Ye Xiu had a hard time following Steamed Bun Invasion’s thought process.

“Pretty much!” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

As for what this “Pretty much!” meant, even Ye Xiu had trouble understanding. However, one of Ye Xiu’s strengths was that he didn’t care much for what you meant. I’ll say what I want according to what I understand, so he continued: “If you’re talking about age, they’re both older than us.”

“Amazing!” Steamed Bun Invasion praised. His comment was another mystery within a mystery. From what it looked like, he was praising how old they were? But why was being old something so amazing?

Cui Li’s expression continued to appear calm, but he was feeling very embarrassed. He definitely didn’t believe that the person in front of him was showing his true character. He felt like Ye Xiu must have set this up beforehand in order to ridicule them. It couldn’t be said that Cui Li was a petty person. Steamed Bun Invasion’s brain wasn’t something most people could understand regardless. Cui Li thinking in this way meant he was still a normal person.

But Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t thinking about this at all. He sincerely patted the shoulders of the director: “We’re all on the same side. Let’s take care of each other!”

His words said one thing, but from his actions, it sounded like he would be looking after them and not the other way around. This time, Chen Guo didn’t laugh. She pulled at Steamed Bun Invasion: “Who’s following who? How are we on the same side?”

“Aren’t we all from the same circle?” Steamed Bun Invasion said, “Right. What team did they say they were from?”

“Excellent Era!” Cui Li was clearly angry as he repeated it again. His face clearly said: “Keep pretending! You just keep on pretending!”

But Steamed Bun Invasion immediately understood: “Excellent Era! Isn’t that that team, the one that lost really badly on TV just now?”

“.....” Cui Li.

“Yes.” Chen Guo nodded her head.

“Ah!” Steamed Bun Invasion looked at Cui Li with pity. He said in grief: “They shouldn’t have lost!”

“.......” This time, Cui Li didn’t answer him. He was afraid this was another trap. If he followed up, the other side would mock him. In his eyes, this guy named Steamed Bun was very terrifying.

“Steamed Bun, come sit over here!” At this moment, Ye Xiu had found seats and was already sitting together with Tang Rou. He called Steamed Bun Invasion over to sit with them.

Steamed Bun Invasion turned to look and felt that there was a lot of space near his seat, so he asked Cui Li and Tao Xuan: “Would you like to sit with us?”

“Ha ha, no need……” Cui Li’s smile looked very unnatural.

“If you lost, you lost. There’s no need to feel so bad.” Steamed Bun Invasion consoled them, “As long as you try hard, you’ll definitely have a future.”

What the f*ck are you talking about!! Cui Li was about to slam the table, but he saw Tao Xuan give him an eye, so he didn’t make any rash moves. He didn’t want to talk to Steamed Bun Invasion any longer, so he didn’t answer back.

Steamed Bun Invasion saw that they were ignoring him, so he ran off to sit together with Ye Xiu and the rest of the group.

“Amazing!” Tang Rou gave Steamed Bun Invasion a big thumbs up.

“Of course.” Steamed Bun Invasion said with excitement, but did he actually know what Tang Rou was praising him for?

“Bao Rongxing. Is that your real name?” Chen Guo asked.

“Yeah yeah! How did you know?” Steamed Bun Invasion asked excitedly.

“I was listening when you introduced yourself earlier.” Chen Guo tried hard to get used to talking with Steamed Bun Invasion.

“Yup yup, that’s my name! We’re all so familiar with each other, so you can just call me Steamed Bun.” Steamed Bun Invasion said.

“Okay, let’s order some food!” Chen Guo nodded her head. On the other side, Tao Xuan and Cui Li had already gotten up. They looked like they were about to leave.

“Enjoy yourself. We’ll be leaving.” Right when they were about to leave, Tao Xuan came over and said bye to the four of them. His tone of voice didn’t sound polite at all. In fact, it sounded very cold.

“Have a safe trip home! When you go back, work hard! You can do it!” Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t seem to notice. He didn’t say bye. Instead, he cheered them on. Chen Guo nearly burst out laughing again.

Soon afterwards, their food arrived. The four of them ate, while chatting with each other. They didn’t talk about anything serious until Chen Guo suddenly had a realization: “Hm? Today was an away match for Excellent Era. They didn’t go with their team?”

“Yeah!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Even though Chen Guo figured it out a bit slower, she also noticed this issue.

Excellent Era was doing terribly, but the two executives of the Club didn’t seem worried at all. Even for such an important match like today, they didn’t go with their team. If it wasn’t because of absolute confidence in the team, it must mean that they didn’t care about how Excellent Era did this season.

With Excellent Era’s terrible performances recently, they shouldn’t be very confident in the team, which meant that these two executives of Excellent Era didn’t have any hopes for this season, but no matter the case, if they get relegated, even if they returned the next year, without a year of fighting in the Professional League, the financial losses would be huge. It didn’t make sense for them not to care about relegations, no?

Chen Guo spoke her thoughts as she analyzed these issues. Ye Xiu listened and also nodded his head.

“Do you think that maybe after knowing you’re forming a team and preparing to go through the Challenger League, they’re losing intentionally to fight against you there?” Chen Guo suddenly said.

“I don’t think they’d go that far. Why would they care so much about me?” Ye Xiu laughed. If that was truly the reason, then they would letting their emotions affect their decisions. Tao Xuan had run the Club and taken care of the team for so many years. He had become an experienced boss long ago. How could he make such a decision just for such a simple reason? Ye Xiu clearly didn’t believe it.

“In any case, next season, Excellent Era will definitely be making big moves.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you mean?” Chen Guo asked.

“They’re already at such a state this season. If they don’t make any big moves next season, won’t Excellent Era go out of business?” Ye Xiu said.

“Then why don’t they hurry up and make any movements now?” Chen Guo asked.

“It’s probably because they can’t do anything right now with their current situation!” Ye Xiu said as he looked at the seats, where the two had sat in before.

Club Excellent Era. After Tao Xuan and Cui Li returned, they went into Tao Xuan’s office. Tao Xuan picked out a random bottle of wine from his wine rack and poured out two cups. One for him and one for Cui Li.

Cui Li took it and sipped on it. He spoke: “Do you think that guy is actually stupid or acting stupid?”

Tao Xuan sat in his big chair and stared at the ceiling. After a moment, he said: “I don’t know.”

“Where did Ye Xiu get this guy?” Cui Li said.

“He doesn’t matter. How are your discussions going? You didn’t get a chance to finish talking about it back there.” Tao Xuan said.

“Everything is going smoothly.” Cui Li had a big smile on his face.

“Have you explained what might happen?” Tao Xuan asked.

“I’ve explained it all clearly.”

“Good.” Tao Xuan nodded his head.

“What next?” Cui Li asked Tao Xuan.

“Don’t have Sun Xiang come out on stage for now.” Tao Xuan said.

“Okay.” Cui Li didn’t seem surprised either. They had clearly talked about this arrangement before. He let out a slight expression of hesitation, but it was because of another reason: “We might really encounter Ye Qiu’s team in the revival tournament.”

“That’s good too!” Tao Xuan smiled, “It’ll be more fun that way!”

Chapter 610 – Wei Chen Arrives

During this April Fool’s Day match, even though Excellent Era didn’t perform exceptionally well, their competitor had performed just as badly. Thus, that day’s featured event passed by without any commotion. Who would have thought that the next day, Club Excellent Era would hold a press conference and throw down a huge bomb.

In the press conference, Club Excellent Era’s director, Cui Li, announced: “The recent addition to the team, Sun Xiang, will not be participating in the remainder of the matches this season due to health reasons.”

When Cui Li answered the questions of the reporters, he answered in a very remorseful way. They had noticed Sun Xiang’s poor health a long time ago, but because of Team Excellent Era’s current predicament, they had insisted that he participated in the matches, but now, it had reached a point where he had to stop.

After answering many questions regarding the details of Sun Xiang’s condition, Cui Li confidently expressed that despite missing their ace player and character, the team would try even harder for their remaining matches. At the same time, however, Cui Li had stated that the Club had already made mental preparations for the worst case scenario. If the worst case scenario occurred, the Club and the team would face it with a proactive approach.

Even though his statements seemed modest and tactful, as professionals, the experienced news reporters could hear what was going on under the surface. Excellent Era had made preparations if they were relegated. This meant that Excellent Era wasn’t confident that they would be able to maintain their current position in the rankings.

What had happened to Excellent Era for such a famous team to not even be confident that they could stay in the Alliance? On paper, Excellent Era shouldn’t have any such trouble maintaining their ranki in the Alliance even without an ace player like Sun Xiang or a God’s character like One Autumn Leaf. However, Excellent Era seemed to already be prepared for such a situation.

“Is Excellent Era really planning on giving up this season and returning through the Challenger League next season?” Seeing the news, Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu in disbelief. They had discussed this possibility just last night.

“I don’t think they’d go that far, but it seems like the team really is a mess.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“Excellent Era is going to be finished?” Chen Guo had a hard time believing it.

Ye Xiu could only shake his head and didn’t comment.

“Wow! Wow!! WOW!!!!”

A string of repeated cries interrupted their conversation. Bao Rongxing also known as Steamed Bun Invasion had been brought over to the team’s living quarters after grabbing their late night snacks. That place had been just been given to Chen Guo on April 1st, so she didn’t have much time to tidy up the place. However, the wide and spacious living area was enough to make Bao Rongxing cry out in amazement.

After resting for the night, it was only until that morning that were they able to finish tidying up the place. At this moment, Bao Rongxing had arrived at Happy Internet Cafe. Last night, it had been too dark to see much and there had also been a huge crowd because of the match broadcast, so he didn’t get to have a good look at the Internet Cafe. Now that he had come again, he checked out the whole building from top to bottom. Just like last night, he was crying out in awe all over the place.

His cries clearly made Chen Guo very satisfied. She happily looked at Bao Rongxing, who was currently running down the stairs.

“What a big Internet Cafe!!” After Bao Rongxing had said enough wows, he exclaimed loudly in admiration. Once he gave this compliment, he didn’t forget to ask: “For such a big Internet Cafe, how many security guards do you have?”

“That……. There hasn’t been a need for any. The public security in this area is pretty good……” Chen Guo wasn’t sure how to answer his question. In any case, from what she remembered, she had never seen a situation where she had needed a professional security guard to take care of the matter. Even though there would occasionally be drunk customers or little thieves coming in, she didn’t see the need for a professional security guard.

“Public security…… not all problems can be solved by public security! How about you leave those matters to me?” Bao Rongxing confidently said.

‘I don’t mind.” Chen Guo laughed.

“Okay okay. Let me see! Can I move that table over there for me to sit at?” Bao Rongxing gestured at Happy Internet Cafe’s entrance. The table he was pointing at would block half the walkway.

“Uh…… I don’t think that’s necessary!” Chen Guo began to sweat.

“It’s necessary! It’s necessary! Only if we set it up this way will there not be any holes. If they want to run this way, the table will block them. If they run this way, I’ll give them a good punch and a kick. He won’t have anywhere to run!” Bao Rongxing explained his plan.

Chen Guo was starting to get anxious, but she didn’t know how to communicate with this guy. At the crucial moment, Ye Xiu stood forth: “Bao Rongxing, was this how you did things back at the Internet Cafe you were working at before?”

“Nope.” Bao Rongxing denied, “I would only come out when the boss called for me.”

“Then let’s do it that way too. If there are any problems, we’ll call for you to come out!” Ye Xiu said.

“I’m pretty used to doing it that way. I just don’t know if boss will think I’m dependable enough!” Bao Rongxing looked over at Chen Guo.

“Yes yes yes! You’re more than dependable enough! Here here here, you should spend most of your time on Glory! If something really does come up, I’ll definitely ask you to come out.” Chen Guo said.

“Okay!” Bao Rongxing replied with reluctance.

Afterwards, Bao Rongxing went to Room 213 on the second floor. Thinking about how more team members would eventually arrive, Chen Guo already knew that they would need a much larger practice room. Recently, she had already discussed with several people about remodeling the second floor. However, she hadn’t made any deals yet, so Room 213 would remain their practice room for now.

Bao Rongxing sat inside and once again praised the room. Chen Guo very much liked to hear these words and happily accepted them.

Then, they began to play Glory, but even though the four players were sitting close together, they were all very far in the game. Tang Rou and Bao Rongxing were still in the tenth server, but Tang Rou was a much higher level than Bao Rongxing, so they couldn’t play together right now.

Ye Xiu was in the Heavenly Domain and continued to level Lord Grim.

Chen Guo’s activities in the game were no longer just for fun. She rarely went on her main account. She usually used her alternate account to check on the guild storage and guild members. Apart from that, she frequently checked the forums for any news, trying to find movements of the going ons in the pro scene.

“Old Wei still isn’t here yet?” They had spent most of the morning tidying up the apartment, so Chen Guo told the Internet Cafe to be on the lookout, but when she returned, she didn’t hear about anyone looking for her.

“He said he’d come today.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s already dark. He’s still not here?” Chen Guo muttered, when her QQ suddenly rang. When she checked it, the little sister at the cash register told her that someone was looking for her.

“Hm? Maybe it’s Old Wei.” Chen Guo said.

“Really?” Ye Xiu put down his game. Tang Rou knew that another member had arrived, so she also got up to meet him. As for Bao Rongxing, he didn’t know what was going on, but seeing that everyone else was getting up, he felt like something must have happened and they needed him, so he immediately followed after them.

Chen Guo led the way. She walked down the stairs and saw an unshaven fellow smoking up a cloud. He had two big bags beside him. His cigarette made the little sister at the cash register knit her brows, but held herself back from saying anything, knowing that this was this boss’ guest. This guy didn’t seem to notice at all. He just looked around carelessly until his gaze reached the stairs. When he saw Chen Guo, his eyes immediately lit up.

“Old Wei!”

At this moment, Chen Guo heard Ye Xiu call out. That guy had already started moving towards them. Chen Guo stepped to the side and let Ye Xiu stand in front. However, when that guy walked over to them, he didn’t shake Ye Xiu’s hand or anything. He immediately looked at Chen Guo and asked Ye Xiu: “Who’s this beauty?”

“She’s our boss.” Ye XIu introduced.

“Ah, it’s nice to meet you.” Wei Chen extended his hands out. He wanted Chen Guo to shake his hand.

Chen Guo instantly felt conflicted! Her initial impression of Wei Chen was nothing good. And seeing how his eyes lit up when he saw a beauty, her impression of him continued to drop. She really didn’t want to shake his hand, but thinking about how he would be a part of the team, as the boss, shouldn’t she show her goodwill? Helpless, she extended her right hand too. She had already come to a decision. If this guy didn’t let go of her hand to take advantage of her, she wouldn’t give him any face.

But Wei Chen just shook her hand a few times and said “Hi, I’m Wei Chen” and then let go, but afterwards, Chen Guo discovered that this guy’s gaze had landed on Tang Rou’s body. His eyes lit up and as soon as he let go of Chen Guo’s hands, his hands seemed to be impatiently heading towards Tang Rou’s hands. He asked: “And this is?”

“Tang Rou.” Ye Xiu used her real name. Tang Rou had never met Wei Chen in-game, so introducing her by her game ID would be confusing.

TL Note: Tang Rou’s game ID in Chinese is Han Yan Rou, which sounds like an actual name

“Good name. It’s nice to meet you.” Wei Chen immediately wanted to shake Tang Rou’s hands. Chen Guo wanted to see how Tang Rou would deal with him, but another hand went up to meet his: “Hi! I’m Bao Rongxing! Those who are familiar with me call me Steamed Bun.”

“Ah….. hi……” Wei Chen was surprised by the sudden interruption. Then, he looked at this guy with his long hair. After saying hi, he turned his head to Ye Xiu: “These are all the members you’ve found so far?”

“Yeah, even though they’re new to the game, they’re quite good.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, right! Did you see this?” Wei Chen suddenly seemed to have thought of something. He ran back to his bags and fished out a folded newspaper.

Ye Xiu looked. It was the evening paper in City H. Even though it wasn’t specifically for reporting on eSports, Excellent Era was a big Club in City H, so it gave a brief report on Excellent Era’s press conference in the sports section.

“Of course I’ve seen it.” Ye Xiu only glanced at it. He knew that Wei Chen was certainly referring to this news, so he stuffed it back into the bag.

“What is Excellent Era planning? It seems like they’re already prepared to get relegated? If they actually get relegated and participate in the Challenger League next season, wouldn’t they bump into us? That could be bad!” Wei Chen seriously said.

Chen Guo was surprised. Wei Chen’s previous glances at her and Tang Rou made her think that this person was very dirty, but in an instant, this guy had already begun discussing the biggest issue the team faced.

For these guys, Glory was the most important thing in their life!

Chapter 611 – True Beginning

Wei Chen didn’t even put his luggage away, nor did he ask where he would be staying. His attention towards the two beauties had also been just a small spark that flickered away almost instantly. With the quickest speed, he began discussing today’s news in Glory because this piece of news was related to their team entering the Professional Alliance. In an instant, Chen Guo couldn’t help but have a change of heart towards this vulgar male. No matter his personality, his passion towards Glory was something that any player would respect.

“What does Excellent Era have planned?” Wei Chen urgently asked Ye Xiu.

“How should I know?” Ye Xius aid.

“You sound too much like an outsider.” Wei Chen was astonished, “What are you? Excellent Era’s great……”

“Great what!” Ye Xiu interrupted Wei Chen and pulled him outside the Internet Cafe. It was very busy at the Internet Cafe right now. If Wei Chen shouted out Ye Xiu’s identity as a God, would he ever live a peaceful life again? Happy Internet Cafe would quickly become an Excellent Era heroic monument. Fans would come every day to see and pay their respects to him.

Wei Chen quickly realized why Ye Xiu had pulled him outside. He looked down on Ye Xiu: “You’re still acting like a hidden boss?”

“Don’t call me Ye Qiu! Call me Ye Xiu, got it?” Ye Xiu scolded.

“Wow, you actually have an alternate account!” Wei Chen gasped.

“Go go go. Let’s get you to the living arrangements and we’ll talk there.’ Ye Xiu said.

“Go where?” Wei Chen asked.

“To where you’ll be staying.” Ye Xiu said. The others helped Wei Chen carry his luggage and walked over to Forest Park.

As soon as they walked into the spacious living area, Wei Chen wasn’t as wowed as Steamed Bun had been. The expression on his face was very similar to Ye Xiu’s expression when he had heard that they would be living in such a place. Clearly, as some of the earliest players to enter the scene, he and Ye Xiu had experienced the difficulties during the beginning of the pro scene. Even though it couldn’t compare to a professional Club, these comfortable conditions were more than enough to make him feel happy, especially for Wei Chen. When he had been in the pro scene, he hadn’t lasted long enough to enjoy the benefits of the Professional Alliance’s rapid growth and the flourishing Clubs. Chen Guo providing this living condition had deeply touched Wei Chen.

“There are six bedrooms upstairs. If we can gather everyone on the team, it will be two person to a room. Sorry everyone.” Chen Guo said.

“For another God, it might be a bit pitiful for them, but not for us. We’ve braved and endured the hard times. These living conditions definitely aren’t anything to be sorry about.” Wei Chen firmly said.

“Thanks.” Chen Guo smiled. Her impression of Wei Chen continued to improve.

Wei Chen circled around the place two times. He clearly didn’t have any problems with the living conditions. After walking around, he started talking about the announcement by Excellent Era today.

“I really don’t know what they’re planning.” Ye Xiu said helplessly.

“Excellent Era is right there. Why can’t you just go over and ask them?” Wei Chen was very unsatisfied.

“Do you think that’s even possible?” Ye Xiu said.

“Even if you had a falling out with Excellent Era, there are so many people in the Club. You don’t even have a single friend you can ask? What about that beautiful partner of yours? Did you also have a falling out with her?” Wei Chen said.

Wei Chen was obviously talking about Su Mucheng, but by the time Su Mucheng had entered the scene, Wei Chen had already retired, so his understanding of Su Mucheng was only at a normal spectator’s level. A normal spectator just knew that Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng had been good partners with each other for several year, but this description was towards their performance on stage. As for their private relationship, they could only listen to gossip and guess. No one had any concrete proof.

When Wei Chen spoke about her, Chen Guo responded. She obviously knew that Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu didn’t have any problems with each other, so she also looked at Ye Xiu.

“That isn’t too convenient, is it?” Ye Xiu said.

“Why not?” Wei Chen asked.

“She’s still a pro player under Excellent Era’s banner.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hm?” Wei Chen sounded surprised, “You really are good partners! It seems like your relationship with each other is very good to make even someone as shameless as you to care. You don’t want her to be stuck between the two sides, right?”

Chen Guo listened and immediately understood. It was very convenient for Su Mucheng to spy on Excellent Era, but why didn’t Ye Xiu ask her? It wasn’t that Ye Xiu didn’t think about it. He didn’t want her to get mixed up in this mess. After all, Su Mucheng was still a member of Excellent Era. If she blurted out the team’s secrets, it would very unprofessional.

“So it’s like that……” After Wei Chen thought about it for a bit, he suddenly had an idea: “How about you let me use your QQ account? I’ll go ask and then you can just pretend that you got hacked. How about it?”

“......’ Ye Xiu didn’t answer. He just looked expressionlessly at Wei Chen.

“Hm? No good? Too bad. You have such an amazing resource and you’re not even using it. What a pity. In order to reach our goal, we have to be ruthless and win through any means necessary, but you’ve got so many emotions. I look down on you. I have to. Where’s my room?”

“You can pick any one you like upstairs!” Ye Xiu acted like he didn’t hear Wei Chen’s previous rant and answered his question.

“I’ll put my stuff down before I continuing to look down on you.” Wei Chen picked up his luggage.

“I’m in room one upstairs. Do you want to be my roommate?!” Steamed Bun yelled loudly.

“Are there any open rooms available?” Wei Chen asked.

“Yes. Steamed Bun is living in room one. Every other room is empty.” Chen Guo replied.

“Then I’ll pick a room for myself for now…..” Wei Chen said. He didn’t go into Steamed Bun’s room and put his luggage down in room two. He didn’t plan on immediately unpacking though. He threw his luggage in and then came back downstairs. He still wanted to talk to Ye Xiu.

“You should at least have some guess as to what Excellent Era is planning, right?” Wei Chen impatiently asked.

“Uh, with my understanding of Excellent Era’s current team members, Excellent Era really has planned to get relegated. However, it’s not necessarily intentional. It really might be because they have no other choice. Today, they announced Sun Xiang was sick in order to find an excuse for getting relegated. If they didn’t have to, I’m sure they wouldn’t get relegated.” Ye Xiu said.

“With Excellent Era’s foundation, how can they not even have confidence in staying in the Professional League?” Wei Chen didn’t understand.

“Their morale is gone. It’s not easy for the team! Excellent Era’s problem isn’t with their skill, but rather with their mentality.” Ye Xiu said.

“Mentality?” Wei Chen said.

“They don’t want to be the one to blame…..” Ye Xiu sighed.

“Why does that sound so lowly of them?” Wei Chen was dumbstruck.

“Excellent Era’s players have gotten in a conflict with me in the game before. They ended up getting wiped .” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you mean by Excellent Era’s players? Their starting roster?” Wei Chen was astonished.

“Pretty much!” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re joking. How did you do that?!” Wei Chen didn’t believe him.

“I had the advantage in numbers.” Ye Xiu said.

“How many more?”

“Two.” Ye Xiu said.

“Those weren’t normal players were they?” Wei Chen said.

“They were players from Heavenly Justice. They’re the current members of the future Team Heavenly Swords.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then their skill should be pretty good, right?” Wei Chen said.

“They’re okay.”

“But to wipe out a pro team like Excellent Era. Isn’t that too much…..” Wei Chen said.

“I agree.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Couldn’t you be a little more f*cking modest? Just a little bit?” Wei Chen said.

“I’m just telling the truth. Didn’t you also say that you find it inconceivable?” Ye Xiu said.

“I find your inability to be modest inconceivable.” Wei Chen said.

“You’re joking! With how unscrupulous you are, how could you possibly find anything inconceivable?” Ye Xiu said.

“Ahem!” Chen Guo coughed: “Are you two practicing your trash talking?”

The two glared at each other.

“I’m warning you not to run away from the subject!” Wei Chen said in a serious voice like he was the team captain.

“I said what I needed to say.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, if it’s just that, then you might affect the mentality of those Excellent Era members for a bit of time, but a single loss shouldn’t make the entire team depressed for so long. That doesn’t seem like the type of drive a pro player should have.” Wei Chen said.

Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Maybe we should look at their recordings and analyze their performances.” Wei Chen said.

“We should.” Ye Xiu said.

“Are there any computers here? Is there wifi?” Wei Chen looked around.

‘Not yet……” Chen Guo said. She had only just gotten the apartment yesterday, so she wasn’t done setting everything up.

“Then let’s go back to the Internet Cafe?” Wei Chen asked.

“Sure!” Ye Xiu got up.

The other three followed them. They were pretty much just listening to their conversation. Towards the pro scene, even though Wei Chen had retired for so long, he was still much better than the other three. No matter how skilled Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were, in terms of their ability to analyze issues, they couldn’t compare to these two experienced pros.

They left the apartment and returned to the Internet Cafe. Room 213 was a four person room, but now they had five people. There weren’t enough computers. Fortunately, they were just watching a recording, so they only needed one computer.

Ye Xiu opened up the VOD folder on his computer. All of the videos lined up made Wei Chen comment: “Not bad, not bad. It seems like you’ve been doing your homework.”

“Let’s watch this match. This is the fight we had in game. It was from here that Excellent Era’s performance started to decline.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay.” Wei Chen nodded. These two leaned forward in front of the computer. Chen Guo and Tang Rou looked at each other. They felt like they had become outsiders. Steamed Bun didn’t seem to have any thoughts. He just squeezed behind them and watched the video very seriously.

“Comrades, we need to study this carefully! If Excellent Era really gets relegated, they’ll be our strongest opponents in the Challenger League. We have to use this time wisely and understand our opponent. Now, the former God, former captain of Excellent Era, and the most shameless person in all of Glory, Ye….. Xiu will be analyzing this match for everyone.” Wei Chen said.

Even though his words didn’t say much, Chen Guo suddenly realized that from this moment onwards, their team would truly begin operating.

Chapter 612 – Lose the battle, but win the war

“Did you watch this match?” Just before the match began, Wei Chen asked Ye Xiu.

“I watched a bit of it after it concluded.” Ye Xiu said. That day, Happy Internet Cafe hadn’t broadcast this match, so Ye Xiu had watched a recording of it later.

“Oh.” Wei Chen nodded his head and didn’t say anything else. On the screen, the match had begun. It was progressing quite quickly. By the time the individual competition and the group arena ended, Wei Chen already had his hands against his forehead.

“You devil! Look at the sins you’ve committed! What exactly did you do to them?!” Wei Chen grieved.

Ye Xiu was expressionless. He continued to quietly watch the match. In the team competition, Excellent Era lost miserably. For this match between Excellent Era and Thunderclap, the final result was 1 point to 9 points in favor of Thunderclap. Their performance had been nauseating to watch. Wei Chen couldn’t even keep watching. It was so terrible that, in a post-match interview, Team Thunderclap’s captain Xiao Shiqin didn’t even know what to say. Facing the question “how did you think your opponents performed today?”, a question every player could recite backwards, Xiao Shiqin had been stumped.

“There wasn’t even one good point about that match. Everything about it was terrible. Do you have the post-match statistics?” Wei Chen asked.

“I do.” Ye Xiu opened up another folder with documents on the statistics for every match. Each document matched up with a recording.

“Wow, holy sh*t…… hurry up and get me a bucket. I’m going to puke.” Wei Chen glanced at the post-match statistics and remarked.

“Let’s watch the next match!” Ye Xiu was calmer.

“The next match isn’t going to be like this too is it? How about you give me a summary. I’m scared that my old heart won’t be able to handle it. It isn’t easy for someone my age.” Wei Chen pressed on his stomach and acted like he was an elderly grandpa. In reality, his “age” was only relative to Glory’s professional scene. At this moment, he wasn’t even 30 yet. He was a young person no matter how you looked.

“They got two points in this match.” Ye Xiu calmly stated.

“Oh, then let’s begin!” Wei Chen looked as if he were about to watch a horror film. Moments after the match began, everyone heard someone shout: “The bucket has arrived!!!”

Everyone turned their heads in astonishment. Steamed Bun had actually slipped out of the room who knew when and had returned just now. He carried a bucket in his hands and handed it over to Wei Chen: “Go ahead and puke……”

“......” Wei Chen stared stupidly at Steamed Bun: “Bro, are you serious?”

“Are you serious? Are you going to puke or not?” Steamed Bun questioned.

Wei Chen turned towards Ye Xiu: “Is he really going to be a part of our team?”

“Mmhm.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“You’re joking, right?” Wei Chen asked.

“Stop with this nonsense. It’s starting.” Ye Xiu said to Wei Chen before turning to speak to Steamed Bun: “Steamed Bun, put the bucket down. Let’s watch the match!”

“I’ll be putting the bucket over here. If you need to puke, just say the word!” Steamed Bun called out before placing the bucket in the corner.

The recording began. This match had been that day’s highlight match. Happy Internet Cafe had broadcast this match. It was between Excellent Era and Samsara. In the individual competition, Excellent Era had earned a total of two points. In the group arena, Zhou Zekai swept the field. During the team competition, the fight had been just as nauseating to watch as it had been in the previous match.

“This guy adjusts quickly. He performed quite well in his match.” They replayed the recording. In the second round of the individual competition, Wei Chen praised one of Excellent Era’s players.

The winner of this second round was Excellent Era’s Liu Hao. Ye Xiu nodded his head at the praise, while Chen Guo gave a snort of contempt.

Excellent Era lost the third round, but having won two points already, this loss was easier to accept. At this moment, Wei Chen was more spirited. He felt like this individual competition didn’t require the bucket. However, in the group arena, Excellent Era had been cleanly swept by a single enemy, making Wei Chen speechless. In the end, he gave a way out for Excellent Era: “That punk Zhou Zekai is looking pretty stylish now! Excellent Era isn’t in good condition either. Beating them 1v3 isn’t too surprising.”

Ye Xiu didn’t comment. The match moved to the team competition.

Even though Wei Chen hadn’t watched this team competition before, he knew the end result because Ye Xiu had told him that Excellent Era had only earned two points total in this entire match. However, they were studying the match, so the process during which it happened was more important than the end result. Right now, they needed to analyze what problems Excellent Era had encountered during this match.

“What’s wrong? Would you like the bucket?” After the team competition ended, Ye Xiu asked.

Wei Chen actually shook his head. He didn’t say anything, as if he was thinking about something.

“Keep going?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Continue!” Wei Chen didn’t express any opinions about this team competition. He only told Ye Xiu to play the next match.

The two continued to quietly watch match after match. Once the recordings finished, they would check the statistics, but none of them made any verbal exchanges. As for Chen Guo, Tang Rou, and Steamed Bun, they had been watching along too. However, whether or not they were analyzing it carefully or watching it for fun, only they knew.

They could skip over the short breaks in between the competitions, so they watched each match in one sitting. Moreover, Excellent Era usually got dominated, so the matches progressed swiftly. They practically all finished in less than an hour. They kept watching matches, not caring about the amount of time that passed, until they had reviewed all of the matches at least once. Midway through the session, Wei Chen had gotten a pen and paper. He was constantly writing stuff down. Ye Xiu occasionally glanced to see what he was writing, but didn’t do anything else.

After the final match concluded, everyone breathed a sigh of relief.

“Did you two discover anything?” Chen Guo impatiently wanted to know the results. For her, this was like a suspense film.

“Excellent Era kept on losing. Did we make a mistake?” Steamed Bun commented, but he clearly didn’t know what was going on. This guy was an expert in Glory, but he didn’t have much understanding of its pro scene.

On the other hand, Tang Rou didn’t express any opinions. She just silently waited for Ye Xiu and Wei Chen to speak.

“What are your thoughts?” Wei Chen asked Ye Xiu.

“I’ve watched them all before. Why don’t you tell me your thoughts?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Lose the battle, but win the war. What do you think?” Wei Chen said.

“Sounds about right…..” Ye Xiu let out a sigh.

“What do you guys mean by that?” Chen Guo asked.

Wei Chen lifted up his notebook with a bunch of arcane symbols on it and pointed at these symbols that no one could read: “The problem with Excellent Era is the mentality of their players. From these matches and statistics, we can see some of this.”

“First there’s the impact on some of them from the fight in-game. This impact could clearly be seen. That disgusting match that made me want to puke was because of this reason. The person affected the most was their core player, Sun Xiang. The impact of that in-game fight on Sun Xiang changed over time. This can be seen through his performance in this match. Initially, he had been struck a heavy blow. He was unable to concentrate during the match, so he frequently made noob mistakes, but as time went on, he slowly began to adjust. However, this doesn’t mean that the impact from that in-game fight completely disappeared. After that match, Sun Xiang became impatient to show off his skill. To put it plainly, at his current level, pursuing glory is a good choice. His skill has already been publicly acknowledged. He doesn’t need any proof, but clearly, because of a certain God, he might have started to doubt himself, which was why he appears so impatient. Simply put, in the beginning he was unable to concentrate, but afterwards, he became too focused, causing his playing to become erratic. This is how a noob behaves. Instead of maintaining his condition, he keeps up his guard against everyone.” Wei Chen said.

“A perfect example of an experienced player the opposite of Sun Xiang is that punk Liu Hao. Apart from an extremely terrible first round, he performed quite steadily. If you pay attention to his individual competition and group arena win rate, you can see all these things present. His performances have been pretty good. Even with the team being a complete mess, Liu Hao still showed moments of brilliance.

“As for the other players, most of them fit into one of two categories. A portion of them had been deeply impacted by a certain God. The others like Su Mucheng and even a few substitute players were normal. However, even if this God didn’t harm them in any way, their team brought them down. Because the team performed terribly, their normal conditions were also brought down with the team. Afterwards, they continually infect each other, resulting in Excellent Era’s current plight.”

“If we pick out Sun Xiang and Liu Hao, these two are the only exceptions. After Sun Xiang woke up, he was able to piece himself back together. Unfortunately, he was unable to piece the team back together, along with himself. There are probably a lot of reasons why. For example, he’s a new member of the team. Even if he holds the title of team captain, he doesn’t have much of an influence on the team, or maybe he was only in a rush to prove himself and didn’t think of the team’s conditions. Or he might have thought of it, but the team’s condition was so bad, that he didn’t know how to fix it, so he didn’t bother. As for Liu Hao, our God here should explain it. He clearly knows this person better than I do. His analysis would be much more accurate and trustworthy.” Wei Chen chattered a bunch and then shifted it over to Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu let out a sigh: “Liu Hao is only thinking about his own future. He has already abandoned his team.”

“Ha ha, so it really is like that. That’s why I said, lose the battle, win the war. Even though Excellent Era performed terribly, someone like Liu Hao was able to display his strength. Not only was he dragged down by his team, he even showed brilliance in this sort of environment. By putting himself above the others, he’s probably planning on using this opportunity to climb up into a higher branch! Also, I’m afraid Liu Hao isn’t the only one with these types of thoughts. The team’s already like this. Their record is so poor already. It’d be strange if they didn’t have these thoughts.” Wei Chen said.

Chapter 613 – Teammate

“When a team faces a crisis, isn’t working together to improve and resolve the crisis the most logical thing to do? But when Excellent Era faced this crisis, with Liu Hao at the lead, a few of the players have already regarded the team to be a sinking ship and they plan on abandoning the ship to save their own lives.” Ye Xiu concluded.

“Then for what reason are they hiding Sun Xiang?” Chen Guo asked.

“This decision will only benefit them whether or not Excellent Era ends up getting relegated.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?” Chen Guo asked.

“There are only two possible results for Excellent Era this season. The first possibility would be that they don’t get relegated, which would be great. Even with Sun Xiang, there wouldn’t be a better result. But without Sun Xiang, if Excellent Era can hold onto their spot, they can make an announcement telling everyone know that they can place their hopes on Excellent Era next season. After all, Excellent Era can’t consider keeping their spot a victory. They need to let their fans know that their goal is to be the champion.” Ye Xiu said.

“If they get relegated, they would use Sun Xiang as an excuse saying that it was due to his absence?” Chen Guo deduced.

“That’s only one excuse. It would be disastrous if they actually got relegated. Excellent Era needs to do a lot of work to put their fans at ease. Just look at today’s news. Sun Xiang suddenly had to stop because of an injury. He had been playing with the injury for such a long time and needed to stop. As a result, they even gave an excuse for their previous performances. However, for Excellent Era, such terrible performances can’t only be due to their ace player being injured. This summer, Excellent Era will probably have a huge upheaval. Only something like that could give the team’s fans any hope. Once the fans have lost hope in the team, the team is truly in a predicament. Thus, everything Excellent Era is doing right now is to urge their fans to continue supporting them. No matter the end result, they absolutely cannot allow the fans to lose hope in them.”

‘The reason they’re hiding Sun Xiang and using him as an excuse is because Sun Xiang represents the core of Excellent Era.” Ye Xiu added.

“Got it!” Chen Guo let out a sigh, “After knowing all of this, what should we do?”

“We……. we can’t do anything for now.” Ye Xiu let out a bitter laugh, “We’ll have to wait until the results come out first.”

“However, it’d be best if everyone lit some incense for Excellent Era, because if Excellent Era gets relegated, Excellent Era being in the Challenger League will only be more terrifying than it is right now. It’d be best if we didn’t meet such an opponent in the Challenger League.” Wei Chen added. This unscrupulous guy was also filled with worry.

“Then what if we beat Excellent Era in the Challenger League? Would Excellent Era be completely done for?” Tang Rou suddenly asked.

“Eliminate Excellent Era……” Wei Chen stared blankly.

Once Excellent Era gets eliminated, even though they could participate in next year’s Challenger League, how could anyone support a team that needed to attempt the Challenger League twice? Would a God like Sun Xiang be willing to waste his golden years in the Challenger League? If that actually happened, Excellent Era would fall into a vicious cycle and they would eventually fall.

“Are you planning on personally putting an end to the dynasty you created?” Wei Chen turned to Ye Xiu.

“What do you mean plan? If we actually meet them, we have to beat them! That’s what it means to be a pro. I know you have no idea what that means.” Ye Xiu said.

“Do you know?” Wei Chen said with contempt.

The two people once again began talking trash each other. Luckily, Chen Guo promptly interrupted them: “If that’s the case, we’ll have to work even harder. It’s getting late. How about we all take a rest.”

The boss had spoken. Everyone still respected her words. Plus, they had been watching the match recordings for a long time, so they really were a bit exhausted. They left the room. Wei Chen walked to the head of the flight of stairs and waited there as if he wanted to say something to Ye Xiu, but then he saw Ye Xiu walk into his room.

“What’s going on?” Wei Chen immediately went back, but then he saw Chen Guo and Tang Rou also go into this room.

“What is this?!” Wei Chen was even more astonished now, but he heard a bang as the door closed shut.

“Old Wei, are you coming or not?” Bao Zi had long since reached the bottom of the stairs and called out to Wei Chen.

“Impudent! You can’t call me Old Wei!” Even though Wei Chen was astonished, he couldn’t just break down the door to see what was going on. Hearing Bao Zi call out to him, he scolded him, while walking down the stairs.

“Then what do I call you? Wei Old?” Bao Zi asked.

“...... Just call me Old Wei…….” Wei Chen gave up.

“Didn’t I say so earlier!” Bao Zi said.

“What did you say?” Wei Chen asked.

“What?” Bao Zi.

“Hm?” Wei Chen.

“Hm!”

“Hm what!!” Wei Chen looked up speechlessly. Just this teammate alone made him have some doubts about his decision towards Ye Xiu’s invitation.

After resting for the night, everyone gathered together at the Internet Cafe the next morning. When Chen Guo saw that two people had already arrived, she immediately began changing the second floor’s layout. She even thought about directly remodeling the second floor to transform it into the team’s practice room, but later, Ye Xiu put in great effort to dissuade her.

“We’ve just started. There is no need to be so lavish. Having a room without any disturbances is already very good. There isn’t actually any need to make changes yet. Just let us have a few rooms. We don’t all need to sit together!” Ye Xiu urged.

“It’s still better if everyone’s nearby.” Although Chen Guo gave up on completely renovating the second floor, she was still adamant towards having everyone sit together. The workers she had contacted before arrived today and began working.

Wei Chen and Bao Zi came to the Internet Cafe together and went straight to the second floor. As Wei Chen passed the inner rooms, he sneakily looked into them, unlike Bao Zi, who didn’t even take a glance.

Chen Guo was personally supervising the changes. Seeing that the two had come, she called out to them and then led them to Room 213. After Wei Chen and Bao Zi went in, they saw that Ye Xiu and Tang Rou were already busy. When they looked, the two people were both in a dungeon!

Teammate Bao Zi had already shocked Wei Chen in a way. At this moment, he prepared himself to check on his other teammate. When he saw that Tang Rou was a Battle Mage, Wei Chen couldn’t help but glance at Ye Xiu. With such a top-tier Battle Mage coaching her, this girl’s skill should be very good, right?”

Speaking of which, Wei Chen had never seen Bao Zi play before. He had only ever interacted with him in person. Although he knew that if Ye Xiu had pulled them onto the team, they must have at least some skill, but he couldn’t help but have some doubts.

Wei Chen watched as Tang Rou played. On the other side, Bao Zi had sat down, turned on his computer, and inserted his account card. Then, he called out: “Old Wei, come sit here. How about we compare notes, so I can see how good you are?”

Wei Chen nearly coughed up blood all over the wall. He hadn’t even examined him yet and this guy dared to ask him how good he was?

“Sure! Let me see how good you really are!” Wei Chen said and stopped watching Tang Rou play. He went over and sat down. He was ready to give this steamed bun a good lesson.

“I’m here. Where are you?” Wei Chen rushed into the Arena and shouted.

“Normal server, Room 5684.” Bao Zi was much calmer than Wei Chen.

But when Wei Chen clicked on the room, he immediately entered. Bao Zi didn’t even set a password on this room. Then, he saw that Bao Zi hadn’t even made it a 1v1. There were already seven players inside. It was clearly a team battle.

“What are you doing?” Wei Chen asked strangely. He turned his head to look at Bao Zi’s screen. Steamed Bun was sitting all alone in a room waiting for him!”

Just when he was about to ask, Ye Xiu poked his head out: “Is this your first time playing? You want to go to the normal server Arena from the Heavenly Domain?”

Ye Xiu didn’t need to look to know what problem the two had encountered.

“Tenth server?” Wei Chen was surprised. Then, he carefully checked Bao Zi’s screen. His character was a Brawler called Steamed Bun Invasion, Level 61.

Wei Chen suddenly became furious. This f*cking Bao Zi wanted to test his strength and he wasn’t even max level yet. At the same time, he recalled that Ye Xiu had said that these two people were new to the game. He didn’t think much of it at that time. Now that he was seeing it for himself, tenth server, Level 61 character, Bao Zi was very new to the game! He probably started playing when the tenth server was released! If that were the case, then he must have only played for four months at best.

Someone who had only played for four months wanted to join the pro scene? As a former pro player, Wei Chen didn’t dare to believe it. He needed to check on this Bao Zi’s skill.

“You wait!” Wei Chen said and had his Windward Formation enter a normal server. Through this way, a Heavenly Domain character could enter the normal server Arena, but his normal Arena record wouldn’t transfer to his Heavenly Domain record.

“Make a new room. Fixed Field.” Wei Chen said to Bao Zi.

“Hm?” Bao Zi was puzzled. He turned his head to look at Wei Chen’s screen and immediately understood: “Wow, you don’t have any equipment! Of course we have to go to the fixed field.”

Wei Chen was about to cough blood again. His Windward Formation really was naked, but of course that was the case. When he came back to the normal server from the Heavenly Domain, his equipment would be left behind. Was that why he asked for the Fixed Field? Of course not! It was because there was a level discrepancy between them. The issue of not having equipment would be fixed in the Fixed Field too, but that wasn’t the main reason. It definitely wasn’t!

“Room number!” Wei Chen burst out when he arrived at the Arena.

Chapter 614 – Comparing Notes

“Ha ha, little punk, now you know this senior’s might!”

Wei Chen laughed. He had clearly beaten Steamed Bun to a pulp. Steamed Bun was more than good enough to crush an overwhelming majority of players, but he wasn’t a match against an experienced opponent.

Wei Chen was, without a doubt, an experienced player and a former pro at that. Even though he was no longer as good as he had been in his glory days, he could only accumulate more and more experience. On the other hand, Steamed Bun was someone who had only started playing Glory for four months. Even if he had talent, had a strong foundation, and improved quickly, it was far from enough to beat an expert like Wei Chen.

“Aw, I lost.” Steamed Bun replied with sorrow.

“Don’t be so emotional. This is completely normal.” Wei Chen laughed delightedly.

“Tsk tsk, how despicable.” Ye Xiu didn’t even watch the match. He had only heard their results. With Wei Chen’s skill, being so delighted about beating a beginner who had only been playing for four months was really despicable. He couldn’t help but express his opinions.

“Right, there’s no need to be so emotional.” Steamed Bun seemed to have come to a realization, “I can just try again!”

“What?” Wei Chen was surprised. Steamed Bun’s thought process going from “no need to be emotional” to “trying again” caught him off guard.

“Come come come. Don’t be afraid. Let’s play again.” Steamed Bun said.

“F*ck, you think I’m afraid of a noob like you?” Wei Chen said and accepted the challenge.

“Ha ha ha ha ha!”

“Ha ha ha ha ha!”

“Ha ha ha ha ha!”

Wei Chen laughed wildly every time he won. His laughter became louder each time. Even the workers outside were starting to feel annoyed. Chen Guo opened the door to the room and looked inside: “What’s going on?”

“Eight to zero!” Wei Chen wrote a “八” in the air. (TL: 八 means eight)

“Seriously?” Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu in astonishment.

“What are you looking at me for? It’s between him and Steamed Bun.” Ye Xiu said.

“Seriously?” Chen Guo looked at Wei Chen in astonishment. Her disdain was exactly the same as Ye Xiu’s initial reaction. Chen Guo also felt that, with Wei Chen’s status, it was too low of him to feel so delighted for destroying Steamed Bun.

But Wei Chen clearly didn’t care and continued to look at Steamed Bun in glee: “What do you think now, you little punk?”

“Amazing, amazing. I didn’t think you would be so amazing. What’s your background?” Steamed Bun sighed.

“You’d better sit still when you hear it! This senior is Team Blue Rain’s former captain and the original owner of the great Swoksaar! I hope I didn’t scare you!” Wei Chen spoke.

“Oh.”

“OH???????” Wei Chen clearly wasn’t happy with Steamed Bun’s indifferent reaction.

“Sooksoo, what’s that?” Steamed Bun asked.

“You don’t even know who that is?! That’s the number one Warlock in Glory. A godly existence!” Wei Chen exclaimed.

“Oh!” Steamed Bun gasped.

“He really needs some catching up to do.” Wei Chen spoke to Ye Xiu.

“Is it important to know that type of stuff?” Ye Xiu asked back.

“Of course.” Wei Chen acted like he was a holy saint, “It’s passing on one’s knowledge and conviction to the future generations.”

“...... How about you talk about Steamed Bun’s skill!” Ye Xiu shifted topics.

“Uh…… he’s not bad. For a player who’s only been playing for four months, he’s pretty decent.” Wei Chen commented.

“You’re not speaking with much confidence.” Ye Xiu remarked.

“F*ck, how am I lacking confidence?” Wei Chen shouted.

“You almost lost, didn’t you...” Ye Xiu said.

“Tch, he’s got a long ways to go if he wants to beat me!” Wei Chen said out loud, but on QQ, he shot Ye Xiu a message: “Sh*t, I got careless once and he almost turned it around.”

“Ha ha ha, who told you to hold on for dear life.” Ye Xiu replied.

“I wasn’t holding on for dear life. I can still beat him, but that Steamed Bun always makes weird moves. Even though most of the time he’s a complete mess, he occasionally makes you really sweat.” Wei Chen typed.

“Quite surprising, right?” Ye Xiu remarked.

“Indeed. Once that little punk improves his fundamentals and game knowledge, who knows what he’ll be like. From the looks of it, if we helped him consolidate his game knowledge and have him do some practice to improve his mechanics, he’ll be good. In terms of experience, teaching him too much would actually be harmful.” Wei Chen said.

“Who needs you to say that?” Ye Xiu replied.

“With this guy’s style, once you die, oh that’s not right, once you retire, you can give your unspecialized to him. That will certainly be a scene to see.” Wei Chen said.

“Oh?” Ye Xiu was surprised, “But an unspecialized…..”

“I know what you want to say. According to common knowledge, only someone who is proficient with every class can play an unspecialized character, but have you ever thought about what would happen if you had a completely blank slate begin playing an unspecialized and have him treat it as a complicated class?” Wei Chen asked.

“Hm? That’s definitely an interesting thought.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Even though Steamed Bun isn’t a completely blank slate, he’s very simple-minded. His noobness isn’t because he’s new to the game, but rather his personality. If you had him treat your unspecialized as a new class, he might actually be able to do it. Think about it, with a 120 extremely quick, short cooldown skills at his disposal and his chaotic play style, what would that be like?” Wei Chen wondered.

“Even more chaotic.” Ye Xiu said.

“But that’s what makes him scary!” Wei Chen felt some lingering fear in his heart.

“It’s just that unspecialized characters won’t last very long!” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s true. Glory hasn’t raised the level cap in three years, right?” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah!”

“I suspect that by the time we make it back into the pro scenes, they’ll have raised the level cap at least once.” Wei Chen said.

“Yeah….. But every time they raise the level cap, it will usually only be five levels, so Level 75. It’s something that an unspecialized can still cope with for now.” Ye Xiu said.

“We’ll wait and see! When the time is right, we can let Steamed Bun try out an unspecialized.” Wei Chen said.

“Okay.” Ye Xiu agreed.

“What about that pretty girl? How good is she?” Wei Chen asked.

“Why don’t you play a practice match against her and see for yourself?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Okay!” Wei Chen happily agreed.

“Little Tang, how about you have a practice match with Wei Chen?” Ye Xiu turned to Tang Rou.

“Sure! Let me finish this dungeon first!” Tang Rou was currently leveling inside a dungeon. She definitely wouldn’t refuse to play a practice match. She loved to compete.

Soon afterwards, Tang Rou exited the dungeon and went to the Fixed Field. Wei Chen had already set up a room, waiting for her. Tang Rou went in and the two immediately started fighting. Ye Xiu didn’t watch them and continued to level up his Lord Grim. Tang Rou was sitting next to him though, so he would occasionally take a peek at the situation.

Tang Rou’s situation was virtually the same as Steamed Bun’s. Both of them lacked experience and experience was Wei Chen’s strength. Ye Xiu didn’t know how badly Steamed Bun had been beaten up, but Tang Rou was being completely suppressed. There wouldn’t be any suspense in who would win, but Ye Xiu reckoned that Wei Chen could feel some pressure from Tang Rou’s playstyle.

In the first match, Wei Chen easily won, just like Ye Xiu predicted.

“Your mechanics are very good. Quick and precise.” Wei Chen pointed out Tang Rou’s strengths after winning.

“Thanks! Again?” Tang Rou asked.

“Come!” Wei Chen happily accepted. On QQ, Ye Xiu sent him a laughing emoji.

“What?” Wei Chen was puzzled.

“You have to stop.” Ye Xiu said.

“Stop? This massacre? It’s no pressure at all!” Wei Chen said.

“Ha ha.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Ha, your sister!” Wei Chen replied and then fought again.

“Ha ha, I’m sorry pretty girl. I won again.” Wei Chen said at the end of the following match.

“Again?”

“Sure!”

When the third match began, Ye Xiu dungeoned, while sipping his tea. He didn’t need to look. He could tell from the sounds of their keyboards and clicking that the pace for this match was going faster. Tang Rou was going all out…… her peak condition usually didn’t show at the start of the match. Her true skill oftentimes didn’t appear until she faced a predicament. She was a perfect example of becoming stronger with the strength of her opponent.

However, Wei Chen still won the third match. Wei Chen gave a cough. He was just about to say something, when Tang Rou stared at him, her battle spirit burning: “Again?”

Wei Chen looked around until he stopped on Ye Xiu, but he discovered that Ye Xiu had hidden himself behind his monitor.

“Come……” Wei Chen didn’t refuse, but his voice was becoming drier.

“What the f*ck is this!!!” He quickly shot Ye Xiu a message on QQ.

“Stop.” Ye Xiu said again, but this time, Wei Chen was starting to understand.

On the fourth match, Wei Chen won again, but before he could say anything, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had already clicked ready in the lobby. When he raised his head to look at Tang Rou, she was staring at him, extremely eager for another try.

“Last match……” Wei Chen was starting to lose confidence.

Tang Rou didn’t comment. She continued to try her hardest and in the end, Tang Rou won.

Wei Chen let out a sigh of relief, when he heard Tang Rou doubt him: “You didn’t intentionally lose did you?”

“No no. Definitely not.” Wei Chen hastily answered.

“Ha ha ha ha.” Ye Xiu finally said something and then added: “Okay okay. Old Wei is tired now. Give him a break, Little Tang.”

Tang Rou wasn’t so stubborn that she wouldn’t drop the matter until he died. Even though she was reluctant, she let it go.

“F*ck!” Wei Chen messaged Ye Xiu.

“What do you think about her?” Ye Xiu asked.

“She’s incredible. The more she fights, the fiercer she becomes. My old hands are about to cramp up.” Wei Chen said.

“Did you give her the win on that last one?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No sh*t. You don’t actually believe I’d actually keep going until my hands cramped did you? If I did, I’d be sick.” Wei Chen said.

“She’s also someone who’s only played for four months!” Ye Xiu said.

“To think you’d be able to pick up two players like this in the tenth server. With the blessings that the God of Glory has bestowed upon you, you’d better return to the Alliance and win that championship.” Wei Chen puffed.

“God of Glory? You mean me?” Ye Xiu replied.

“F*ck off! Enough with your sh*t! ” Wei Chen cursed.

Chapter 615 – Qingming Festival

He even discussed the issue of hiding these talents with Ye Xiu. At the same time, he also asked if there were any hidden talents undiscovered. After all, only having four people in the team was not enough.

This issue made Wei Chen a little disappointed, the other two confirmed members on the team, Little Cold Hands and Concealed Light, were unable to reach Steamed Bun or Tang Rou’s level of expectation. However, this was not enough to cause a tactful guy like Wei Chen to feel worried over. He and Ye Xiu alike, had experienced the initial stage of the Professional League. If he had to compare the two, he would find the current situation not bad. It was Excellent Era’s records that had caused Wei Chen to feel a little vexed. Even though it would feel good to personally bury his previous glory and restart his journey again, a tactful guy like Wei Chen no longer had the hot-bloodedness like a youth. On the contrary, he wished to avoid Excellent Era and take down the Challenger League safely.

Everyone had something busy to do the next day. Chen Guo supervised the decorating. Ye Xiu, Tang Rou and Steamed Bun levelled up on their own, while Wei Chen switched back to his spy account in Samsara to continue to be a hired thug. Due to the fact that they had different levels in the game, the four people weren't able to interact together as a group for the time being

A day passed. The next day, Chen Guo woke up very early. She handed all her decoration work to Tang Rou today because she had something else to do.

April 4th was this year’s Qingming Festival. Chen Guo would visit her deceased father’s grave every year.

After she had left her room quietly and went down the stairs, Chen Guo was startled. She didn't think that Ye Xiu would be up earlier than her. He was also neatly dressed as he sat casually at the reception desk.

Chen Guo looked suspiciously towards the reception desk. Ye Xiu wasn’t just neatly dressed. He was dressed very formally.

“Morning.” Ye Xiu and Chen Guo greeted each other.

“You’re going out?” Chen Guo looked at Ye Xiu’s attire and made a guess. It was already April and the weather was becoming warmer, so there was no need to wear different clothes indoors and outdoors, which made it hard for Chen Guo to judge.

“Yeah!” Ye Xiu nodded.

“That's new! Where are you going?” Chen Guo was curious. Ye Xiu had been to Happy Internet Cafe for four months. Apart from All Stars Weekend and Spring Festival, his range of activity had never left this street.

“I’m going to visit a grave.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“Huh? Where are you going to visit?” Chen Guo was startled. Because of Ye Xiu’s brother Ye Qiu’s previous visit, Chen Guo was sure that Ye Xiu wasn’t from City H. If he planned on visiting a grave, wouldn't he be returning home?

“Nanshan Public Cemetery.” Ye Xiu said.

“Nanshan Public Cemetery?” Chen Guo was once again surprised because this was exactly where she was planning to go.

“To go visit a friend.” Ye Xiu obviously saw Chen Guo’s confusion, so he took the initiative to explain it to her.

“Oh, I’m also going there.” Chen Guo said.

“Let's go together?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Sure, should we go now?” Chen Guo asked.

“Wait for Mucheng.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, Mumu is going as well!” Chen Guo replied. Usually, she would undoubtedly be more than happy to be able to interact Su Mucheng. However, today was a special day. It was inappropriate to be happy because of this.

They didn't wait long. Su Mucheng arrived exactly on time to Happy Internet Cafe at 7:30. Evidently, Su MuCheng and Ye Xiu had arranged a time to meet beforehand. As an eSports star, especially in the area of City H, it was very inconvenient for Su Mucheng to go out. Now that winter had passed, Su MuCheng was unable to dress in her tight armour, so she was wearing a large sunglasses with a baseball cap and stood briskly at the Internet cafe’s entrance.

“Let's go!” Ye Xiu stood up, while Chen Guo went to greet Su Mucheng. Chen Guo helped Su Mucheng look around to see if they had attracted any attention. Ye Xiu saw this and only gave a laugh before the three set off. They called for a taxi and set off towards Nanshan Public Cemetery.

Chen Guo was curious about who Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng was going to visit, but it wasn't an easy question to openly ask about. As for her, even though she had never mentioned it to Ye Xiu before, she reckoned that everyone in the Internet Cafe knew about her home life. Ye Xiu probably knew already, so she didn't explain it herself.

The atmosphere was somewhat tense. Chen Guo quickly glanced at the rear mirror from her passenger seat. Ye Xiu’s expression was as natural as always. As for Su MuCheng, her expression was hard to recognise because of her armour, but it felt like she wasn’t too sad. Chen Guo hesitated whether she should pick a topic to talk about, but it was Ye Xiu who spoke first. However, he didn't speak to Chen Guo or Su Mucheng but the rental car driver: “Sir, do you play Glory?”

“What?” The driver was asked a question all of a sudden, so he was a bit surprised.

“Glory, an online game.”Ye Xiu said.

“Online game? Aren’t those for children!! How would I know?” The driver scoffed.

The three on the car were suddenly regarded as children. Chen Guo felt a little embarrassed, while Ye Xiu appeared very natural. He turned towards Su Mucheng and spoke: “You can take it off and rest……”

Su Mucheng quickly took off her giant sunglasses and took a long breath. “So heavy.”

Chen Guo realised why Ye Xiu had asked the driver this question. Afterwards, Ye Xiu asked. “It’s still the previous set, right?”

“Yeah!”

“Tsk tsk tsk……” Ye Xiu continuously sighed as if feeling relieved that she didn't have to suffer because of him.

Based on this topic, Chen Guo quickly joined in and helped by giving advice. Once the topic was opened up, the atmosphere was no longer heavy. Chen Guo and Su Mucheng discussed enthusiastically about makeup and other cosmetics. This took away the chance for Ye Xiu to join in the conversation. They traveled in this way until they arrived at City H’s Nanshan Public Cemetery.

Although the three had arrived early, it was the Qingming Festival so there were a lot of people that had come to visit their ancestor’s graves.

“Are you guys going to buy anything?” Chen Guo asked the two.

“Should we buy flowers?” Ye Xiu asked Su Mucheng.

“Sure!”

“Then you should pick them out.” Ye Xiu said.

“Of course.” Su Mucheng said as she and Chen Guo entered a flower shop nearby. Not long aftewards, the two came out, each holding a bunch of flowers. The flowers that Chen Guo bought were normal flowers. As for Su Mucheng, Ye Xiu couldn't recognise any of the flowers within her bundle.

“What kind of flowers are those?” Ye Xiu asked after he came over.

“Birds of Paradise.”

“Oh.” Ye Xiu replied, but didn’t make any further remarks.

The three people entered the cemetery and kept silent. They all quietly followed the stone path until Chen Guo stopped: “I’m going this way, how about you guys?”

“Oh, we’ll be going a little further that way.” Ye Xiu pointed to another side along the path.

“Oh, I see. Then I’ll go find you guys afterwards?” Chen Guo said.

“Sure, see you later.” Ye Xiu said.

“See you later.” Chen Guo nodded and the two said their goodbyes. Chen Guo took her bunch of flowers and went to her father’s grave.

“Dad, I’ve come to see you.” With a small smile, Chen Guo gently placed the bunch of flowers down.

“I’m doing well and so is the Internet Cafe, but it's a little different than before! A strange guy came and said that he would willingly take the night shift for the Internet Cafe. I’ve then discovered that he's an amazing and famous person. He's an eSports player and a top-tier one too. Haha, if you were some other dad, you would definitely think so what, but you’re different. You opened up an Internet Cafe, so you know all about online games! To have such a great figure like him to come to our Internet Cafe and become an employee, it's weird isn't it?”

“I learned about him having some conflicts with his original team, so he was forced to retire and leave. However, he has no intentions on giving up at all. He’s preparing to create another team to return to the professional league and aim for the championships again. As for me, I’ve decided to fiercely support him. This is another major decision I’ve made after taking over the Internet Cafe. I haven't had any dreams or ideals, uhh, though I wish for you could come back to life, but that's only a fantasy! It only counts as a dream if you make it into a reality with your own ability, right? I now want to work hard and create a team, what do you think? Amazing, isn't it? It's going to be very difficult, but I think it can be done! You don't have to worry about the Internet Cafe either! Because even though that guy and the others he brought along can be quite a mess sometimes, I have a feeling that they’re all very reliable people! It feels good to be with them and I think our shared goal will become a reality. At that time, I will definitely come and tell you about it. Wait for our good news!”

Standing before the grave, Chen Guo told her deceased father about everything. Although he was no longer present, the tied emotions between them would never disappear. Even time wouldn't be able to collapse this bond. Chen Guo hoped that her father knew that everything was going well for her and wished that she could share the enthusiasm and happiness with him.

“Alright, I’ll be going now. I might even bring good news the next time I see you!” Chen Guo smiled as she turned and made her leave. She returned to the stone path and walked towards the direction Ye Xiu had previously pointed to.

Chen Guo had visited Nanshan Public Cemetery for quite some time, so she was pretty familiar with the place, which explained why she knew which area Ye Xiu had previously pointed to. That area had not yet been opened when her father entered the cemetery. She couldn't remember which year that area had opened up.

While thinking, Chen Guo reached one side and walked past the rows. She soon found Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng, standing shoulder to shoulder.

Chen Guo didn't go over because she knew that many people had a lot of say when visiting the graves of their dear ones, so it would be inconvenient if there was an outsider there.

Chen Guo didn't walk forward, but from a distance, she could still see the name carved upon the gravestone.

Su Muqiu?

Chen Guo was startled. Judging from the name, the person seemed like a family member of Su Mucheng.

Chapter 616 – Su Muqiu

When Chen Guo saw the name on the grave, her mind was instantly filled with countless ideas and thoughts. She wanted to further confirm through the content given on the grave, but from her current position and distance from them, she couldn't see any other words. Chen Guo didn’t want to distract them, so she didn't progress any closer. She only stretched and bent herself around to see if she could pick up any useful information that the two figures had blocked.

In the midst of her efforts, Ye Xiu suddenly turned his head and saw Chen Guo.

Chen Guo knew that Ye Xiu must have caught her peeking. She wanted to find a hole for herself, lie in there, straighten up a gravestone, and just die. She subconsciously pretended not to notice Ye Xiu looking her way and continued to look around. After a while, she quickly scanned around again and saw Ye Xiu, who was smiling, and still looking at her. When he saw her looking his way, he waved towards her, as if hinting for her to come over.

Chen Guo was surprised and made a hand gesture confirming that she was allowed to walk forward. She only started to walk over after Ye Xiu gave her a nod.

Chen Guo was quite familiar with Nanshan Cemetery and knew about the different types of graves that were used here. The row Ye Xiu was in belonged to one of the lower grade gravestones in Nanshan Cemetery. The setup was simple and the space for visiting the grave was very small. If there were more family members or friends visiting, it wasn’t possible for everyone to stand in front of the grave together. Chen Guo came to the front and found the small and simple grave tidied up very neatly. It must have been cleaned by the two just then. The Birds of Paradise were placed silently before the grave. Chen Guo could finally clearly read the words on the grave.

The name and the time the grave was set up instantly gave Chen Guo some information. At this moment, Ye Xiu stood aside and patted the gravestone lightly while saying: “Look at this, if he weren’t lying here, he would have definitely become one of the Gods in Glory.

“He’s your brother!” Chen Guo looked at Su Mucheng. The name on the gravestone pointed it out.

“Yeah.” Su Mucheng nodded. She took off her hat and sunglasses before the grave. Her emotions didn't seem to be too sorrowful. She seemed like she was reminiscing her past. Judging by the dates on the grave, he passed away at the mere age of 18, which had been almost eight years ago.

“He…..?”

“Car accident.” Su Mucheng spoke.

“Oh……” Chen Guo fell silent. She had also experienced the unexpected pain of loss before.

“He was the only family member I had.” Su Mucheng said.

“Huh?” Chen Guo was stunned while immediately remembering that, despite the fact that Su Mucheng was a celebrity figure, her information portfolio had never introduced anything about her family. Chen Guo had always thought that she just didn't want to reveal information about her family. During this year’s Spring Festival, Chen Guo knew the reason why Ye Xiu didn't return home. However, when Su Mucheng also stayed at the club, Chen Guo was slightly puzzled in the beginning, but didn't think much of it afterwards. She assumed that Su Mucheng stayed behind to be with Ye Xiu. She only knew about it now that even if Su Mucheng wanted to gather with relatives for a festival, there was no one she could find. As for Chen Guo? Although she was living by herself, she still had a few relatives, they just didn't interact much.

“We both grew up in the orphanage, then something happened, so we were left to wander outside, it was my brother who always cared for me for the whole time.” Su Mucheng said.

Chen Guo continued to be stunned. She had never thought that such a dazzling Glory celebrity had such a miserable past. Her brother Su Muqiu was not even 18 when he passed away and before that, he already had to bear the responsibility of raising two people. Chen Guo was unable to imagine how hard it must have been..

“Haha.” It was unexpected that Su Mucheng would laugh at a time like this, “Don't assume that our lives were hard at that time, because it wasn't! Our lives were pretty good due to my brother’s gaming talent.”

“Gaming talent?”

“Yeah!” Su Mucheng smiled, “Power leveling, selling equipment, organizing gambling dens, or even assassinating. In terms of gaming, there's really nothing he couldn't do.”

“Oh, that's nice.” Although Chen Guo spoke in this manner, she was pained on the inside. She knew that although Su Mucheng had said it like this, the reality might not have been as blissful as she had described. Chen Guo had grown up in the Internet Cafe. Later, she managed the Internet Cafe, a relatively big one too. Although she didn't involve herself with online games at first, she had watched over such a place every day, so Chen Guo knew quite clearly about what it was like to seek a living in gaming, similar to what Su Mucheng had described.

Although doing these things could help them survive, it would be difficult to let a person live a luxurious life. Chen Guo didn’t know to what degree Su Muqiu could do it, but at that time, he was just a teenager and he had needed to support two people’s lives, so it must have been very difficult. Also, another reality was before her eyes. Su Muqiu’s grave was one of those with a low standard in Nanshan Public Cemetery, so it could be seen that when he had passed away, their financial assets had been very limited.

Chen Guo didn't think that Su Mucheng had spoken in such way just to comfort her. Maybe she really was satisfied during that time. Her living demands weren’t too high as someone who had grown up living on the streets and depended on her brother. This was why she felt very happy even though her life might not have been very good in another person’s eyes.

Chen Guo received confirmation because she caught Ye Xiu’s emotions in that instant. When Su Mucheng was happily remembering her past, Ye Xiu, who was always calm, had a bit of bitterness displayed on his face. Chen Guo knew that he wasn't some kind of pitiable teenager who didn't have a home to go to. In terms of his quality of life, he definitely wasn’t on the same level as a homeless girl. Evidently, Ye Xiu was clear about what the Su sibling’s lives were like, so when Su Mucheng brought up the “happiness” from her past, his emotions were similar to Chen Guo’s.

“When the game Glory came out, my brother was so happy! He had high hopes for this game and put all his heart into it.” Su Mucheng said.

“I met those two around that time.” Ye Xiu said.

“After you have left home, right?” Chen Guo asked.

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu nodded, “After meeting them, I got along with Muqu. Both of us aspired to make something out of Glory, so we spent all our time on Glory every day. We researched classes, skills, equipment, and creating our own equipment in Glory. The Pro League still has Silver equipment created by him.”

“Really?” Chen Guo was astonished.

“Really! One Autumn Leaf’s spear Evil Annihilation is one of his works!” Ye Xiu said.

“As well as the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella?” Chen Guo suddenly remembered, when she had first learned about this piece of Silver equipment, Ye Xiu had mentioned a friend. Chen Guo felt it was a sensitive topic, so she hadn’t investigated the matter any further. Now it could be seen that the friend Ye Xiu had previously mentioned was Su Muqiu.

“Yeah, very gifted, right? It was a pity that the update for Level 55 destroyed any meaning in unspecialized characters and this weapon.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“But my brother didn't give up!” Su Mucheng spoke.

“That's right. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s conception was a vision produced by him when unspecialized characters had been extremely popular. From then on, he researched unceasingly. He experimented and experimented. No one knew how many failures he experienced, but he never gave up. Who knew that, just when he was about to succeed, when he had prepared a character to level up with the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, that update happened. When the news came out, even I couldn't accept such a sorrowful thing. His silence during that time scared all of us. Do you know what happened afterwards?” Ye Xiu asked.

“What happened?” Chen Guo was startled. The first thing that came to her mind was that Su Muqiu had been too depressed because of this and deliberately got into a car accident. However, after giving it more thoughts and this really happened, how could Ye Xiu ask something like “Do you know what happened afterwards?”

“On the second day, when we were all still worrying about him, he smiled and handed a card to me, saying: “It’s a new start.” Ye Xiu said.

“He’s really strong.” Chen Guo instantly gained respect for Su Muqiu from the bottom of her heart.

“He gave up on the idea of playing an unspecialized. He picked a class and leveled it up again. During that time, the news of a Professional League forming was gradually released. We were famous in Glory at that time, so we were contacted and invited everywhere. Of course, we weren't able to bring out our unspecialized characters, but we could finally take a step ahead in Glory. Everyone was happy, only that……” Ye Xiu fell dim when he spoke here and lowered his head towards the gravestone. In the picture that was mounted on the gravestone, was a delicate teenager, who looked kind of like Su Mucheng, giving off a confident and easy smile.

At that moment, Chen Guo felt as if she could really hear a free and easy voice saying: It's a new start.

Yeah! Only a person with absolute confidence would be able to casually say such a thing after experiencing an attack that destroyed all of his hard work. And he had only been a youth in his teens.

“At that time, we had already confirmed our team and were prepared to formally sign the contract, but he was caught up in an accident.” Ye Xiu sighed.

The three fell silent, Su Mucheng slightly turned her head, but quickly turned it back to its original position. Although the tears in her eyes were shining, there was still a strong smile hanging on her face: “But he left behind many things!”

“That's right, without the Silver weapon, Evil Annihilation for One Autumn Leaf, I wouldn't have been able to win three championships in a row so easily. Haha, at that time, that Silver weapon was ahead of its time. You can even ask Old Wei when you return. It scared him to death!” Ye Xiu said.

“There's also Lord Grim and the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. What he wasn't able to achieve before can be achieved now!” Chen Guo spoke.

“As well as the account he prepared to use for the Pro League.” Su Mucheng added.

“Oh? Where?” Chen Guo truly wanted to worship the character that this firm and confident youth had left behind. This youth would have become a God, but ended up with such a tragic ending instead.

“It's the Dancing Rain account that I’m currently using!” Su Mucheng said.

Chapter 617 – Let’s Work Hard Together Everyone

“Ah?” Chen Guo was very surprised at this response. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had been the account that Su Muqiu had originally intended to use in the Pro Alliance?

Guys playing female characters or girls playing male characters weren’t commonly seen in the game, but it wasn’t anything strange in the pro scene. Every character in the pro scene had been built up step by step. The character’s gender was something that had been set at creation and couldn’t be changed regardless. In some cases, a younger generation successor would be a male player playing a female character, or a female player playing a male character.

Team Misty Rain’s Chu Yunxiu and Team Void’s Wu Yuce were two notable examples. Both of them were All Star level players. Chu Yunxiu’s Elementalist, Windy Rain, and Wu Yuxe’s Ghostblade, Carved Ghost, were the opposite gender of their respective players.

Windy Rain was a male character. Carved Ghost didn’t sound like a female name, but she was a female character anyways.

These two were famous, so they were talked about more often than others. There were also others, but there weren’t very many. After all, there were more male players than female players. Male players were, on average, more skilled than the female players. In the pro scene, whether it was players or characters, males held the majority.

Nearly all of the above players had inherited their current accounts. In the beginning, this issue would often be talked about by others, but later, everyone got used to it, so not many were surprised by it anymore. However, if someone took the initiative to play as the opposite gender, it would attract a lot of attention. In the past few years, there were no lack of players who wanted to attract attention in this way. Unfortunately, this was a competitive place and not a place for recreation. Just relying on this method wouldn’t allow them to keep their position. Everything depended on their skill alone. If your skills were just for show, then you would be picked out swiftly. Let alone players who played a different gender, even if you were an actual transgendered person, you would just be seen as a joke if you couldn’t back up the attention with skill.

But this Su Muqiu had actually planned on joining the pro scene by using a female account? It was quite surprising to Chen Guo. Someone with such confidence didn’t need to gather attention in this way!

After she said “ah”, Su Mucheng explained to her with a smile: “He didn’t care whether or not he played a male or female character. The reason he created that account was to tease me.”

“Oh……” Chen Guo understood. It was just a little joke between brother and sister. It had nothing to do with the politics of the pro scene.

He had even used his sister’s name for the female character. Chen Guo could tell that Su Muqiu loved his sister dearly. Such a caring person ended up in such a way…...

Chen Guo felt sad, but she didn’t want to disturb Ye Xiu’s and Su Mucheng’s feelings, so she tried hard not to cry. Now she understood why, that day, when Excellent Era’s boss Tao Xuan came over and promised he could even let One Autumn Leaf go if Ye Xiu desired, but Ye Xiu decisively asked for Dancing Rain instead. In his eyes, Dancing Rain meant much more to him than even One Autumn Leaf. Whether it was for Su Muqiu or Su Mucheng, he would try his hardest to get Dancing Rain back. As for One Autumn Leaf, it was mostly Ye Xiu’s memories. He could give the, up or maybe it was because he was confident like Su Muqiu that he could start all over from scratch.

Afterwards, the three fell into silence. No one said anything. After standing there reminiscing for a short while, Ye Xiu spoke: “Let’s go back?”

“Okay.” Chen Guo didn’t object. Su Mucheng also nodded. The three left. Before leaving, Chen Guo couldn’t help but look back one last time. With Su Muqiu’s skill, personality, and even appearance, if he had been able to join the pro scene, what would he have been able to accomplish?

“Had he been planning on joining Excellent Era together with you?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“Yeah!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“If you had been able to fight alongside each other in Excellent Era…..” Chen Guo couldn’t help but imagine the possibilities. Just Ye Xiu alone had been able to bring Excellent Era to dominate the pro scene for three years. If he had someone else, who was no worse than himself, someone like Su Muqiu…..

“Then maybe the Pro Alliance would close down because the same team would win the championships every year without any competition?” Ye Xiu said.

“Alright……” Today was a special day, so Chen Guo didn’t make any remarks towards Ye Xiu’s comment.

The three walked along the road down the mountain and returned by taxi. All the way, they talked about the game and their moods gradually returned to normal, but Chen Guo had just listened to the story for the first time. Her mood couldn’t go back to normal so quickly. At this moment, her ambitions became even grander. She suddenly felt that bearing so much weight on her shoulders was something to be happy about. She was glad that she had the opportunity to meet all these people and share their burden. Struggle and move forward! Whether they succeeded or failed, they could be proud of their life. Their life wouldn’t be filled with boredom or loneliness.

“How are things going? How are things going? Is everything done yet?”

When they returned to the Internet Cafe, Su Mucheng went back to Club Excellent Era, while Chen Guo checked with the second floor renovators on their current progress. Her energy startled Wei Chen and Steamed Bun, who were playing the game in the room.

The two came out to see what was going on. Wei Chen still had a cigarette in his mouth, which Chen Guo quickly noticed.

“No smoking!” Chen Guo pointed out.

“Are you joking? You can’t smoke in this Internet Cafe?” Wei Chen was astonished. Chen Guo recalled that exact same scene four months ago. Ye Xiu had arrived at the Internet Cafe with a cigarette in his mouth. After being scolded by her, he also had that same incomprehensible look.

“If you’re going to smoke, go smoke in that room.” Chen Guo pointed. Prohibiting smoking in an Internet Cafe would make things difficult for customers and would negatively impact the business, so even though Chen Guo didn’t like smoking, she had to open up a smoking area for these customers. There were certain areas downstairs and upstairs for customers to freely smoke in.

“How did you survive?” Wei Chen looked at Ye Xiu. He clearly knew that Ye Xiu also smoked.

“I’ve got morals. I only smoke in smoking areas.” Ye Xiu said.

“Don’t tell me the Clubs allowed you to smoke in the practice rooms?” Chen Guo asked incredulously.

“Usually not.” Wei Chen said, “But I was the captain.” After speaking, he sucked in a deep breath and handed a cigarette over to Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu took it and skillfully lit it. After taking in a deep breath, he puffed out: “Mm, I was also the captain.”

“Scum! Both of you are scum!!” Chen Guo was furious. At this moment, she couldn’t help but think of Su Muqiu. If he had been the captain, he definitely wouldn’t have acted so inappropriately.

“Even if you don’t care about yourself, you have to at least care about the other team members. A lot of our team members are minors! Don’t you feel bad exposing them to secondhand smoke?” Chen Guo lectured.

“This senior had already started smoking when he was a minor.” Wei Chen inhaled.

“What a coincidence! Me too.” Ye Xiu nodded his head and also inhaled.

“YOU TWO!!!!” Chen Guo yelled.

‘Speaking of which, who’s going to be our team captain?” Wei Chen asked Ye Xiu.

“Are you going senile? If not me, then who else?” Ye Xiu said.

“I guess we have to make do with what we got!” Wei Chen nodded his head.

These two guys chatted and went into the room.

“Steamed Bun, do you smoke?” Wei Chen even asked Steamed Bun.

“I don’t know how.” Steamed Bun said.

“There are youths who actually don’t know how to smoke?” Wei Chen expressed his disdain.

“Then let me try?” Steamed Bun asked. Chen Guo was going crazy. Wasn’t he being brought over to the dark side too easily? Just when she was about to stop their vile behavior, Ye Xiu said: “If he doesn’t know, there’s no point letting him try. It’d be a waste.”

“Agreed.” Wei Chen nodded his head.

After speaking, the two went into the room. Chen Guo was depressed. Just Ye Xiu alone had made her go mad, but now Wei Chen was here too. With these two shameless villains colluding with one another, they directly ignored her no smoking policy.

Chen Guo once again thought of Su Muqiu and felt grieved. Why did such a good person have to die? Was it really as the saying went, good people don’t live for long, while disasters can last centuries?

She couldn’t do anything about these two. Chen Guo went back and checked on the renovation progress. She was quite satisfied with the progress, but when she thought about those two scourges, she had to propose another requirement: the practice room would need very strong ventilation.

“You’re back?” At this moment, Tang Rou came out from her room and called out to Chen Guo.

“Hmph. Those two make me angry.” Chen Guo grumbled.

“What’s wrong?” Tang Rou asked.

Chen Guo explained. Tang Rou consoled her with a smile: “There’s nothing we can do. From the looks of it, that Old Wei’s smoking addiction is even worse than Ye Xiu’s. If you didn’t let him smoke while he played, he might not be able to handle it.”

“Mm, I know. A lot of old players are like that.” Chen Guo said.

“Just let them do what they’re used to doing!’ Tang Rou said.

“What else can I do? I can only lecture them a bit.” Chen Guo sighed.

“Ye Xiu wasn’t here in the morning. Did he go out with you?” Tang Rou asked.

“Yeah! He and Su Mucheng went to sweep a gravestone.” Chen Guo pulled Tang Rou to one side and told her about Su Mucheng’s brother, Su Muqiu. She wasn’t afraid that she would disturb Ye Xiu’s or Su Mucheng’s mood. Chen Guo completely poured out her thoughts. Tang Rou listened and could only feel sorry as well.

“This has made me even more determined to work hard for this team!” Chen Guo said.

“Let’s work hard together.” Tang Rou said.

Chapter 618 – Practice Room

The second floor renovation wasn’t a very large project, but it wasn’t a small project either. However, with Chen Guo personally supervised the project in high spirits, the work progressed swiftly. About two weeks later, the project was complete. They then moved in some equipment that had been prepared beforehand. Chen Guo inspected everything again and felt very satisfied with the work. Only then did she call everyone over and officially move them into the team’s new practice room.

“Isn’t it too bright?” Ye Xiu led the way in and made a remark. Sunshine came in through the huge window and into his eyes, forcing him to squint.

“It really is a bit bright.” Wei Chen followed after him.

Chen Guo ignored the comments given by these two shameless guys. She just continued to invite them to use the computers and experience the room some more. The computers used weren’t any different from the ones used in the Internet Cafe. Glory ran smoothly on these computers without any problems. As for their mice and keyboards, she had asked them which ones they preferred. Ye Xiu had recommended a suitable set for Steamed Bun.

There were twelve computer stations total, every three computers were in a group. The groups were arranged in a square formation, giving off a very competitive atmosphere. Because they used different sets of keyboards and mice, their seats were already fixed. Ye Xiu and Wei Chen were placed right underneath the strong ventilation fan. Chen Guo already regarded them as smoke machines.

The four people sat down in their respective seats, turned on their computers, and entered the game. Not long afterwards, Ye Xiu wrinkled his brows as he complained again: “It’s too bright.”

“Yeah.” Wei Chen agreed.

Chen Guo was just about to ignore their complaints again, but Steamed Bun also squinted his eyes and leaned extremely far forward, his eyes were about to touch the screen: “It’s too bright. I can’t see the screen clearly.”

Even Tang Rou said helplessly: “It really is.”

Chen Guo had never tried it before. She stood behind Tang Rou to check and suddenly felt stupid. She had intentionally positioned the room so that it faced the sun. The sunlight would brighten up the atmosphere, but it also brought an intense glare to the computer monitors. It really was hard to see stuff on the screen.

“We should hang a curtain.” Ye Xiu looked at the window.

Chen Guo accepted the suggestion and hung a curtain up over the window. They immediately spread it out.

“Good!” Steamed Bun was excited when he returned to his computer.

“Mm, this is good.” Wei Chen complimented.

Ye Xiu and Tang Rou didn’t say anything, but also looked very satisfied. Chen Guo was speechless. The curtain blocked the sunlight, making the room very dark. The brightly lit and magnificent practice room that she had imagined had turned into a dark and gloomy room. In this dusky room, the constantly changing light from the screens shone on the faces of the people in front of the computers. Even a beautiful girl like Tang Rou now looked like she was a ghost.

Chen Guo couldn’t bear it anymore. She walked to the entrance and turned on the light.

“AH!!” Everyone in the room cried out as if a bunch of leeches had been burned by the sun.

“Turn it off. Hurry up and turn it off.” Wei Chen’s voice was especially impatient and desperate. As he shouted, he kept on adjusting his seat and waving his keyboard and mouse. The light seemed as if it had an extremely dangerous effect on him.

The other three didn’t react as crazily. All of them kept looking up at the lights.

Chen Guo had personally chosen the lights as well. The lights were very beautiful crystal lamps, but right now, the others were glaring at them very unwelcomingly. Chen Guo was gloomy.

“Don’t turn them all on. It makes it too hard to see the screen.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo flipped two of the light switches off.

“A couple more.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo turned off more lights.

“Another one.” Ye Xiu said again.

Chen Guo turned off a couple more lights.

“Another one.” Ye Xiu still said.

Chen Guo turned off another light and then heard Ye Xiu say in satisfaction: “Mm, this is perfect. Let’s keep it like this!”

All of the lights had been turned off. Chen Guo was so depressed that she wanted to hit a wall. It turns out that she had done too many unnecessary things. The practice room had a few other features too, but right now, Chen Guo felt too afraid to display them to everyone. After the four felt satisfied with their environment, they had already begun focusing on the game.

Chen Guo was feeling down, when she suddenly heard Ye Xiu say: “Is this all? I remember you installed a projector too?”

“Ah, yeah!” Chen Guo heard his question and her spirits came back. She hastily ran to the corner on the east side and pressed on a button. The projector screen slowly descended. The screen was a bit smaller than the screen downstairs used to project the matches on Saturday, but it was more than enough for this practice room.

“Hey, this is real nice! We can use this projector to watch matches. We won’t need to go downstairs and squeeze our way through the crowd. Hearing all those noobs talking rubbish really makes me mad.” Wei Chen felt moved.

Everyone laughed.

In the beginning, Wei Chen had liked the way Happy Internet Cafe broadcast the Saturday matches. During his first week here, he had a good time with everyone else.

But good things didn’t last forever. In the second week, after Wei Chen got a good seat to watch the match, he got into a big argument with the person next to him. That person was commenting on the match to his friend and acted like he knew everything. Wei Chen listened to him and saw that it was all complete nonsense! As a result, he passionately participated in the discussion and pointed out all of his mistakes. That guy didn’t have the patience to listen to any of Wei Chen’s words. He looked at Wei Chen in contempt: “You understand?”

Wei Chen wasn’t a typical gaming nerd. He had come from the streets. After being in the streets for so long, he had gone from being a small delinquent to a big boss. His temperament was the same as it had been back then. He was too lazy to reason with this guy. When right, others might play as the scholar who can never win an argument with a military man, but Wei Chen was the military man and would straight up use force to win.

But in this occasion, Wei Chen didn’t make a move. According to him, because he had just gotten to the Internet Cafe, he had to give the boss face. In addition, since they were going to form their team, he had to control himself. Later, Ye Xiu heard the story and looked down on him: “Don’t listen to his nonsense. He’s just saying that because the other side had the numbers advantage.”

In short, from then on, Wei Chen no longer watched the matches with the crowd, but he really did like the feeling of using that big projection screen to watch matches. Chen Guo had installed one for them up here, making Wei Chen very happy.

‘Let’s watch the matches here this week.” Wei Chen declared.

“Uh….. I still like downstairs.” Steamed Bun said.

“Why is that?” Wei Chen asked.

‘More people, bigger screen.” Steamed Bun excitedly said. His simple reasoning was hard to to dispute.

Facing his own teammate, no matter how angry Wei Chen was, he couldn’t just go up and punch him! So he sincerely educated Steamed Bun: “Steamed Bun! Look, we’re extremely skilled players aspiring to be pros. It isn’t right to crowd together with those noobs. They won’t understand the words that you say, but the words that they say will only make you angry. What’s the point?”

“That won’t happen! I feel like it’s good!” Steamed Bun said.

Everyone laughed again.

Wei Chen was helpless. He had been with him for two weeks already. How could he not know about Steamed Bun’s ability to derail any topic at this point, so he didn’t try to put in pointless effort. He buried his head in the game once more.

These past two weeks everyone else had been leveling on their own accounts. Wei Chen continued to spy on Samsara. With his skill, Wei Chen still wasn’t a core member of Samsara yet, but he was at least an elite player of the guild and had joined the elites of Samsara’s main guild. During these two weeks, he had participated in several wild boss fights and made heroic contributions to the guild. Even if he was a spy, the guild was happy to use him. After all, the benefits brought about by such an expert could clearly be seen.

Wei Chen earned their trust, while slowly moving his gang of brothers into the guild.

Wei Chen had been guiding his friends for a long time, so their skills weren’t bad. They at least had the qualifications to hold a seat in any of the big guilds. They had originally been members of Blue Brook Guild, so they didn’t have any issues in joining.

Normal players might not care if he recommended a bunch of players to join the guild. The guild leader might even happily welcome all of them, but a Club guild had to be much more careful. After all, the competition between the Club guilds was too fierce. It was no longer as simple as playing for fun.

As a result, under Wei Chen’s arrangements, his friends pretended like they were Samsara fans and sent their applications to Samsara. There were countless Samsara fans and many of these fans wanted to join the Club guilds that they supported. No one would ever have any suspicions towards this reason. Afterwards, they just needed to patiently wait for the guild to recruit them.

Wei Chen didn’t have any proper business to do when he went online. After walking around in a circle, he received a personal message from the guild leader Three Realms Six Paths.

The guild leader of a grand Club guild was someone very high-up in the game. To personally receive a message from the guild leader showed how high of a status Wei Chen held.

Wei Chen opened up the message and after conversing with Three Realms Six Paths for a bit, he cursed: “F*ck!”

“What’s wrong?” Ye Xiu glanced over.

“That f*cker already wants this senior to lead a team. I still haven’t gotten everyone together yet!” Wei Chen cursed.

This had originally been his and Ye Xiu’s original plan. Wei Chen displayed his talents as a leader. In order to properly utilize his talents, the guild would give him a team to lead. Wei Chen was currently in an elite team of Samsara, but such a top team would certainly be commanded by the guild leader, Three Realms Six Paths. No matter how amazing his leading was, it wasn’t his place to go beyond his status. Leading was a very prestigious matter. If your guild’s elite team and even the guild leader were listening to a single person’s orders, what did that mean? It clearly wouldn’t be appropriate, so the two of them were certain that Samsara would give Wei Chen a team to shine. However, they didn’t anticipate that Samsara would move so quickly. Only a few of Wei Chen’s friends had joined the guild!

Chapter 619 – Do You Have a Clear Conscience?

“That’s not that important is it?” Ye Xiu said as he skimmed through the chat window on Wei Chen’s screen. Three Realms Six Paths seemed to place a lot of importance on Wei Chen and told him that he was planning on giving him control over the fifth elite group of Samsara’s main guild to lead.

“It’s not that important, but I just feel that with the ability I’ve displayed, it’s still too soon for me to become an elite group’s leader.” Wei Chen said.

“Really? The fifth elite group…… one group has a hundred players. When a guild fights for a wild boss, the guild will usually brings two groups, at most three or four. Your fifth elite group is just a reserve group for the reserve group! Your current status isn’t any higher than a cheerleader in the first elite group! At the very least, you won’t be able to receive any extremely important pieces of intelligence. Right now, just take your fifth elite group or whatever and run dungeons all day!” Ye Xiu said.

“Shut up. If that guild leader immediately handed me the first elite group, his head must have been kicked into mush by a donkey! The fifth elite group isn’t that bad anyways. Wait until I show off a bit more skill and we’ll push past those second, third, fourth elite groups.” Wei Chen said with confidence.

“Don’t stoop too low. If you get a rare item in the next dungeon, try to restrain yourself from pocketing it for yourself. That would be like killing the hen for the eggs.” Ye Xiu warned.

“F*ck off. Do you think this senior needs your advice?” Wei Chen shooed away Ye Xiu as if he were a fly.

Just when Ye Xiu turned back to his computer screen, he heard Wei Chen yell: “Woah! Eternal Life Spring! I just happen to need something from this dungeon. This group’s dungeon progress is perfect!”

Ye Xiu turned his head and looked. After Wei Chen had accepted Three Realm Six Path’s proposal, Three Realms Six Paths asked for him to lead his new team to tackle dungeons. Their main target was a Level 70 dungeon, Eternal Life Springs.

Even though Ye Xiu regarded the fifth elite group of Samsara’s main guild as the reserve group of the reserve group, in reality, they were definitely among the top teams in Glory.

Eternal Life Springs was one of the seven great hundred-player dungeons in the Heavenly Domain.

These seven great hundred-player raid dungeons were named as such because they were currently the hardest dungeons that existed in Glory. They belonged in the same category of difficulty, but because there were a lot of differences between each dungeon, different raid groups had easier times in some dungeons but had a harder time in others. As a result, it was hard to say which of these seven dungeons was the easiest. Every raid group had their own opinions.

These seven dungeons had been added to Glory at the same time and refreshed at the same time every week. In other words, even though there were seven dungeons, players could only choose one of the seven to run every week. Large guilds, like Samsara, would always try to split their forces up so they could run all seven dungeons during the week. How many of the seven dungeons a guild could clear was another way they could measure the guild’s strength. If a raid group could only attempt one dungeon every week, how many dungeons a guild could clear indicated how many top elite teams that guild possessed. The more of these top elite teams they had, the more experts the guild had, and the better the equipment these experts possessed.

Samsara’s fifth elite group was one of the groups responsible for running one of the seven great dungeons every week. Since these dungeons refreshed on the same day each week, the equipment and uncommon materials inside were extraordinarily precious. Although, in theory, the drops wouldn’t be at the same level as a wild boss’, but not only did a group only have a single opportunity to attempt one of the seven dungeons, but very few of them could actually clear them. As for random raid groups, they were far from being good enough to take down any of the seven dungeons.

Wei Chen used to be a part of the Blue Brook Guild before. With his skill, entering an elite group definitely wouldn’t be a difficult task. He had probably run this dungeon before. Even if he had run the dungeon in the past, most players wouldn’t be able to get any of the items that dropped. If it were any normal player guild or another group, it might be possible, but for Club guilds, materials needed to be provided for the pro team. Unless there was a special reason, these materials rarely fell into a player’s hands, so when Wei Chen saw that he would be leading the team into Eternal Life Springs, he immediately thought of killing the hen to get the eggs. He was the group leader! According to custom, equipment and materials dropped wouldn’t be rolled for to determine the owner. The drops would go directly to the group leader. If Wei Chen needed an item, he could take it directly and leave if he wanted to. However, if he did this, he would never be trusted by anymore again.

“Don’t stoop too low.” Ye Xiu reminded again.

“Tch, I just felt that it was a bit of pity. Do you think that I’m you?” Wei Chen looked back with contempt.

Ye Xiu didn’t reply, but after awhile, he suddenly heard Wei Chen slap his head in vexation: “Ah, why didn’t I think of that before!”

“Think of what?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Getting materials this way! I should have created a smurf, climbed to the top, lead a team, then took the items and ran.” Wei Chen said.

“This means that you’re still human.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“But you thought of it today.” Wei Chen glanced at him.

“Must be a difference in IQ?” Ye Xiu asked.

“More like a difference in morals.” Wei Chen said.

“Everything is for work.” Ye Xiu expressed.

“How about we get a few alternates and use this method? It’s a pity about your Unrivaled Super Hottie. You should have at least risen to the level of a group leader, run a dungeon, and take all the items before leaving!” Wei Chen said.

“You’re joking! Do you know how much effort that requires? Wouldn’t it be better to directly target the group leaders? Wait for them to exit the dungeons and directly kill them. Isn’t that much more direct and efficient?” Ye Xiu said.

“Hadn’t we planned on doing this before? When we have a bit more manpower, we’ll do it!” Wei Chen said.

“That’s why I said we’re not in a hurry for dungeon drops. It would make more sense to hurry up and figure out a way to steal wild bosses.” Ye Xiu said.

“Slow down, slow down. As long as you remain patient, there will be more bread waiting for you.” Wei Chen advised.

Chen Guo listened to their discussion and felt very remorseful! The content of their discussion becoming more and more despicable. They wouldn’t stop at anything to reach their goals whether it be murdering or plundering! If a pure and innocent child ended up joining their team, under the evil influence of these two people, what would he be like when he grew up? It would be okay if the child could distinguish between game and reality, but if he was completely corrupted, what would happen if he went to the streets and plundered?

Most players thought of running dungeons to get equipment drops or finding ways to trade for other items. Why did these two have to think of inhumane methods like “they clear the dungeon, while we clear the group leader”? How did these guys view the game? What did they eat when they grew up?

Chen Guo looked at the two incredulously. When she glanced at Steamed Bun and Tang Rou, they were wearing the headphones and leveling in dungeons. They probably didn’t hear of them talking, so they didn’t react in any way.

If a team was formed like this, their entire history would be filled with black! If their wrongdoings were exposed, how terrible would their reputation be? Chen Guo thought. She felt like their plans were too excessive. But when she thought about it again, killing people for equipment was very common in the Heavenly Domain! Who didn’t know that the Heavenly Domain was a dangerous place? These two were just a bit more bold than others. Most players would think of bullying strays, whose equipment were about to break anyways. But these two guys directly locked onto the group leaders of the top guild’s elite groups.

In any case, this was a game and it wasn’t against the law. Even so, Chen Guo didn’t like this sort of conduct. But if she tried to talk some sense into these two, she felt like her chances were very low. In that instant, Chen Guo once again thought of Su Muqiu! This youth died before he could complete his dreams. Chen Guo had only understood a little bit about his situation from Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng on the Qingming Festival, but in her heart, she regarded him as a perfect existence. He was a big reason for Chen Guo’s recent motivation.

When she thought of this perfect person, Chen Guo became determined. She walked over to those two unscrupulous guys and tapped the table: “Hey!”

“What?” The two didn’t even lift their heads.

“You guys weren’t actually serious about those things you guys just talked about, right?” Chen Guo said.

“What?” The two finally lifted their heads.

“Directly killing the group leader for his stuff.” Chen Guo said in an incomparably serious tone.

“Did we say that?” Ye Xiu looked at Wei Chen.

“I don’t think so!” Wei Chen looked at Chen Guo.

“I’m serious.” Chen Guo didn’t waver.

Ye Xiu could fell Chen Guo’s determination and laughed: “Of course not. We were just joking.”

“Really?” Chen Guo hesitated, but still told them her thoughts: “I understand your dreams and how precious time is and how difficult it is right now, but I feel that we shouldn’t achieve these goals through any means possible such as relying on immoral methods like stealing the results that others got through hard work. Do you guys not have a clear conscience?”

Wei Chen furrowed his brows, when he heard her words. Right when he was about to say something in response, Ye Xiu smiled: “We have a clear conscience!”

Ye Xiu had his usual indifferent expression, but it currently made Chen Guo feel disappointed. Fortunately, she soon heard Ye Xiu add: “Because we really were just joking.”

“Really? That’s good!” Chen Guo suddenly felt a heavy weight come off of her shoulder and smiled.

Wei Chen didn’t say anything until Chen Guo left. Then, he looked at Ye Xiu: “But we weren’t actually joking, right?”

“I was just joking. You were the one being too immoral.” Ye Xiu said.

“Stop with the bullsh*t. I doubt you’d care about something like that.” Wei Chen said.

“But there’s nothing we can do.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?” Wei Chen said.

“Because she’s the boss……” Ye Xiu smiled.

“F*ck…… females are always so sensitive.” Wei Chen rubbed his nose fiercely and returned to the game without saying anything more.

Chapter 620 – Excellent Era Relegated

April soon came to an end. In April, the Pro Alliance held a total of five matches. There were only two matches remaining now. The positions of many teams on the rankings list were already determined. The first place spot in the regular season looked as if it would be taken by Team Blue Rain. For all five matches in April, Team Blue Rain had performed consistently well and were currently five points ahead of the second place team, Samsara. Their opponents in the next two matches had no hope of making it to the playoffs and wouldn’t get relegated either way. These types of opponents wouldn’t try very hard for these upcoming matches. Under this type of situation, allowing Samsara to close the five point gap wasn’t Team Blue Rain’s style, so nearly everyone agreed that Team Blue Rain would take first during the regular season.

As for second, third, and fourth places, after the five matches in April, there were only slight differences in points, but their rankings stayed the same: Samsara, Tiny Herb, and Tyranny. After them, Team Misty Rain was locked into fifth place and Team Void was locked into sixth. Their spots in the playoffs were also firmly set.

In seventh place was Team 301. They could still lose their playoff spot, but the probability of that happening was extremely low. In other words, it would be a miracle if they managed to lose their spot. Miracles didn’t happen often, so everyone also treated their playoff spot as fixed.

Team Wind Howl and Team Thunderclap were fighting for the final ticket to the playoffs. Their former competitor, Team Royal Style, had no possibility of making it through anymore. As for Team Hundred Blossoms, they were in a similar situation as Team 301. The only difference was that instead of the possibility of losing their playoff spot, they could be relegated in theory.

As a result, for the next two matches, fans of Team Wind Howl and Team Thunderclap were the most worried, but no matter what, one of these two teams would not make it to the playoffs. This was the cruel nature of competition.

In comparison to the fight for the playoff spot, the relegation spots weren’t watched as much. There were a total of 38 matches in a season and 380 points possible. To be last or second to last among the twenty teams indicated that the two relegated teams were truly terrible teams. It didn’t mean that these two teams wouldn’t have any fans, but they usually didn’t have as many fans as other teams, so the attention given to them was naturally less than the other teams.

But this year was an exception. Team Excellent Era had once reigned over the professional scene, but this season, they looked as if they were determined to get relegated. Whether it was experts, fans, or the media, no one thought that Team Excellent Era would ever get relegated. However, Team Excellent Era seemed to like to create miracles and was about to turn this dream into a reality.

Unfortunately, this was a miracle for haters and a disaster for fans.

As for the twentieth place team, Mysterious Fantasy, it didn’t matter what they did in the last two matches. They would be relegated regardless, but for this team, which had been last place the entire season, no one cared about whether they survived or died. Excellent Era, on the other hand, had continued to drop to second to last place and raised much criticism from everyone.

However, because Excellent Era could still place outside of relegations, quite a few analyzed their past results. Even though many fans saw that Excellent Era seemed to be determined to get relegated, in reality, they were just barely outside the relegation zone most of the time. It was only their second time breaking through the door to relegations.

When did the first time happen?

The fans of Excellent Era quickly remembered. At that time, it was still winter. Their captain for seven years, Ye Qiu, had announced his retirement. The exceptional talent, Sun Xiang, who had already been regarded as a God, joined Excellent Era and inherited the legendary Battle God, One Autumn Leaf.

At that time, some were disappointed. Some were hopeful. Some hoped for a miracle.

And now a miracle had truly occurred!

Except this wasn’t the miracle that they had expected. Even when Excellent Era had fallen to second to last place for the first time that winter and the feelings of the fans were ice-cold like the weather, none of them would have ever imagined something like this could happen, but now, they were second to last place and the eighteenth place team, Bright Green, was five points ahead of them.

What a coincidence. This was the same point difference between Samsara and Blue Rain, but because of Team Blue Rain’s consistency, everyone thought that Blue Rain would definitely come in first, but in this case? Everyone thought that the situation was the exactly the same because Excellent Era was also very consistent. The only difference was that Blue Rain was consistently good, while Excellent Era was consistently bad. These two teams used to be regarded as powerhouses, but now their definitions of consistency were the opposite of each other. Fortunately, Blue Rain didn’t have any enmity towards Excellent Era. If Blue Rain had been Excellent Era’s long time rival, Tyranny, such a definite comparison would have gotten Excellent Era even more ridicule.

Even so, Excellent Era received a lot of mockery. After all, a tall tree attracts the wind. Many people hoped to see them fail! It was just that they could only fantasize Excellent Era getting relegated. Who would have thought that it would actually become reality? It truly was a miracle. Countless people were dying from laughter right now.

The fans of Excellent Era were unexpectedly calm though. Apart from growing numb to Excellent Era’s disastrous performances, the work done by Excellent Era’s PR department was starting to take effect. In one of their statements, they stated that this season was “incredibly disappointing” and that the team was in an “unprecedented crisis”. They also expressed that the Club had been “working their hardest”, but the “problem could not be resolved.”

In their statement, they even mentioned contacting the retired captain Ye Qiu, hoping that Ye Xiu would act as an advisor and help them find their problem. Unfortunately, Ye Qiu declined.

This was without a doubt a method of shifting everyone’s attention to somewhere else. They expressed that they had been working hard the entire time, while also tactfully explaining one of the reasons that they had been unable to resolve the problem. When the statement came out, Chen Guo slammed the table in anger, but many fans believed their words and started to criticize Ye Qiu. Ye Xiu himself heard the statement, but simply replied: “It’s the truth!”

“It’s true, but how can they spin it like that! It’s like they’re blaming your for their problems!” Chen Guo continued to vent.

At this moment, Wei Chen looked strangely at Chen Guo: “Are you saying it’s not his fault? If he didn’t wipe out their team in game, no matter how terrible Excellent Era performed, they wouldn’t be in such a messed up jumble that they might even end up getting relegated.”

“They reap what they sow.” Chen Guo refuted.

“Women! Weak, kind-hearted, and they don’t listen to reason! It’s an inborn trait.” Wei Chen sighed.

“Let’s stop arguing.” Ye Xiu hastily urged them to stop.

“Excellent Era getting relegated is my fault.” Ye Xiu expressed with sorrow. He didn’t wait for Chen Guo to refute and immediately continued: “But how would I have known that wiping them out in game would turn out like this? No one would have imagined that such actions would have so severe a consequence? But you can’t deny their current record either. They’re still young. They still have chances. They shouldn’t give up so easily. I don’t know what they plan on doing in the future. Too much has been happening recently. I want to be by myself for a bit. If you don’t need me for anything, I’ll be leaving.”

Ye Xiu took out a cigarette after speaking. Wei Chen and Chen Guo looked at one another. After a while, Chen Guo turned to Wei Chen and asked: “Why does that sound so familiar?”

“......”

In the end, Excellent Era was relegated. On May 13th, Glory’s eighth regular season came to an end.

Blue Rain, Samsara, Tiny Herb, Tyranny, Misty Rain, Void, 301, and Thunderclap entered the playoffs. The other teams were on break for the next week. Excellent Era and Mysterious Fantasy were relegated. In the Alliance’s history, relegations almost always meant the disappearance of a team. Except this time, a formerly glorious team like Excellent Era had been relegated, bringing about numerous discussions.

Some began to hold a memorial service for the end of an era, while others were confident that Excellent Era would rise again.

At the end, Club Excellent Era expressed clearly that this season had been a disaster, but it didn’t spell their end. Soon afterwards, they said a string of placating words to their fans. Their team’s ace player, Sun Xiang, wouldn’t be leaving the team because of this disaster.

Not many trusted their words though until Sun Xiang personally said so in an interview that he would get through these troubling days together with Excellent Era. At the same time, he spoke of how much care he had received from the Club ever since he had joined the Club, proving that, even though he had only been with Excellent Era for half a year, their relationship wasn’t limited by time. He definitely wouldn’t waver because they had been relegated.

“In next season’s Challenger League, I’ll lead Excellent Era back onto the pro stage!” Sun Xiang confidently said to the interviewer.

This concluded the interview, making Chen Guo want to puke.

Sun Xiang obviously wasn’t the only person the interviewer wanted to interview.

Excellent Era’s other extremely popular player, the All Star, Su Mucheng. There was also the vice captain Liu Hao, who had performed quite well throughout the season. There were also the main and substitute players. The interviewer wanted to interview as many people in Excellent Era as possible.

But unfortunately, whether it was because these people didn’t want to be interviewed or if the Club told them not to, they all refused every interviews. This caused the keen media people to think that Excellent Era wasn’t as calm as they pretended to be. Under this calm cover, what were they going to do next?

But right now wasn’t a good time to dig up this information. After a two week break, it would be the season playoffs. The competition to see who would be the champions of this season would begin. No matter the situation, these eight teams would undoubtedly be the highlight of the entire Glory scene.

Chapter 621 – Pressure on Team Happy

Hype for the playoffs spread like wildfire. As the most intense competition of every season, this was a huge way to rake in money for the Alliance. The teams that failed to enter the playoffs could only watch the happenings with envy. They wouldn’t be receive a piece of the pie for broadcasting the playoffs, ticket revenue, advertising, etc.

These were the concerns of the Club owners and managers. For the pro players, the playoffs was the highest stage obtainable and the place where they could attain the greatest glory.

As for the spectators, the playoffs was a time to enjoy high level competition. Glory wasn’t so popular that there would be discussions about it all over the streets, but in the Internet Cafe, Glory forums, Glory global chat, and guild chats, the places where Glory players gathered, the playoffs was undoubtedly the hottest topic. Everyone passionately discussed who they thought would take the championships.

From the online polls, Blue Rain, Samsara, and Tiny Herb were the most favored teams. Tyranny was a bit less favored. As for the four other teams, the meager amount of support they received was due to their zealous fans. After all, no one could give a convincing argument for why any of these four teams would be the winner.

Who would be the champion? The members of Team Happy were calmer in comparison to the public. Ye Xiu and Wei Chen had been a part of the pro scene before. Both of them were experienced players too. They had already adapted to their current circumstances. Since they weren’t participating in the playoffs, why would they be excited? The two calmly analyzed the weaknesses and strengths of each participating team.

As for the other three, after Chen Guo turned her back on Excellent Era, she invested her support into Team Happy instead. She didn’t really care who became the champion. As for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, they hadn’t played long enough to favor any of the teams. Now that they were a part of a team, they obviously didn’t have any favorites.

While people outside were discussing this question fervently, even as an aspiring pro team, Team Happy appeared a bit too calm.

On the other hand, they were much more interested in Excellent Era. After all, they were an approaching reality. However, this reality put a huge amount of pressure on them.

After Excellent Era got relegated, they calmly placated their fans. They had clearly prepared for everything long beforehand. They definitely had detailed plans for how to maintain their competitive state and return to the Alliance. Ye Xiu and the rest of the team knew that Excellent Era would be a fierce boss in the Challenger League, but even Ye Xiu, who had once been the captain of Excellent Era for seven years, didn’t know how much they would progress. Because he knew that, ever since his departure, Excellent Era had gone through bold and decisive changes. That team would never be the same team that he had once struggled for, so of course he wouldn’t know how it had changed.

“We won’t be so unlucky as to meet Excellent Era in the first round, right? That would be a joke.” In these past two days, Wei Chen often cracked these types of jokes to scare everyone.

“How about you shut your mouth!!” Ye Xiu often replied in this way. Everyone could tell that the usually calm Ye Xiu felt somewhat nervous towards Wei Chen’s jokes. This sort of possibility was theoretically possible. If it actually happened, the Challenger League would no longer be the start of their dreams, but rather the end.

With the team’s current strength, they didn’t need to worry about normal player teams, but in comparison to a professional team like Excellent Era, the difference between them wasn’t small. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were still far from being a pro player’s match! Their characters didn’t need to be mentioned. Both of their characters were still in the tenth server. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had a Silver weapon, but it was only Level 50 right now. Wei Chen’s Death Hand was also only Level 60. Even if they upgraded their two Silver weapons to max level, how could two Silver weapons compare to Excellent Era’s characters? A God-level character like One Autumn Leaf had a full set of Silver equipment!

The disparity between their characters was even larger than the disparity between players.

Both teams would be participating in the Challenger League, but the Challenger League only had one winner. This meant that, as long as neither of the two were eliminated early on, they would inevitably meet. In this case, meeting them early on would be much worse than meeting them later. In fact, the later they met, the better. Happy would have more time to improve, whether that be the players themselves or the characters.

Fortunately, this was a special feature of an eSport competition like Glory. The characters could grow as the season progressed. For example, if the character found a skill book in the game, the character could use it immediately. The character could also switch out his or her old equipment for better equipment.

For Ye Xiu, he wouldn’t be able to return to the pro scene until next year August. This period of time was enough for the team members and characters to grow, because even if they were participating in the Challenger League, they could also run back to the game and obtain more materials and equipment. When they entered the pro scene, their team would have definitely have improved significantly compared to their initial stage. Even after joining the pro scene, they could still grow while competing, because the regular season lasted a long time. A single match wouldn’t determine their team’s fate. Even if they encountered an incredibly difficult team in the beginning of the season, they still had a huge amount of time to improve. Perhaps by the end of the season, they would be able to enter the playoffs, and at that time, their strength might not lose out to any other team.

However, in the Challenger League, a single match could decide your fate. A powerful team like Excellent Era completely messed up Ye Xiu’s current plans. Right now, he needed to hurry and build up the team so that it would be strong enough to contest against such a formidable opponent. If Wei Chen’s joke became a reality and they met Excellent Era in the first round, in accordance with the Challenger League’s schedule, the first match would begin in September. The amount of time that Ye Xiu had originally planned to use to build up the team had now been reduced significantly. How could he not be anxious?

“Do you think Excellent Era has some dirty trick up their sleeves? From the looks of it, they have quite some enmity with you. If they were to play some trick behind our back and sabotage the competition arrangements with their connections, what would we do if they had our team fight against them in the first match?” The more Wei Chen spoke, the fiercer he became. The probability of this happening used to be infinitesimally small, but now he described a situation where the probability would be 100%.

“If that happens, I’ll go across the street and break their glass.” Ye Xiu wasn’t in a good mood.

“I’m just saying!” Wei Chen knew that he was poking at a sore spot, but he justified himself: “If they did that, they might not entirely be letting their emotions affect their decisions. You definitely make them worry as an opponent. They’ll also regard you as a formidable opponent in the Challenger League. They know about your situation and they know that time is of huge importance to our team. In order to ensure their victory, it isn’t completely impossible that they would mess with the rules in order to fight your team on the first round, no? You’ve been a part of Excellent Era for seven years. Does Excellent Era have the power to do that? You should be much more clear on such matters than me.”

When Wei Chen finished talking, he looked at Ye Xiu in anticipation, as if he were waiting for Ye Xiu to give him a precise answer. Ye Xiu immediately understood after seeing his expression. Wei Chen wasn’t any less worried than him. Wei Chen intentionally said these scary things to irritate him and also to make himself numb to the possibility. That way, his emotions wouldn’t be affected as much. He and Ye Xiu were clear that, even if they faced Excellent Era at the very end of the Challenger League, Excellent Era would still be an extremely difficult opponent for them.

Their opponents were a powerful force with eight years of accumulated resources and experiences. As for them? Since Ye Xiu’s departure from Excellent Era, it had only been half a year. His second best player was a middle-aged player, who had been retired for almost six years. The characters in his possession couldn’t even compare to most in-game experts. And they wanted to challenge Excellent Era? Don’t say that it would be a miracle! Even the author is getting tired of using this word!

After understanding Wei Chen’s intentions, Ye Xiu felt deeply moved. He didn’t answer with a biting remark like he usually did. Instead, he replied in a serious tone: “I don’t know.”

“You don’t know?” Wei Chen didn’t want to believe it either.

“Of course I don’t know. If they actually did that sort of shady business, of course not many would know about it.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck, I just want you to make a prediction. You should understand Excellent Era’s owner and manager and the current environment in the pro scene. Just analyze the possibility of it happening.” Wei Chen said.

Everyone in the practice room stopped what they were doing and looked at Ye Xiu, but Ye Xiu just stared at the ceiling and didn’t say anything for a long time.

“You don’t dare be certain, so it’s still a possibility, no?” Wei Chen said.

“Fine! I’ll help ask for you!” Ye Xiu suddenly straightened his back.

“Ask who?” Wei Chen was puzzled. He saw Ye Xiu open up QQ and in the team category, he clicked on a person’s name.

“Who’s this?” Wei Chen walked over. This person’s QQ name was in English. He definitely didn’t know who this person was.

“Excellent Era’s boss.” Ye Xiu said as he typed in a message: “I never thought we would actually be opponents.”

“F*ck f*ck f*ck! You just directly ran over to ask him? What if he hadn’t thought of it and now you reminded of it?” Wei Chen said.

“If he hadn’t thought of it, he still wouldn’t do it even if I reminded him. If he had planned on doing it, whether or not I remind him about it, he would still do it.” Ye Xiu said.

Wei Chen repeated his words and then cursed: “Are you saying a tongue twister?”

The other side on QQ suddenly lit up and replied: “It’s a bitter rivalry too.”

“Do you think we’ll meet in the first round?” Ye Xiu replied.

After a short pause, Wei Chen stared at the screen with wide eyes. After a while, the other side replied: “Ha ha, are you scared?”

Chapter 622 – The Boss’s Support

Tao Xuan, who was sitting in front of his computer, laughed out loud. He could empathize with how Ye Qiu was feeling right now. Anyone could imagine how much pressure a brand new team would face upon encountering a powerhouse like Excellent Era. For Tao Xuan, participating in the Challenger League truly wasn’t anything to be happy about, but he was feeling a bit excited seeing how much worry it was giving Ye Qiu.

Tao Xuan didn’t know when it started, but he had begun becoming more and more annoyed at how serious Ye Qiu dedicated himself to Glory. In the end, wasn’t this just a game? What was more important than having fun? But Ye Qiu was extremely passionate and persistent in winning. Whenever he did something, it would always be with victory in mind. But anything else unrelated would always be treated with indifference.

Having a passion for victory wasn’t a bad thing in itself. From a business perspective, someone with a personality was easier to work with than someone without a personality. However, Ye Qiu refused to cooperate on the business end. Because both sides had signed a long-term contract early on, when they wrote up the contract, they hadn’t thought too far into the future so the contract didn’t have any clauses or terms on cooperating with the business end. It wasn’t his fault for being too careless. How could he have imagined that anyone would refuse a win-win cooperation?

As the Glory Alliance rapidly developed, the ace players of the teams brought numerous benefits to their respective Clubs. The more Tao Xuan saw these benefits pass by him, the more he couldn’t sit still. Even though he had a prolific money tree like Su Mucheng, the more he felt the benefits of having Su Mucheng helping the business end, the more he loathed how Ye Qiu wouldn’t cooperate with him.

Ye Qiu was Excellent Era’s ace. He was the king who founded their dominating dynasty. In his hands, he held the famed Battle God One Autumn Leaf and was awarded Best Partners with the extremely popular Su Mucheng for several years in a row. Ye Qiu was like an enormous gold mine that couldn’t be mined. Year after year, day after day passed. It didn’t seem like this gold mine would ever be mined. Tao Xuan finally couldn’t bear it anymore. If Ye Qiu wouldn’t cooperate, why not throw him away?

Tao Xuan had thought of doing so a long time ago, but he never made the order because no one could succeed him. He didn’t need just anyone who could play a Battle Mage. One Autumn Leaf was a top character in Glory and required a top-tier God to play it in order for it to have any business value.

Correct. Tao Xuan always considered things with the business in mind. He also wanted Ye Qiu to see that after cooperating together, the character and the player would push towards new heights. He hoped that Ye Qiu would feel regret towards refusing a cooperation. He hoped that Ye Qiu would admit that he was wrong.

Although there were many Battle Mage players in the Alliance, none of them fit Tao Xuan’s requirements. Finding a successor to Ye Qiu was easier said than done. He could only continue waiting until he saw Sun Xiang appear. This youth had talent, a boundless future, mastery over the Battle Mage class, and didn’t have a God-level character. Sun Xiang was without a doubt a fitting successor.

The old being replaced by the new was something that teams often had to deal with, but no Club was as impatient was Tao Xuan. He had tolerated Ye Qiu for too many years and a talent like Sun Xiang would quickly be taken away by another team. Excellent Era no longer had complete dominance over the league like in the past. They were just now one of the powerhouses.

Tao Xuan not only wanted Sun Xiang to come, he wanted him to immediately take over. He wished he could instantly kick Ye Qiu out.

These were Tao Xuan’s true thoughts. If he could have done so without any terrible consequences, he would have done so immediately. But there was nothing he could do. Ye Qiu’s prestige was just too high. He was still bringing his team to the top. If he suddenly had a successor without even deciding to retire yet and was treated so roughly, the Club would be criticized harshly. Tao Xuan place a great amount of importance on the Club’s business. The support of the fans was extremely important. After all, no matter how smoothly a business operated, their needed to be supporters to provide the income. Tao Xuan needed to be careful not to offend fans.

After thinking it over, even if gently transferred Ye Qiu away, he would come across a lot of obstacles. The fans definitely wouldn’t be able to accept it and Tao Xuan wouldn’t be happy with the transfer either. No one knew better than him how capable Ye Qiu was. If he transferred Ye Qiu away, Ye Qiu would become a powerful enemy. The other teams would be laughing at his decision. Thus, the best result would be if Ye Qiu retired forever.

Tao Xuan understood this point, so he had made plans long ago.

As the owner of a team, he had a lot of work to do. Simply speaking, for a team to run smoothly, the coordination between every department had to be extremely tight. And any cooperation between himself and the team’s senior, even if it was just his attitude towards him, could have huge consequences.

For example, it was widely known in Team Tyranny that once, Han Wenqing was lecturing a team member, when he was interrupted by the boss’s phone call. Han Wenqing shouted at the boss and hung up.

Did this mean that Han Wenqing had more authority than the boss? Or that the boss was actually scared of Han Wenqing?

Of course not. A part of it was Han Wenqing’s personality. Another part of it was that the boss acted according to his personality. Han Wenqing had immediately picked up the phone, even in this special situation. This minute action showed how much trust he gave to the boss.

Many people saw it as a reflection of Han Wenqing’s tyranny. But in reality, this was the boss’s respect for his team’s captain.

Trust and respect.

The boss and players needed this type of relationship. In particular, the team captain required the boss’s strong support. A difference in views could harm the team captain’s authority over the team because the players knew who the team truly belonged to, who decided their futures, and who gave them their salaries. If the boss didn’t support the team captain, the team captain would have difficulty being respected by his team.

After Tao Xuan decided to give up on Ye Qiu, he had quietly weakened Ye Qiu’s authority in the team. It would be hard to avoid Excellent Era’s records from being affects. Tao Xuan anticipated it would delince. After all, nothing good could come without sacrifice. In order to make a chance, their records would waver. If their records wavered, the fans would also weaken their support for Ye Qiu. It would make things easier for them to accept his leave.

Once Sun Xiang stormed onto the scene, Tao Xuan finally saw the person he needed and finally put his plans into actions starting in the eighth scene. All sorts of issues arose in the team and their record declined drastically. The fans openly complained as Tao Xuan quickly signed an agreement to transfer Sun Xiang over to Excellent Era that winter.

However, Tao Xuan hadn’t imagined that the team’s record would drop so badly. He had underestimated Ye Qiu’s importance to the team, but the more it was like this, he more he despised Ye Qiu. In his eyes, Ye Qiu was not their team’s core, but their team’s tyrant. He was a tumor that needed to be removed.

Thus, he went along with his original plans. He transferred Sun Xiang over that winter and forced Ye Qiu to retire. Even though the fans were sad, their support for Team Excellent Era didn’t change too much just because of a single change.

Tao Xuan relaxed. The worst hadn’t happened, making him feel like he had passed a huge block. He was still worried about Su Mucheng though. When he decided to kick out Ye Qiu, Tao Xuan had already accepted that he might need to give up on Su Mucheng as well. After all, his tolerance for Ye Qiu had reached his limits. Su Mucheng would cause him to waver over his decision to kick Ye Qiu out of the team and rebuild the team anew.

Tao Xuan originally thought everything would progress like he had expected, but the team’s records actually dropped to the bottom. This was something that truly shocked him. He was at a loss towards the team. As the boss, he knew a lot of things, but there were also a lot of things he didn’t know.

His enmity towards Ye Qiu had ended when he kicked Ye Qiu out of the team, but he didn’t think that Liu Hao would have an even deeper enmity than him towards Ye Qiu. Liu Hao chasing after Ye Qiu had affected his performance and led to a disastrous loss for Excellent Era. Afterwards, Liu Hao quickly adjusted and the team gradually stabilized. But after Ye Qiu left, he didn’t give up. He wanted to try again and created a huge storm in the tenth server. His existence caused no end to trouble for the Clubs. He even caused a commotion amongst the pro players.

If it was just Huang Shaotian or Wang jiexi running to the game to fight with Ye Qiu, it wouldn’t make a difference. But Excellent Era’s enmity towards Ye Qiu ran deep! As soon as there was a chance, Liu Hao wanted to fight and even brought Sun Xiang into the mess. Then, he called over the entire main team. The first time, Liu Hao’s condition had been affected. The next time, the entire team’s condition had been affected. This season, Excellent Era hadn’t been doing well in the first place. Now that their condition declined even further, their record plummeted even faster. Sun Xiang had trouble recovering from the blow. He was like a toothless old tiger who couldn’t bring about any energy.

At the end of the season, the team directly dropped into relegations and the players panicked. Relegations was a catastrophe for any team. No one wanted to be on a sinking ship, so their morale completely died. Tao Xuan was unable to turn around the situation. In the end, he could only prepare for their relegations and trust that this crisis would pass.

Getting relegated definitely wasn’t within Tao Xuan’s predictions. He wasn’t happy at all about this result. And everything was because of Ye Qiu.

If it wasn’t for him, how could things have ended up like this?

Lord Grim? Did you really think you could start over from zero? Tao Xuan sneered, seeing the changed name on QQ. That instant, he suddenly felt like participating in the Challenger League wasn’t too bad. Even though their image would certainly take a hit, personally eliminating Ye Qiu would certainly be a sight to see. At this time, Tao Xuan finally saw the other side reply: “Are you scared of me?”

Chapter 623 – Fundamental Doctrine

Are you afraid of me?

Tao Xuan felt the urge to jump out of the window, run across the street, and slap his face until it bled.

“I’m afraid of you???”

Tao Xuan typed it out, but before clicking send, he wondered if his reply seemed too serious. He should be looking down on this question in contempt and express that Ye Qiu didn’t even have the qualification to ask him such a thing.

So maybe I shouldn’t reply back? His mouse hovered over the send button. Tao Xuan hesitated for a long time. Do I reply or not? He finally realized how painful it must have been for enemies to talk trash with Ye Qiu. Just this single question made him furious. If he replied, he’d be angry. If he didn’t reply, he’d still be angry. He could easily imagine how getting aggravated from this question could affect someone’s performance. If a player hesitated like Tao Xuan had right now, the player would be dead.

“Look. He’s not replying. He’s scared.” Across the street at Happy Internet Cafe, Ye Xiu told Wei Chen and the others looking at his chat window. Fortunately, it wasn’t a voice chat, so Tao Xuan couldn’t hear what he was saying. If not, he really might have run across the street and vented his rage.

“F*ck off. He’s probably shocked by your shamelessness!” Wei Chen countered. Excellent Era being scared of a brand new team? What a joke.

“We should always be confident in ourselves.” Ye Xiu advised.

“F*ck, then why are we being so nervous for? We should just fight with Excellent Era in round one. You can go up alone and wipe them out by yourself! Go ahead!” Wei Chen urged.

They argued back and forth. On the other side, Tao Xuan finally replied. In the end, he erased his “I’m scared of you???” message and typed: “Give me a reason to be scared of you.”

“You still need a reason? Everyone in Glory is afraid of me. It’s common knowledge.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Sh*t, I can’t take it anymore. Everyone look at how despicable this guy is!!!” Wei Chen shouted. Steamed Bun and Tang Rou had been playing Glory, so they hadn’t been reading the conversation taking place. Now, Wei Chen called them over. Chen Guo had been watching too. When she saw the reply, she was already bashing her head against the wall.

“Maybe in the past, but now……” Tao Xuan answered back using ellipses.

“Now? You should go to the game and interview people. Both the tenth server and the Heavenly Domain are fine.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Showing off your skills in game! Not bad!” Tao Xuan remarked cynically. Honestly, he almost didn’t believe he had said this. It wasn’t like him, but as the owner of a powerful Club, very few talked to him in this way. Today, Ye Xiu did it! Ye Xiu had brought someone of a higher status down to his level and was talking trash with him on QQ. What an incredible talent for taunting!

“The game is Glory’s foundation. Would you dare to close Excellent Dynasty?” Ye Xiu asked back.

“If you’d like, I can arrange a position for you in Excellent Dynasty.” Tao Xuan let go of everything. He rolled up his sleeves, ready to fight it out with Ye Qiu.

“No need. I recommend paying attention to Excellent Dynasty. Don’t let it close down.” Ye Xiu said.

“Because of you?” Tao Xuan asked.

“Why don’t you ask Chen Yehui? He’d be scared to death.” Ye Xiu said.

This time, Tao Xuan couldn’t think of a reply. Ye Xiu looked as if he had definitive proof that what he was saying was correct, but Tao Xuan didn’t know if it was the truth or not. He had never personally participated in any of these matters! It’s like a debate, where one side raised a strong argument, while the other side couldn’t answer and could only emphasize a previous point. Even though Ye Xiu didn’t raise any strong argument, he still gave off that sort of feeling. His words were rooted in reality, while Tao Xuan’s words were baseless.

“See, he didn’t reply again. I win!” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck, what did you come here for then!” Wei Chen was fuming. He had watched them talk trash each other back and forth. Ye Xiu’s original goal was to confirm that their team wouldn’t encounter Excellent Era in the first round. He directly asked for confirmation, but after going back and forth at it for a long time, he still hadn’t gotten an answer to the question. A great God and a great boss were bickering like little kids. It was so childish.

“There’s no point talking any further. We’ll talk on stage!” Tao Xuan replied.

“Good. It looks like you haven’t changed. Prove your words on the battlefield.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ha ha, I’d suggest lighting some incense. You’d better pray you don’t meet us in the first round!” Tao Xuan said.

“Mm, I’ll be praying.” Ye Xiu replied. At the same time, he sent an emoji of a panda burning incense.

Ye Xiu’s words suddenly changed from offensive to defensive. Tao Xuan saw the emoji of a panda burning incense and after a short pause, he answered: “I’ll see you on stage.”

“I’ll see you on stage.” Ye Xiu replied and closed the chat window.

“Done?” Wei Chen stared with wide eyes.

“Done.”

“What’s the result.”

“We’ll see each other on stage.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck! Did you get an answer or not.” Wei Chen said.

“He won’t try to rig anything. Who will win and who will lose will be decided on stage.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re sure?” Wei Chen confirmed.

“Mm.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“Why?” Wei Chen didn’t understand. It looked like the two of them had some enmity towards each other.

“I’ve known him for many years. Even though our goals changed, a few fundamental principles still haven’t changed.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why did it feel like even if they hadn’t changed, he was about to change them out of anger after being mocked by you?” Wei Chen said.

“Only someone as immoral as you would do something like that.” Ye Xiu said.

“I really want to throw you out of the window!!” Wei Chen really wanted to bash his head against the wall. Ye Xiu had given him an answer with certainty, but after watching the conversation that had just taken place, he wasn’t convinced that the messages were definitive. Wei Chen was still unsure. Then, Ye Xiu turned around and said to him: “Hurry up and burn some incense!”

“What do you mean?” Wei Chen stared blankly.

“Even if he doesn’t rig the matchups, there is still a possibility for us to meet in the first round. If we don’t burn incense, what do we do?” Ye Xiu said.

“What’s the f*cking point of burning incense?” Wei Chen cursed.

“Then what will work?” Ye Xiu asked.

Wei Chen was stumped. What else would work? Even if Excellent Era didn’t personally rig it, it wasn’t possible to completely eliminate the possibility of them meeting in the first round. If they actually won the lottery and got Excellent Era, they couldn’t run away from it.

“Okay, let’s hurry up and practice!” Wei Chen said and went back to his seat.

The practice room suddenly became quiet again. Wei Chen suddenly asked: “Boss, if we go and rob those elite group leaders, will you still object?”

“That isn’t a good reason to do so, is it?” Chen Guo was surprised by the sudden question, but quickly replied back.

“Great. Everyone has their principles. How great.” Wei Chen muttered.

“Someone as completely unscrupulous like you must feel deeply touched, right?” Ye Xiu said.

“Tch.” Wei Chen clicked his tongue in disdain. He grabbed his headphones and returned to the game.

“It’s f*cking time to start work! Today’s the day that the dungeons refresh! Where’s your energy?! If you guys can’t even stay in your positions and kill yourself like last time, I’ll kick you out of the elite group and you’ll never come back!!!!” Wei Chen roared. He began leading Samsara’s elite group in tackling the dungeon. Wei Chen’s work in Eternal Springs had been very fruitful. In reality, even the top elite groups of the Club guilds could pass through the Seven Great Dungeons every time. They often wiped out after several bosses, but under Wei Chen’s lead, their elite group’s clear rate had improved greatly. Last week, the elite group had performed terribly. The dungeon had ten bosses. On the fourth boss, so many had died that they could no longer continue, making Wei Chen extremely angry.

‘Is he….. okay?” Chen Guo walked over to Ye Xiu and whispered to him.

“Relax. Don’t worry about it. The good thing about old people is that they can take care of their own problems.” Ye Xiu said with confidence.

“Oh, that’s good.” Chen Guo nodded her head. Then, she pointed to Ye Xiu’s screen: “Someone messaged you.”

“Hm?” Ye Xiu clicked on the message, “Oh, it’s Concealed Light!”

Concealed Light had messaged Ye Xiu on QQ.

“Hey, what’s up?” Ye Xiu replied.

“I studied the stuff you sent me. I confirmed that many of things inside are highly likely through the calculations I made. I also corrected a few mistakes through backwards reasoning. There were a few parts of it that I wasn’t too sure of. Later, I asked my professor and, based on the data and calculations made, I created a mathematical model for it with his guidance. I’ll send it to you so that you can take a look at.” Concealed Light messaged.

“Holy sh*t. Wait a minute. I pretty much don’t understand anything that you have said this far. How did your professor get into this?” Ye Xiu was sweating.

“There were a lot of things that I couldn’t figure out, so I could only ask for help. Relax. My professor is Professor Zhang Yichun.” Concealed Light said.

“How can I relax?!” Ye Xiu replied. Chen Guo felt proud: “Amazing. A university professor is even helping us!”

“University professor?” The others were puzzled when they heard this.

“Yeah, Concealed Light asked Professor Zhang Yichun to help us study the data!” Chen Guo exclaimed.

“Who?” The others didn’t have any reaction, but Tang Rou was astonished.

“Professor Zhang Yichun.” Chen Guo said the name again, but she clearly didn’t know who this person was either.

“You guys don’t know who he is?” Tang Rou looked at them helplessly.

“Who is he?” The others asked in unison.

“He’s a world famous mathematician and a member of the National Academy of the Sciences. He’s made several breakthroughs in several fields of mathematics. What type of student is Concealed Light that he’d be personally taught by such a world class mathematician?” Tang Rou asked as she walked over. She wanted to see their conversation too.

Chapter 624 – The Pinnacle of Research

“Scientist?” Wei Chen sounded as if he were mumbling to himself. It was clear that his brain couldn't digest the fact that he would ever have anything to do with these types of people in his life.

“Are you stupid? He’s a mathematician.” Ye Xiu looked down on him.

“F*ck, isn’t that the same thing?” Wei Chen yelled.

Apart from Steamed Bun, everyone else found it difficult to breathe after Tang Rou told them about Zhang Yichuan’s identity and status.

“Concealed Light, you’re actually the student of such a math god? What sort of background do you have?” Ye Xiu asked him Tang Rou’s question.

“What’s the point in asking him about it? Do you even know anything about universities?” Wei Chen asked Ye Xiu.

“Even if one has never eaten a pig before, that doesn’t mean one has never seen one running around.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’ve seen a pig running around a university?” Wei Chen said.

“It’s impossible to talk with uncultured people like you!” Ye Xiu said.

At this moment, Concealed Light replied back on QQ. He didn’t have any special background, but he was incredible. He had received countless awards from participating in math competitions as a teen. He was a specially enrolled math student who had been accepted into the university without needing to take any of the required examinations at the age of 17. Although he was only a second year, that was just a title. With the knowledge that Concealed Light possessed, he had already learned everything that could be learned in a normal math undergraduate student’s curriculum. He was getting ready to apply as a recommended graduate student next year. He told them that, if possible, he would like to finish his Master’s and PhD at the same time.

“Ambitious!” Ye Xiu didn’t really know what else to say.

However, Concealed Light didn’t think too much of himself. Along the way, he would often hear about people getting their PhDs at the age of 20, people being employed as professors in all kinds of famous universities at the age of 24, people receiving all kinds of medals and achievements before the age of 30, people with IQs over 200. Compared to those inhuman geniuses, Concealed Light lamented in QQ: “No, no, I’m still far off!”

The people before the computer looked at one another with consternation and didn’t know what to say.

“Wouldn’t it be a loss to our country if we let a talent like him get into gaming?” Even Wei Chen felt like a sinner.

“There’s a lot of pressure.” Ye Xiu agreed.

“When you asked your mentor for help, did he say anything?” Ye Xiu asked. According to conventional thinking, instead of studying properly, you play games and even ask your teacher for help with your issues about the game, aren’t you asking to be whipped?

“Professor Zhang? He said the problem was pretty interesting.” Concealed Light replied.

This problem was pretty interesting......

Ye Xiu and the people wanted to kneel out of respect. Even though they didn’t understand any of what was being talked about with their education levels, they at least knew that it had to do with the logic or rules involved in the game’s data. However, according to a mathematician from the National Academy of Sciences, this was just another problem?

At least he said the problem was pretty interesting. It meant that Glory wasn’t a drag. Glory really had some depth to it.

However, designers, engineers, programmers of Glory: Apologies, but your problem has been solved.

“I’ll send it over for you guys to have a look at!” Concealed Light said as he sent the document over.

Ye Xiu turned serious when he opened the file. It wouldn’t be right to categorize what they were about to do as hacking. This really wasn’t hacking, it was just exposing the core of Glory.

However, a problem soon came about.

Ye Xiu and Wei Chen were top experts in calculating the consumption of a character’s HP or MP, calculating the cooldown of a skill, attack range, positioning, movement speed, jump height, etc. But when the game was unraveled to its roots, the two could only stare at each other blankly.

“Ahem.” Ye Xiu coughed.

“This……” Tang Rou also mumbled.

“Hm?” Everyone immediately gazed at her with hope.

“This is definitely not something we can understand.” Tang Rou said.

“I agree.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why don’t we buy some books?” Wei Chen said.

“Math books?” Ye Xiu asked.

“What else? Language books?” Wei Chen was disdainful towards Ye Xiu’s stupid question.

“You should go buy some books on morals!” Ye Xiu said while he searched for Concealed Light on QQ: “Concealed Light, do you think that we can interpret this?”

“You don’t understand anything?” Concealed Light asked.

“This kid’s not laughing at us right now, is he?” Ye Xiu turned around to ask the people behind him.

“Do you think everyone is like you?” Chen Guo refuted. Did he really think that everyone was a natural at taunting like him?

“I don’t understand it. Not even a little bit.” Ye Xiu replied to Concealed Light.

“Then what should we do?” Concealed Light asked.

“Uh, use the same language that you use for your guides and describe this information to us.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, I understand what you mean.” Concealed Light replied.

“Then you wouldn’t need to bother your teacher again with this, right?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No need, he’s never played Glory before, so he wouldn’t know.” Concealed Light replied.

“Sorry for the trouble.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay, wait for my good news!” Concealed Light said.

“Also.” Ye Xiu hurriedly called for Concealed Light, “The Pro League for this season is going to be ending soon. As for us, we plan on participating in the Challenger League in September. Would that be alright with you? Would it be too busy for you or distract you from your studies?”

“No, no, I’m not busy. I have plenty of time, September is it? I understand!” Concealed Light said.

“Then off you go!”

Concealed Light’s picture dimmed. Ye Xiu heard sighs of relief sound out from behind him. Concealed Light saw himself as someone ‘far off’, but in the eyes of everyone else, he was an extraordinary person, needless to mention his incredible teacher. Having him play Glory instantly made everyone feel like their burden had become even heavier.

“Go back to your seats! Why are you all still standing around for?” Ye Xiu turned around and shooed away the three dazed people behind him. Look at how calm Steamed Bun was! At first, he joined in to see why there was a crowd, but after opening the things that Concealed Light sent over, everyone felt ashamed for not understanding a thing, except for Steamed Bun, who said “What’s this” and returned to his seat to continue playing.

Everyone returned to their seats. No one spoke in the practice room, and only the tapping of the keyboard and mouse could be heard. Apart from Steamed Bun, everyone else was robotic and stiff. Evidently, everyone was still digesting the news and couldn’t calm down at that moment.

Ye Xiu and the others didn’t understand any of it. On the other hand, the hardest part for Concealed Light had been coming up with a model. However, understanding it and explaining it in simpler words wasn’t a problem for him. Not long afterwards, Concealed Light returned to QQ and messaged Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu didn’t make it public to prevent everyone else from making a big fuss over nothing. Concealed Light sent some things over while saying: “Does this make more sense?”

Ye Xiu received it and read it. The familiar Concealed Light had returned! It was like one of Concealed Light’s old guides, long-winded and down to the finest detail, but this time, Ye Xiu needed instructions like this, so he immediately gave out a series of loud praises.

“Then I’ll keep going.” Concealed Light spoke as he focused again.

“Come look at this.” Ye Xiu immediately called Wei Chen over. After all, Wei Chen was the researcher for this project. He had a strong impression and understanding of the data he had pulled. When he came over to see Concealed Light’s guide, he couldn’t help but to feel curious about it. It turned out that everything Wei Chen had described in the draft was turned into data by Concealed Light. Most importantly, all the logical relationships between the triggering requirements were listed out clearly.

Wei Chen originally had things like this, but that was through his experience and intuition. After being sorted out by Concealed Light, it had become facts.

“You go try it?” Wei Chen couldn’t wait to know the results.

“Mm, everyone will try it.” Ye Xiu spoke and called Steamed Bun and Tang Rou over. The parts Concealed Light had just sorted were coincidentally contents for quests in the normal servers.

There were a lot of quests in Glory. If it was just for gaining experience to level up, then there were too many quests to finish. Glory wasn’t just a game anymore either. The experienced players had found the most optimal ways to level up. The quests were picked out logically, so almost everyone did the same quests.

The situation in the new servers were better. After all, not everyone would go check a guide before they played the game. Some players liked to find their own way and find their own quests to do because there was plenty of content in the game.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun weren’t enthusiastic about quests. Tang Rou simply had no interest in the quests at all. If not for the rewards from quests such as stat or skill points, she wouldn’t have done any quests. As for Steamed Bun, he did whatever he wanted and lacked planning. He might be clearing monsters, but when you call out “Steamed Bun, come for a quest”, he would immediately come. Or perhaps, he was on such a quest, and when you called out “Steamed Bun, come join for a dungeon”, he would instantly drop his quest for the dungeon.

The data that Wei Chen had obtained was important in creating a character. Skill points decided the level of a skill, which greatly influenced a character’s strength in battle. So when Wei Chen investigated on such a thing, Ye Xiu didn’t care whether it was useful or not, he first checked what the quests were. The required quests were removed.

After all, these quests weren’t daily quests. It couldn’t be done again if it had already been completed. Otherwise, Wei Chen didn’t need to investigate so much. He could just research one quest and keep on repeating it. Besides, if skill points were awarded just by completing quests repeatedly, then it wouldn’t be an issue in the first place. With this many players, there wouldn’t be anymore secrets that hadn’t been found for repeatable quests.

But now, after passing through the hands of Concealed Light, this material had become more realistic and accurate. They had really reached the pinnacle by investigating the game to this point. To surpass this, one would have to directly alter the game, and that would be hacking.

Chapter 625 – Worry

The three aspiring pro players Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Ye Xiu still didn’t have max leveled characters.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist was the highest level among them at Level 69. She would be considered a high level player in the tenth server, but she couldn’t compare to the Club guilds, who leveled their characters 24/7. The first batch of max leveled characters in the tenth server appeared at the start of April. Usually, it wouldn’t be until mid-April when the first max leveled characters appeared in a new server. The reason that the tenth server had their first batch of characters come out before then was because of the huge exp rewards from the Christmas event.

Relying on the advantage gained from the Christmas event, the first batch of characters reached Level 70 ahead of schedule. Afterwards, the Club guilds worked hard at leveling their characters, keeping up the same leveling speed as usual.

Tang Rou played a lot more compared to the vast majority of players, but she could only play two thirds of what the Club guilds could play with their 24/7 leveling. In the end, she was left further and further behind. It was only until today that she made it to the final step before Level 70.

Steamed Bun Invasion was Level 68. He was only one level behind Soft Mist. But in reality, he hadn’t been able to close the distance that had been made during the Christmas event. The amount of experience needed for a Level 60 character was very different compared to the amount of experience needed for a Level 30 character. Even though it was only a one level difference, the experience disparity was huge. It would take Steamed Bun Invasion several days more than Soft Mist to reach Level 70.

In comparison, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had a very difficult time leveling in the Heavenly Domain. The advantage he had established during the Christmas event had quickly been whittled away by Steamed Bun Invasion. But after the short break at Level 55, Lord Grim’s leveling speed soared. First of all, Ye Xiu was much more skilled than Steamed Bun Invasion. Secondly, the Heavenly Domain was much more generous with rewarding experience, so leveling there was naturally faster than in the normal servers. Thus, because of the Christmas event Lord Grim had pulled a distance away from Steamed Bun Invasion, who eventually caught up and surpassed him. Later, he started catching up to Steamed Bun Invasion…… Currently, Lord Grim was Level 66, two levels behind Steamed Bun Invasion. Their level difference was mostly because of the time that Ye Xiu had spent on Unrivaled Super Hottie. During that time, Lord Grim hadn’t been leveling.

In truth, apart from Lord Grim, the levels of their characters had never been an issue. Lord Grim was an unspecialized and a max leveled unspecialized couldn’t be bought. At best, he would be able to get a Level 50 account. As for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, there were only advantages and no disadvantages to have them personally level their characters to max because they were still new to the game.

At present, things couldn’t be better having these clean accounts with Wei Chen’s skill book guide. If Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze came, she might have already done some of these quests. Even if she knew how to get better rewards from these quests, she would no longer have the chance to get them.

When Ye Xiu gave the small portion that Concealed Light had interpreted so far to Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, Chen Guo was naturally very happy to get a copy of her own too. Afterwards, she got on her Chasing Haze and returned to the normal server to start following the guide.

Ye Xiu wasn’t in a hurry though. He logged out of his game and ran over to Steamed Bun’s side.

Steamed Bun was staring at the document given to him with his brows furrowed. After awhile, he finally noticed that Ye Xiu was next to him.

“It’s so complicated.” Steamed Bun said.

“It just has a lot of words. It’s really not that complicated.” Ye Xiu said.

“Concealed Light talks too much nonsense!” Steamed Bun sighed. He probably didn’t care that Concealed Light was a math genius, who would very likely be getting his PhD in math at a very young age. He still regarded him as a little kid.

“Go try it out!” Ye Xiu said.

“I was just about to go.” Steamed Bun had his character head to the location of the first quest in the guide.

Ye Xiu didn’t walk away. He continued to watch Steamed Bun.

It was very wise for Ye Xiu to stay with Steamed Bun. Not long after accepting the quest, he had begun deviating from the guide.

“Where are you going?” Ye Xiu didn’t realize it at first. He thought that Steamed Bun had gotten lost, so he asked.

“Hm? Aren’t we going to fight Frank?” Steamed Bun said.

“You’re going to duel him already? There’s two steps in between that you haven’t done yet!” Ye Xiu said.

“Really?” Steamed Bun went back to the guide and after reading for a long time: “Oops. I skipped a line.”

“You skipped three lines?” Ye Xiu said.

“There are too many words……” Steamed Bun’s defense was reasonable. After thinking about it for a bit, Ye Xiu felt that it really was an issue and not just an excuse.

Steamed Bun read those three lines again very carefully and then asked excitedly: “What happens if I don’t do these in order and just go and duel Frank?”

“We can try it next time. For now, let’s follow the guide.” Ye Xiu lied. At this point, he was too afraid to let Steamed Bun do anything on his own right now. Sure enough, having Steamed Bun do such a precise and mechanical task was very suspenseful. Steamed Bun’s thought process far surpassed what an ordinary person could think of.

“Okay!” Steamed Bun listened to Ye Xiu’s suggestion and followed the guide.

“How’s it going?” Wei Chen was clearly very concerned with the results. He put down his work and headed over to watch.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything. He continued to pay attention to each and every one of Steamed Bun’s movements. Wei Chen went over to Tang Rou’s side to watch.

“Almost there!” It was almost the last step, when there would be a chance for a skill book to drop. Wei Chen started getting anxious.

Even Tang Rou, who had only played Glory for five months, knew the value of skill books. After all, she played on her character every day and understood the importance of skills. She had a good understanding of an extra level in a skill could do.

Now that they had reached the final step, Tang Rou paused for a bit before completing it.

The rewards came out. Tang Rou and Wei Chen were both disappointed. The skill book that they had hoped for didn’t come out.

“Did we make a mistake?” Wei Chen said.

“Be patient. It was never guaranteed that a skill book would drop, right? The guide that Concealed Light had created was based on the framework that you had provided, no? Even if we follow it, luck is still needed. Concealed Light never said it was guaranteed. He said that it was better than your original method by 17.481%. In the end, the probability of one dropping is still only 34.314%. It’s not that high, so it’s normal that it didn’t drop.” Ye Xiu said.

“Are there any guaranteed drops that we can try?” Wei Chen was very anxious. In reality, he was still worried about Excellent Era getting relegated. Wei Chen wasn’t like Tang Rou or Steamed Bun. They were still new and didn’t understand the vast difference between them and Excellent Era. On the other hand, Wei Chen understood it well and couldn’t relax. He was very stressed out right now.

“There aren’t any in the guide so far. There might be later. Shh, we’re almost there too.” Ye Xiu said.

Under Ye Xiu’s supervision, Steamed Bun was about to reach the final step too. Here, Steamed Bun showed his cool-headedness. He had his character jog over and turn in the quest. Wei Chen couldn’t even look.

“Did it drop?” When Wei Chen turned back, he hastily asked.

“No.” Ye Xiu shook his head in disappointment.

“So unlucky!” Wei Chen was gloomy.

“Don’t panic. There are more chances, no?” Ye Xiu said.

“But we’ll never be able to get this 20 point skill book again.” Wei Chen shook his head.

“Old Wei!” Ye Xiu shouted.

“What?” Wei Chen was still depressed.

“It seems like you really need to go across the street and break a few of Excellent Era’s windows to calm down.” Ye Xiu said. He had told Chen Guo that she didn’t need to be worried about Wei Chen because he would be able to adjust himself. But Wei Chen didn’t act like he had expected. Wei Chen was constantly stressed and very unlike what an experienced player should be like. These past few years of reclusion had stifled Wei Chen. Suddenly, he had been presented with an ambitious goal and couldn’t control his excitement. But the more passionate he was about it, the more worried he became. This type of state of mind would negatively affect his performance.

“Mm, I’ll go smoke a cigarette.” Wei Chen didn’t retort. He took out a cigarette and went outside to smoke. Even he knew that his current behavior was abnormal. However, something like emotions couldn’t be controlled so easily.

“Little Tang, keep going! Help me watch Steamed Bun too.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ll help!” Chen Guo got up and prepared to be like Steamed Bun’s nanny for doing quests. Steamed Bun really needed someone to take care of him for these quests.

Ye Xiu nodded his head and went out the door. He saw Wei Chen standing at the window, smoking and staring blankly out the window.

Ye Xiu walked up and looked outside too. Excellent Era’s logo stood out clearly. It was probably incomparably unsightly in Wei Chen’s eyes.

“What do I do? I can’t help but be nervous.” Wei Chen said.

“You’re too worried.” Ye Xiu said.

“How could I not be worried? That’s Excellent Era!” Wei Chen said.

“Yeah. It’s just Excellent Era. You’ve never met them?” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ve met them. And that was during Excellent Era’s golden era. But I’m also much worse compared to the me in the past!” Wei Chen said.

“What about you now? You have strengths now that you didn’t have before.” Ye Xiu said.

“Age?” Wei Chen laughed mockingly.

“That’s just one.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh? There’s more?’ Wei Chen was surprised. He thought Ye Xiu would console him by telling him about one of his experiences.

“The person who crushed you in the past is now your teammate.” Ye Xiu said.

Wei Chen turned his head to look at Ye Xiu and then continued to look out the window: “Tch, that’s what I’m worried about!”

“I’ve never viewed Excellent Era like this before.” Ye Xiu looked out the window.

“In what way?”

“Viewed them as opponents that I have to defeat.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 626 – The Character with the Most Skill Points

Opponents that must be defeated.

When Ye Xiu said these words, he didn’t grind his teeth or give a determined look. He seemed as calm as ever.

“Yes! They must be defeated.” Wei Chen followed, but he wasn’t calm at all. He said these words fiercely and crushed his cigarette on the window sill.

“It doesn’t matter what type of tricks Excellent Era uses. We have to beat them regardless!” Wei Chen might have been talking to himself. He encouraged himself to not be scared of anything anymore.

At that moment, the door to the practice room suddenly opened. Chen Guo rushed out excitedly and yelled: “It dropped! It dropped!!!”

“Oh? That quickly?” Ye Xiu and Wei Chen were pleasantly surprised.

“Yeah, the quest this time wasn’t as long. The two of them quickly finished it.” Chen Guo said.

“Who got it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Both of them.” Chen Guo said.

“F*ck, that punk is really amazing!” Wei Chen said as he rushed into the practice room. Ye Xiu looked back at Excellent Era and sucked in a deep breath before gently extinguishing his cigarette.

When he walked back into the practice room, the atmosphere was naturally joyful.

The second quest in the guide was fairly short, so the results soon came out. Both Tang Rou and Steamed Bun had obtained a 25 point skill book.

“Let me see, let me see.” Ye Xiu hastily walked over.

“What’s there to see? They already used them.” Chen Guo said.

“I wonder how many people would be jealous if they knew that they got a skill book this easily!” Ye Xiu sighed. Afterwards, he didn’t forget to ask Chen Guo: “How’s it going on your end?”

Chen Guo’s face turned ugly: “I’ve already completed these quests before.”

“That’s too bad, but it doesn’t matter. There will always be more chances later. There will also be some quests that you haven’t done yet too.” Ye Xiu encouraged her.

“I hope so!” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu then asked Wei Chen: “I remember that you said the accounts in your group all had around 4700 skill points, right?”

“Pretty much!” Wei Chen answered.

“The methods that you used weren’t as good as the ones that Concealed Light came up with!” Ye Xiu said.

“But getting drops by chance is never definite.” Wei Chen said.

“That’s true. Have you ever thought of calculating how many possible skill points that could be obtained if everything went your way?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Of course. 1650 skill points.” Wei Chen immediately answered. This number included his many years of work and studying and he was very proud of it.

“Oh, and your friends have around 4700 skill points total. The base number of skill points is 4000, so you got around 700 skill points through these skill books. If that’s the case, then with your original method, your probability of getting a skill book was around 50%.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hey hey, how come everything that comes out of your mouth is so shallow! 4700 points is still an incredible result, okay? Apart from pro player accounts, do you know how many people in the game have over 4700 skill points? With the amount of skill points that our characters have, our characters are worth a lot.” Wei Chen said.

“Then hurry up and sell them. In any case, you guys are blacklisted by the big guilds anyways.” Ye Xiu said.

“Tch, it’s been so long. We fell from their sights a long time ago.” Wei Chen said. This was because of a boss fight. Wei Chen had led his friends and caused chaos amongst the top guilds. Because of this, the top guilds chased after them like crazy. In the end, Ye Xiu had given them the accounts that he had won in a bet, allowing them to continue playing. A long time had already passed since then. It was more than long enough for guilds to forget about them, let alone the top guilds. These Club guilds were very busy. How could any of them have the time to keep chasing down a small team of players? These Club guilds were massive. Everyday, their main guild and branch guilds had tons of problems to deal with. If every single issue was never let go of, the guilds would go crazy.

As a result, once Wei Chen’s group escaped after provoking the top guilds, the top guilds kept one eye open, while keeping the other closed. They might run into each other. If they remember, then they might kill them in the passing, but they definitely wouldn’t send a specialized group tasked with hunting them down.

“Are you still planning on using that Warlock?” Ye Xiu asked.

“The account’s not bad.” Wei Chen said.

“Apart from skill points, what’s the difference between accounts.” Ye Xiu said.

“Their names are different!” Steamed Bun answered.

“Their appearances are different too.” Chen Guo added. She placed a lot of importance on appearances.

“Okay…..” Ye Xiu nodded his head. He didn’t bother arguing because he knew that Wei Chen didn’t care about these areas.

“He he.” Wei Chen laughed evilly.

“How many skill points does your account have?” Ye Xiu suddenly seemed to have realized something.

“He he, which character in Glory has the highest number of skill points?” Wei Chen suddenly asked.

“Han Wenqing’s Desert Smoke, 4880 skill points.” Ye Xiu said. He seemed to know where Wei Chen was heading with his words.

“Correct. Desert Smoke has 40 more points than your One Autumn Leaf, right?” Wei Chen didn’t hurry.

“Right, how many skill points does your character have?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Ha ha, not much. It only has 4920 skill points, that’s all. It has 40 more points than Desert Smoke, 80 more points than One Autumn Leaf, 90 more points than Swoksaar, so my Windward Formation is, in fact, the character with the most skill points in Glory!” Wei Chen said delightedly.

“Your luck is pretty good.” Ye Xiu sighed. Wei Chen’s Warlock must have relied on his method to get all of these skill points. After all, as long as he had luck on his side, even if his method wasn’t as good, he would still be able to get a lot of extra skill points. As a result, while the other characters had around 4700 skill points, he was lucky and got 4920 skill points. Wei Chen’s methods could obtain a total of 1650 points. If one had insane luck, then one could even obtain the maximum amount of skill points in Glory and have extra leftover.

“But there’s still 80 points of room to improve. You’re willing to give those up?” Ye Xiu asked.

“You guys try first. I’ll wait and see before I do anything.” Wei Chen calmly said.

Ye Xiu didn’t urge him. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun continued to quest. Steamed Bun was being supervised by Chen Guo, so Ye Xiu also ran over to try it out for himself.

Lord Grim’s return to the tenth server immediately spread around in Happy. The top guilds were naturally terrified. But after seeing his level and knowing that Lord Grim wasn’t Level 70 yet, they relaxed slightly. Last month, the top guilds already had Level 70 guilds, so they currently held the records for the Level 70 dungeons. Even if the records for the dungeons below Level 70 were crushed, the player base was no longer focusing on them, so the top guilds could tolerate it. However, they then thought of how Lord Grim had casually snatched a wild boss last time he came. This loss was even worse than losing a dungeon record. The top guilds didn’t dare be negligent and informed all of their players: if you ever see Lord Grim, report his actions to the guild.

After nearly half a year, the Club guilds in the tenth server had expanded greatly. Lord Grim’s existence during the initial stages had suppressed them significantly. All of them had suffered at one point. None of them were able to establish their power amongst the new player base until Lord Grim left to the Heavenly Domain. Only then could the Club guilds flip over and start singing. From then on, they could compete without having anyone step all over them.

The more time passed, the weaker the influence Lord Grim had in the tenth server. The top guilds expanded like crazy. As the players played Glory, they began paying attention to the pro scene and had their own favorite team and pro players. Thus, the advantage that the Club guilds possessed finally appeared. They could attract their fans to join. They didn’t need any reason other than their name.

But at the same time, because of this reason, the performance of the team in the Pro Alliance would directly affect their respective guild’s development, especially among the popular mass. The new players had only just begun paying attention to the pro scene, so they didn’t have many feelings for the past glory of the current teams. What they looked at was their current strength at the moment.

Through this reason, Samsara developed rapidly in the tenth server just like their team this season. Many of the new players started watching the Pro Alliance during the later half of the season, which just happened to be when Samsara began dominating the scene after the All Star Competition. Samsara shot up the rankings and their fans increased alongside the team’s growth. Samsara’s guild growth expanded swiftly, completely suppressing Blue Brook Guild, Herb Garden, and Tyrannical Ambition.

The most tragic Club guilds was naturally Excellent Dynasty. When the new players started paying attention to the Pro Alliance, Excellent Era stayed at the bottom until they were beautifully relegated. If someone new like Excellent Era for getting relegated, then that person would be a very strange person. No one in the tenth server had many feelings for Excellent Dynasty.

Chen Yehui had originally planned on making huge movements this season alongside the Club. He made preparations for the guild to shine in the tenth server. At the very beginning, he had sent more experts to help pioneer in the new server than the other guilds. He had wanted to use the opportunity while the new players didn’t know much about Glory to show their guild’s strength in order to attract their attention and establish a solid base. How could he have known that at this stage, he would run into Ye Xiu starting over again in the tenth server. It didn’t matter that he had more experts. Ye Xiu was a God. Chen Yehui had even pulled over Liu Hao to help, but didn’t he also get crushed?

His original plan had been destroyed by Ye Xiu. By the time Ye Xiu stepped into the Heavenly Domain with Lord Grim, the tenth server players now had a certain understanding of Glory and had begun paying attention to the pro scene. With Team Excellent Era’s disgusting performances, when Guild Excellent Dynasty was recruiting players to join, they hated how they couldn’t hide their guild’s name.

Even if the players didn’t know that Guild Excellent Dynasty and Team Excellent Era were related, the other Club guilds like Tyrannical Ambition, Blue Brook Guild, Herb Garden would help spread this type of common knowledge to the player base. Excellent Dynasty’s start in the tenth server had been an utter disaster from start to finish.

Chapter 627 – Assembly Line

The top guilds prepared themselves for Lord Grim’s return to the tenth server. Who knew what evil this God was planning on committing this time. All of the guilds from top to bottom were assigned to monitoring him. They swore that they wouldn’t stop until they figured out what his intentions were for returning this time.

In reality, Ye Xiu was just here to do some quests. Getting involved with the guilds never even crossed his mind. When he arrived back in the tenth server, he still greeted everyone in Guild Happy though.

Without someone as mighty as Ye Xiu watching over them, Happy naturally had no way of contesting the various Club guilds, especially as the influence of the pro teams pervaded their way through the server. In fact, no player guild could compete against these Club guilds. Right now, Happy was developing like a normal guild. People came and left.

Chen Guo still managed the guild. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun could only provide their strength. For the guild affairs, the person who helped Chen Guo the most was the player, Horse Shooter, who had joined because he had been a fan of Su Mucheng. The other player who joined alongside Horse Shooter was Thousand Creations. Even though he was also an experienced player that had been in a top guild before, he was pretty much a lone wolf. He couldn’t be relied on for matters regarding the guild. In the end, he was the same as Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, and could provide some strength when needed.

These four players were the highest level players in Happy. They couldn’t compare to the crazy power leveling of the Club guilds, but amongst the player guilds, their levels were still considered very high. From this perspective, Happy couldn’t compare to the Club guilds, but it was still much more powerful than the other regular player guilds. At the very least, they had a fairly robust guild storage system.

Seeing the guild storage system, Ye Xiu thought of Blue River. He asked Chen Guo about him and found out that Blue River hadn’t logged on in a long time. His smurf’s level had stopped there. When Ye Xiu checked his friends list, of the people he had interacted with, nearly all of his enemies and none of his friends were online!

Ye Xiu didn’t greet them. He just chatted with his guild members in the guild chat while having his Lord Grim head over to the quest locations. Steamed Bun obviously participated in the guild chat. He said even more than Ye Xiu did, boasting wildly about him. Steamed Bun talked about Ye Xiu as if he were an all powerful entity, making Ye Xiu feel embarrassed to say anything in the chat anymore. Steamed Bun didn’t stop and began talking about their team. Returning to the pro scene and winning the championships really was Ye Xiu’s goal, but the problem was that Steamed Bun was brainlessly talking without any basis for it…….

Very few players in Happy were noobs who had just started playing Glory. So when the guild heard Steamed Bun’s words, who would believe him? However, Steamed Bun was quite popular in Happy and many of them understood his personality, so quite a few of them played along, however, Steamed Bun was being serious! As a result, anyone who saw Happy’s guild chat would see it as absolutely ridiculous and that Happy was bragging and exaggerating about their own abilities.

The Club guilds had spies inside Happy. It was just that without Lord Grim, it wasn’t any different from a normal player guild, so they didn’t make trouble for Happy. The various top guilds were busy competing against each other and didn’t have any plans on picking a fight with Happy. After a while, many of the spies stopped logging in, but now that Lord Grim had returned, the circumstances had vastly changed. All sorts of dead accounts suddenly popped up out of nowhere, observing Lord Grim’s activities in the guild

At the same time, the players spread out around the leveling areas in the tenth server and constantly reported Lord Grim’s movements to their guilds.

Ye Xiu wasn’t thinking about any of this. He just went to the quest location, accepted the quest, and then started following the guide.

“He’s doing quests!!” The players monitoring Lord Grim reported to their guilds.

“What quest is he running??” The higher ups asked one after another.

“It seems to be Ambitious Frank.” The reporting players guessed.

Ambitious Frank?

Some of the guild leaders, who heard this quest’s name, knew of it, while some didn’t. For them, if the it wasn’t a quest in a quest chain that helped them level up quicker, they wouldn’t touch it. They might have some impression of this quest, but they didn’t know why they had an impression.

As a result, everyone looked up the quest online. They browsed through numerous related pages to see if there was anything special about this quest.

Page after page after page…...

The links on these pages all explained the quest and how to complete it. It was a very normal quest. There weren’t any secrets involved.

Impossible! It couldn’t be so simple.

The guilds affirmed.

Their analysis wasn’t wrong. Ye Xiu obviously had a very good reason for returning to the normal server to do quests. However, this reason wasn’t something others could think of.

“Keep monitoring him!” The guilds ordered as they continued to search for any mysteries to this quest.

During this time, Ye Xiu smoothly completed the quests. Fighting was troublesome though because the equipment that he had included in the upgrades of Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had been from the Heavenly Domain, so he couldn’t bring it back into the normal server. The naked Lord Grim grabbed some equipment from the guild storage. Ye Xiu was accustomed to using the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, so now that he had switched to a different weapon, it didn’t feel comfortable to use.

The guilds were still trying to figure out this quest’s mystery, when Ye Xiu finished the last part of the quest.

The quest rewards dropped. Ye Xiu checked the rewards and laughed out loud: “I got one.”

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun hadn’t gotten anything from this quest, but Ye Xiu got the 20 point skill book.

This quest had a 34.314% chance of dropping one. For a skill book, this was already an extremely high probability.

It had been ten years since Glory came out and there still hadn’t been a single character with a maxed set of 5000 skill points. One could easily imagine how difficult it was to get skill books. After many years of research, Wei Chen was able to get a batch of characters with around 4700 skill points, but with Ye Xiu’s understanding of Wei Chen, he knew that when he said around 4700 skill points, there were definitely fewer accounts with more than 4700 skill points than accounts with less than 4700 skill points. It might have just been him having crazy luck to get 4920 skill points, while the others might all be below 4700 skill points.

If those were the results, it wasn’t too special in Glory. If someone really wanted an account with 4700 skill points, it could still be bought with money.

But after Concealed Light and his professor cleared up Wei Chen’s efforts, the probability of skill books dropping were even higher now. Even though Concealed Light didn’t say exactly how much the probability went up, with the part that they have right now, it would definitely be higher than Wei Chen’s original method, not lower.

A bunch of characters at that level would truly be the best, even in the pro scene. Let alone the limit of 5000 skill points, anything above 4900 skill points was enough to make all of the God characters kneel. There were quite a few characters in the pro scene with 4800 to 4900 skill points, but there weren’t any with over 4900 skill points.

Currently, building characters with high skill points could only be found through luck, but for Ye Xiu’s group? Through the years of effort from Wei Chen and analysis from extremely intelligent people like Concealed Light and his professor, they suddenly came up with an assembly line. If they manufactured a ton of high skill point characters, the account market in Glory would take a huge hit.

The value of an account was mainly based on its class, equipment, and skill points. The difference between different classes wasn’t much and equipment could always be bought, but skill points were different. If you had them, you had them. If you didn’t have them, you didn’t have them. If these high skill point characters were poured into the market, they would be of the utmost priority amongst buyers. As for other accounts, if they didn’t have equipment that added skill points, they wouldn’t be able to sell. Even if they had the right equipment, they might as well take off the equipment and buy a more powerful account.

Wei Chen’s efforts weren’t just for fun, nor were they just to strengthen his character. He had thought of all of these issues before. However, his results weren’t too stable. Accounts with 4700 skill points weren’t bad for accounts that had been accumulating skill points for ten years, but it wasn’t anything too amazing.

As a result, he didn’t immediately sell those accounts to make money. He wanted to find a more steady assembly line to increase the amount of skill points.

And now it had become a reality. The original goal was to solve the problem of their team’s weak characters, but now couldn’t they also make some money in the passing?

Seeing how Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Ye Xiu continued to easily get skill books, Wei Chen offered this suggestion.

Chen Guo was startled. She had been excited at how their team would have a bunch of powerful characters. She hadn’t thought of making money by using such a method, but she was an experienced player after all. When Wei Chen made the suggestion, Chen Guo immediately understood the opportunity.

“Not only are they extremely valuable, have you ever seen such an account on the market? If one actually came out, there would definitely be a huge bidding war. Of course, as the number of these accounts increase, the price will certainly lower, but don’t forget that we have a complete monopoly over them! The market would be completely controlled by us.” Wei Chen had clearly thought of doing this before and said a whole bunch of stuff.

“In your dreams. The game company wouldn’t let that happen. I feel like they’ll quickly figure out how these characters came about. Then, all they need to do is make some revisions to the code and our method will become useless.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re right! That’s why I haven’t done it yet. I was waiting until this method worked well, so our profits would be maximized. That day has finally arrived!” Wei Chen grasped his fists.

“Then let me ask you, are you planning on creating a team or creating accounts to sell?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chapter 628 – Correct Line of Thinking

“Mm, that’s a difficult question.” Wei Chen felt a bit awkward. In truth, selling accounts with high skill points had been his plan all along. Joining a team and returning to the pro scene was something that he had never expected to do, so when Ye Xiu suddenly asked him this question, Wei Chen had a hard time answering it.

“What I’m saying is that we should do both.” Wei Chen expressed.

“You’re so old already. Are you sure you can do it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Earning money is never easy.” Wei Chen said.

“But right now, we’re at a very important preparation stage. With an opponent like Excellent Era facing us in the near future, are you sure you have time to do both?” Ye Xiu asked.

Wei Chen didn’t say anything for awhile: “How about we…… let it go for now?”

“It seems like to me that you need to be clear about this. Your account business would require a certain amount of time to start up. First, you’d need to find a batch of suitable accounts. If you directly buy a max leveled account, you don’t know which quests they’ve done completed. You would need to ask the sellers for more details and filter out the unsuitable characters. That would be too time-consuming and you don’t even know if you can find characters that suit your needs.”

“If it’s finding suitable accounts, let’s say we look for a studio to power level new accounts for us. In the old servers, it would only take three months or so to level them from 0 to 70 at the fastest. For a studio, the speed and price are dependent. If you require the fastest leveling speed, the initial cost would be much higher……”

“There’s no need to be in such a rush!” Wei Chen said.

“You’re not in a rush? Don’t forget that the Challenger League starts in September. Even though skill points can’t directly be checked through a character’s profile page, by analyzing the equipment and strength of the skills, it isn’t difficult to estimate the number of skill points that a character has. The greater the attention our team receives, the more likely the fact that our characters have high skill points will be revealed. When the secret gets exposed, there will certainly be a huge reaction to it. All the company needs to do is look up our characters and they’ll know that we’ve completely figured out how to earn skill books by following a certain sequence of steps. If that happened, wouldn’t it be too late?” Ye Xiu said.

“This.” Wei Chen paused. Only now did he realize that his account business would conflict with the team’s priorities.

Three months was the shortest amount of time possible to get suitable accounts.

Even after they got the accounts, they would still need to do a bunch of quests to earn those skill points. These quests required a person to run them. The way to do these quests also had to stay a secret too, so they obviously couldn’t have someone else farm for them.

“One more thing. If you want to buy suitable accounts, you can search for a studio and ask for however many you’d like. However, these accounts have special requirements and need to be leveled up at the time of the order. How many accounts are you planning on selling? 1000? There isn’t a studio out there that has the type of manpower to level a thousand accounts in three months. Leveling in Glory requires manually doing it. Leveling an account to 70 in 3 months requires 24/7 non-stop playing. One character would need at least two players. How many studios do you know that have 2000 workers?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Oh right. Three months is the time it takes to level up an account from 0 to 70 using the fastest method. With your special requirements, the quests need to be left blank. Whether or not they can be leveled to 70 in three months is also another issue in and of itself.” Ye Xiu said.

“And……”

“And your sister! Can you shut up for a moment?” Wei Chen interrupted Ye Xiu. He clearly realized that this was an issue and only one choice could be made. Doing both things at once clearly wouldn’t work out.

Ye Xiu didn’t continue speaking. Everyone understood Wei Chen’s emotions right now.

Earning money by selling high skill point accounts had been his goal that he had been striving for all these years. Now they were telling him to make a choice. There was no way he would feel good right now.

“So…..”

“Stop being so noisy. Give me some to think.” Wei Chen interrupted Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu still wanted to say something, but Chen Guo grabbed him. If this guy made a caustic remark right now, it would be too infuriating to see, so Chen Guo didn’t care what he planned on saying and stopped him.

The practice room was very quiet. Even Steamed Bun, who didn’t know what was going on, felt that the atmosphere was heavy, so he stayed silent like everyone else and stared solemnly at Wei Chen.

Wei Chen didn’t stop playing as he contemplated. He continued to tap his keyboard and click his mouse. He looked to be grinding his teeth before finally saying: “Okay! F*ck. This senior has decided not to go into the account business. To hell with it!!”

In the end, Wei Chen still chose the pro scene!

Wei Chen had only been a pro for two years, while these skill points had taken him nearly five years of his life.

For those two years, Wei Chen had carried his dreams with him, while in those other five years, he had carried his livelihood.

Looking at the options in front of him, Wei Chen quickly and decisively came to a decision. In the end, he chose the two short years despite knowing that this attempt might end up in failure again.

“Good, Old Wei is wise! We really can’t afford to go into the account business right now!” Ye Xiu applauded.

“Go to hell! If we don’t win the championships, you’d better compensate this senior for his losses!” Wei Chen cursed.

“Losses? What losses?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I gave up on such a big business opportunity. If it’s not a loss, then what is it?” Wei Chen was furious.

“This business would require a lot of time regardless. It also has high initial costs and isn’t something that can go on for a long time. The company just needs to come out with an update and it will undermine everything you worked so hard for. It really isn’t worth that much.” Ye Xiu said.

“You talk quite deftly!” Wei Chen wasn’t happy.

“I feel like the correct choice is to directly sell the guide.” Ye Xiu said.

“What did you say?” Wei Chen was surprised.

“Sell the guide.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck!” Wei Chen suddenly awoke with a start. He suddenly jumped up, walked around in a circle, and then suddenly turned towards Ye Xiu: “You beast!!”

“Generally speaking, monopolizing the method is the way towards a long term lifeline, but like I said before, this business won’t last very long. The company will break that lifeline, so you might as well just sell the method.” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re right! Why didn’t I think of it before!” Wei Chen yelled.

“If we do it like that, shouldn’t we tell Concealed Light?” Chen Guo asked.

“Oh, of course.” Ye Xiu had a rare expression of seriousness. This incident made him realize the power of intellectuals and naturally made him respectful towards them.

“How do we go about selling it? You’ve probably already thought of how, right?” Wei Chen said.

“The higher the demand, the higher the price.” Ye Xiu said plainly.

“Sell it to the Clubs?” Wei Chen thought.

The Clubs would gain the most benefits from strengthening their characters and would be willing to pay a high price to do so.

For a normal player, a max skilled character would only be able to make that player a bit stronger, but for a pro team, more skill points meant stronger skills, which could be the deciding factor in a match. In addition to that, the amount of profits from winning a match was on a completely different level than a normal player winning a match in the Arena.

“If that happens, everyone will have high skill characters.” Chen Guo sighed.

Originally, their team would have a bunch of 5000 skill point characters, while the highest amount for the other teams would be Tyranny’s Desert Smoke at 4880 points. Wouldn’t that be amazing? However, if everyone had 5000 skill point characters, then there advantage would be lost.

“Making other opponents stronger really doesn’t leave a good taste in my mouth!” Wei Chen sighed as well.

However, his greedy gaze betrayed him. Even though it didn’t leave a good taste in his mouth, he wouldn’t feel bad about taking their money. He soon continued: “But it wouldn’t make them much stronger. Their characters aren’t far from the limit anyways, so it wouldn’t make too big of a difference.”

These words were to console himself. 100 to 200 skill points definitely wasn’t as insignificant as Wei Chen had said it was.

“They might not even be able to use the method. Look how famous the names of those famous characters are? With how valuable those names are, they might not replace those characters.”

Chen Guo said.

These words were also to console herself. God level accounts were famous and they might actually not be replaced just for this reason, but the other characters could be replaced, no? In any case, the strengths of the teams would increase greatly. It would definitely happen.

“Mm, you guys want money, but don’t want others to benefit. You guys are really demanding.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hey, having such desires is a beautiful thing, but we have to accept reality.” Wei Chen expressed.

“But I feel like this won’t be as beautiful as you imagine it will be.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why?”

“If we sell the method to the Clubs right now, my guess is that the Clubs will quickly group together and buy it once for the entire alliance.” Ye Xiu said.

“If that happens, the price will go down.” Wei Chen said.

“That’s why I feel that it’d be better to find one Club and then agree that they directly buy it out. If that happens, the advantage won’t spread to the entire Alliance. The money that we earn might not be lower than if everyone bought it together.” Ye Xiu said.

“You demon. I have to admit you’re a demon. Such an evil idea is something only a demon could come up with.” Wei Chen seemed like he was praising Ye Xiu.

“Then which Club do you plan on selling it to? Blue Rain? Tyranny? Samsara? I think Samsara is a good choice. They’re very ambitious and would probably buy it for the highest price.” Wei Chen said.

‘Samsara is a good choice, but I feel like they might not be the ones who need it the most.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then who?” Wei Chen was puzzled.

At this moment, Chen Guo suddenly jumped up and guessed Ye Xiu’s intentions: “Loulan Slash!!”

Chapter 629 – Why Should I?

“Loulan Slash? The rich guy who formed Team Heavenly Swords and is preparing to enter the Pro Alliance next season?” Wei Chen had kept up with the news, so he obviously knew someone as famous as Loulan Slash.

Last time, Guild Heavenly Justice had a duel of words with the other guilds in the forums and managed to win the support of many players. It was an incident that made even Wei Chen feel jealous.

“Yeah, he’s the perfect target.” Wei Chen thought about Loulan Slash’s background and immediately felt like Ye Xiu’s suggestion was very good.

Loulan Slash had money, but because his team was new, there were still huge differences between his team and the other pro teams that were difficult to make up for with money. Of course, if you insisted on it and recklessly threw money at the problem, then it could still be done. For example, those God level accounts might not necessarily be something that Club owners wouldn’t sell if the price was high enough, but the problem was that if you threw your money without any regard for the costs, it showed that you were planning on using money to solve everything. Outsiders wouldn’t know whether or not Loulan Slash had any plans on doing this sort of move, but no matter the case, Ye Xiu believed that a skill point guide was enough to make his heart thump. This was something that, no matter how much money you had, it wouldn’t be possible to obtain from anywhere else. Ye Xiu would be giving him an opportunity to buy it.

“Hurry up and contact him!” Wei Chen was already impatient.

“More like contact Concealed Light first.” Chen Guo reminded.

“Of course.” Ye Xiu calmly opened chat windows for Loulan Slash and Concealed Light on QQ.

Ye Xiu didn’t ask “are you here?” and left them a direct message saying what he needed to say. For Concealed Light, Ye Xiu told him that they were planning on selling this skill points guide and asked if he had any opinion on them doing so.

Concealed Light had been on the entire time. He had just been invisible. When he saw the message, he immediately replied in bewilderment: “Do what you want! What opinions would I have?”

“Hurry up and do what you want!” Wei Chen impatiently urged.

After Ye Xiu and Chen Guo gave him a disdainful look, Ye Xiu replied: “This guide is very valuable. After all, without your assistance, it wouldn’t have been possible to get it. You have the power to decide what we do with it!”

After Concealed Light read the message, he collapsed in shame: “I actually only did a bit of the work. Without Professor Zhang, it really wouldn’t have been possible.”

“Then shouldn’t we ask him? This has never been sold before, so I don’t really know the price, but seven figures shouldn’t be a problem.” Ye Xiu was worried that someone like Concealed Light, who stayed at home studying math wouldn’t know the value of this guide, so he gave this future mathematician a number.

But Concealed Light replied: “Are you asking me to get reprimanded!”

“What?” Ye Xiu and everyone else was startled.

“Professor Zhang is a world renowned mathematician. He’s never cared about money! Telling him about this would just bother him. Isn’t that just going to make him angry?” Concealed Light replied.

“Then what’s important to him?” Ye Xiu asked.

But the answer made everyone want to cry.

“Scientific development, advancement of humanity.” Concealed Light replied.

“How shameful!” Wei Chen looked up at the sky and let out a deep sigh.

“And we still want to talk about money with him?” Chen Guo was also ashamed.

If you said this to a normal person, that person would definitely think you were joking, but the situation was different. For a scholar like Zhang Yichun, any results that he came out with could be something that advanced mankind, so it really wasn’t a joke. It was a fact that made Ye Xiu and the others crazy.

“Then we’ll deal with it.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Sure.” Concealed Light replied.

“Ai ai ai!” Wei Chen sighed repeatedly at this reply: “Famous scholars truly think differently from normal people! Their minds aren’t something that little people like us can understand. It’s best if we didn’t make trouble for that senior. We’ll just go at it blindly!”

It was a classic example of someone gaining a favor and calling it a disfavor. Everyone gave him a disdainful look, but didn’t say anything because Loulan Slash had replied.

Ye Xiu and Loulan Slash didn’t immediately start negotiating the price. Instead, Ye Xiu asked Loulan Slash how things were going for him.

“We’re busy improving ourselves so we don’t lose face when the time comes.” Loulan Slash replied honestly. Don’t look at how Team Heavenly Swords seemed incomparably confident, laughing at all the Clubs to build up fans. In terms of actual strength, Loulan Slash and his team clearly knew where they were at after several interactions and exchanges with Ye Xiu.

If they hadn’t met Ye Xiu, they might really have taken their arrogant words to the public as the truth.

Fortunately, they met Ye Xiu. They still built their fanbase through their arrogant words, but Loulan Slash didn’t dare to be arrogant over their actual strength. Their team was practicing hard and had lowered their goal by a lot. Before they had met Ye Xiu, they thought that they would be a very competitive team. Now, their goal had been changed to not lose too much face. Others who heard their actual goal might think they were being modest, but Ye Xiu knew that Loulan Slash was being sincere. “How are your accounts?” Ye Xiu asked.

“They’re okay!” Loulan Slash replied vaguely.

“How many skill points do each of your characters have?” Ye Xiu began to move towards the main subject.

Loulan Slash saw the question and was surprised. He took some time to reflect on it. He clearly knew that this God wasn’t chatting with him because he was bored, but because he had a purpose in mind. This sudden question must have something to do with this purpose. Skill points truly was something that Loulan Slash couldn’t do much about. Did Ye Xiu have some way of resolving this problem?

After thinking for a bit, Loulan Slash became excited, but still calmly replied: “Skill points hm? Not bad I’d say. Our characters have been pretty lucky, so we have a lot of skill points.”

“Ha ha, don’t tell me your accounts all have maxed skill points!” Ye Xiu said.

“How could that be! Are there are any characters in the entire game with maxed skill points?” Loulan Slash was probing Ye Xiu, but he was starting to become amazed because he had a feeling as to what Ye Xiu’s intentions were.

“There haven’t been any, but now maybe not!” Ye Xiu said.

“You have such an account?” Loulan Slash questioned.

“It’s very likely.” Ye Xiu said.

“Likely?”

“Mm, because it still depends on luck, so it isn’t completely guaranteed.” Ye Xiu replied.

“What do you mean luck?” Loulan Slash couldn’t pretend any longer. Let alone a character with maxed skill points, there weren’t even any with over 4900 skill points. Characters with 4800 skill points were usually famous stars in the pro scene. It wasn’t by chance that these characters became famous. Having such a high number of skill points was an important deciding factor in these pro games.

The characters used by Loulan Slash’s team didn’t have a low number of skill points. They had between 4700-4800 skill points, which was quite decent in the pro scene, but there was still a gap between their characters and the top characters, let alone a character with maxed skill points.

If you had that many skill points, then that was how much you had. What did it have to do with luck? Loulan Slash couldn’t understand, so he asked this question.

“To tell you the truth, I have a method of getting skill points. The very first thing I thought of was that you might need it. Isn’t that kind of me?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Very kind.” Loulan Slash replied, but he was bitterly laughing in his heart. He wasn’t stupid. He understood what Ye Xiu was getting at. The very first thing Ye Xiu thought of was him. That wasn’t kindness. Ye Xiu clearly wanted his money. However, Loulan Slash didn’t care because he needed it. If someone could provide him with a solution, he would happily take them up on that offer.

After replying “Very kind”, Loulan Slash didn’t say anything else. He wanted to wait until the other side came out with his offer.

But after waiting and waiting, there was no reply. Loulan Slash was sad! He wanted to know the other side’s price and start negotiating from there, but the other side was truly fierce. Ye Xiu pretended like he was dead, putting on a do-you-want-it-or-not appearance.

Loulan Slash wanted to cry. Ye Xiu was telling him that he couldn’t be like this.

Helpless, Loulan Slash could only start the conversation: “What type of method is it?”

“It’s a certain way of completing quests. I can guarantee that there’s a high chance of obtaining skill books as a reward.” Ye Xiu replied quickly. He had clearly been sitting in front of his computer the entire time! He had purposely pretended to be dead, but Loulan Slash didn’t have a choice!

“How new? I’ve never heard of it before.” Loulan Slash had ambitions to flourish in the pro scene and had obviously put a lot of effort into researching skill points, but he had never heard of this method before.

“Of course you haven’t. An old comrade of mine sacrificed much of his youth bitterly researching it before getting these results.” Ye Xiu said.

“I see. What are your plans?” Loulan Slash asked.

“My plan is to see if you have any plans.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Okay!” Loulan Slash said weakly, “Let’s get to the point. If you really can get characters with maxed skill points, then I obviously need them very much.”

“I thought so too.”

“Give me a price. I’ll need nine.” Loulan Slash said.

“Nine?”

“If I need more, I’ll look for you!” Loulan Slash said.

“Why not just directly buy the guide itself?” Ye Xiu replied.

“You’re willing to sell it?” Loulan Slash was surprised.

“Why not?” Ye Xiu asked back.

Loulan Slash replied: “But why should I buy the whole guide? I only need enough characters for my team.”

Chapter 630 – New Goal

Why should I?

When Loulan Slash asked this question, it was Ye Xiu’s turn to become dazed.

Why should I? Ye Xiu had helped Loulan Slash think of a reason, but his reasoning hadn’t matched Loulan Slash’s.

“You’re too polite…..” Ye Xiu replied.

Indeed, Ye Xiu’s side felt like Loulan Slash was being too polite. Why would you not just straight up buy the guide, and instead settle for the next best thing and only buy a batch of accounts?

“How am I being polite?” Loulan Slash didn’t understand. His line of thinking was clearly different from what Ye Xiu had analyzed his thinking to be.

“If you have the guide, you can make however many accounts you’d like.” Ye Xiu explained.

“Ha ha, wouldn’t buying the guide be much more expensive though? I don’t need that many accounts, just ten is enough.” Loulan Slash answered back.

“It would actually be more difficult for us to get those accounts to you rather than give you the guide itself.” Ye Xiu said.

“So you’re saying that if I want to buy it, I have to buy the guide at a high price?” Loulan Slash asked.

“Pretty much.” Ye Xiu said.

“If that’s the case, you’ll need to give me some time to think about it.” Loulan Slash replied.

If he had to think about it, then it meant that he was leaning towards rejecting the offer and only had a bit of leeway remaining. If he was seriously considering it, he would have at least asked for the price. However, Loulan Slash didn’t even ask about the price and had jumped straight to considering it. This wasn’t a good sign for Ye Xiu’s side.

“If this had been us previously, we would have bought it without any hesitation. We would have bought it out too, so that no one else would be able to get it and guarantee our advantage over the other teams.” Loulan Slash didn’t hide his reasons and started discussing with Ye Xiu.

“Then what about now?”

“Luckily we bumped into you! You helped us realize that our original ideas had been careless. With just our skill level alone, we thought we would be able to immediately compete with those powerhouses. We were too ignorant and narrow-minded, so we decided to do things realistically. We’ll first establish a solid position in the pro scene before doing anything. Of course we need characters with high skill points, but any player would want a character like that. The current us isn’t thinking of expending all of our efforts to weaken our opponents. Even if we do weaken them a bit, it wouldn’t change our overall situation too much. Improving our actual skill is the most stable way of improve our chances. We aren’t thinking of doing anything else at the moment.” Loulan Slash was very honest and showed his gratefulness towards Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu read the message and could only force a smile: “Then good luck!”

“Thank you. If you can provide accounts with high skill points, contact me at any time. The price won’t be a problem.” Loulan Slash said.

“Understood.” Ye Xiu replied. He turned around and forced a smile at Wei Chen and Chen Guo. Their first plan had failed. It turned into selling accounts. The price for accounts would still be considerable, but compared to their original plan, it was still a huge difference.

“Then we’re going to give up just like this?” Wei Chen wasn’t willing.

“There’s nothing we can do. His line of thinking is completely different from ours.” Ye Xiu said.

“I can see that. I could also tell that the reason his line of thinking is different is all because of you!” Wei Chen accused him.

“Life is full of twists as you can see.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do we do now?” Wei Chen said.

“It looks like we can only look for another pro team to sell it to.” Ye Xiu said.

“Samsara?” Wei Chen asked.

“The ambitious Samsara is a very suitable target.” Ye Xiu said.

“Samsara will be in the playoffs. We have to hurry up and sell them our guide beforehand. Their price will definitely be a lot higher.” Wei Chen said.

“There are still two weeks. I don’t know if Concealed Light will be able to arrange everything by then.” Ye Xiu thought and looked for Concealed Light on QQ to check how long it would take.

“Hm? Are we in a rush?” Concealed Light asked.

“Yeah!”

“I’ll try to finish it in a week. “Concealed Light estimated.

“Good luck!”

“Time isn’t an issue.” Ye Xiu turned around and spoke, “As long as we can get the guide ready, Samsara can easily upgrade their characters in two days.”

“Then let’s contact Samsara?” Wei Chen asked.

“There’s no hurry! Wait for Concealed Light to finish first and we’ll personally take a trip to City C!” Ye Xiu said.

“Wait, did you not think about an issue!” Chen Guo suddenly interrupted.

“What?” Ye Xiu looked at her.

“If Samsara suddenly won the championships with a bunch of max skilled characters, wouldn’t that attract more eyes towards this method? The game company would definitely notice it. If they saw through the process and came out with an update getting rid of it, wouldn’t that be trouble for us too? The characters that we have now will be upgraded in time, but what about the others? Our team won’t just have these four characters, right?” Chen Guo said.

“Oh, don’t worry about that. Samsara is a pro team and their characters are already quite good. I’m guessing that all of them have at least 4700 skill points. If we give them the guide, we’ll only be helping them push towards that final hurdle. As long as they don’t run too many quests, the game company won’t find out so easily.” Ye Xiu said.

“But what if they’ve already done the quests and have to create new accounts?” Chen Guo had a lot of thoughts.

“New accounts? If it’s a new account, it will take at least three months. Even pro teams won’t be able to go any faster than that. By that time, we’ll have a batch of characters too, so we won’t lose out.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo heard Ye Xiu’s explanation before finally relaxing. In the end, she only sighed: “But that means in the future, they’ll be stronger opponents!”

“Aren’t you looking down on Loulan Slash too much. Won’t they be getting stronger too?”

Ye Xiu said.

“It’s the difference between 1+1 = 2 and 9+1 = 10.” Chen Guo said.

“That’s the reason why Loulan Slash isn’t willing to buy it.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“Isn’t it because of you?” Wei Chen gave him a disdainful look.

“In any case, that’s our plan for now! Once Concealed Light arranges everything, we’ll make a trip to visit Samsara.” Ye Xiu said.

“This time, if you don’t sell it, don’t come back.” Wei Chen said.

Concealed Light’s diligence didn’t need to be said. He said one week, but on the fifth day, he had already completed the guide. He wrote it in a word doc and sent it over.

After receiving the guide, Ye Xiu skimmed through it and checked it every time Concealed Light sent a doc over.

As Concealed Light sent over parts of the guide, Ye Xiu, Steamed Bun, and Tang Rou continued to follow them. The skill points on Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and Steamed Bun Invasion continually shot up. The highest was Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim because Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion couldn’t enter the Heavenly Domain yet, so there were a lot of quests that they couldn’t complete yet. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim ran between the two servers and cleared out all the quests. His skill points rose like a rocket. His level wasn’t max yet, so he couldn’t do some of the high leveled quests yet. However, he already had maximized his potential skill points.

The guide increased the drop chances and Ye XIu’s luck was quite good. Once he got 5000 skill points, Wei Chen became conflicted. His Windward Formation had done all these quests before, so he had no way of improving his character anymore. He didn’t think that Ye Xiu would really be able to get all 5000 skill points.

If he didn’t switch accounts, he would have less skill points. If he switched accounts, his Windward Formation wouldn’t have the chance of rising to the top! It made Wei Chen very depressed.

“I feel like we don’t need to give Samsara everything.”

Ye Xiu inspected the guide and got rid of a portion of it. In the end, he left enough for an additional 1000 skill points.

“Right now, they just need a way to have their characters increase by a level. If I just give them these, it’ll be enough. There’s no need to give them everything.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo supported this idea very much. Chen Guo’s biggest hope was that they would keep the guide to themselves and no one else would have it. There was no other choice though, but it if they could give less of the guide to the other side, that was worthy of being happy about too.

“Then it’ll just be these!” Ye Xiu looked at the remaining content, “I just hope that Samsara won’t have done too many of these quests already! If so, this will be more than enough.”

“Since their base is already so high, if they haven’t already completed these quests, just a little bump should be enough.”

Chen Guo said.

“Listening to you, we should get rid of another 500 points?” Ye Xiu said.

“Good good!” Chen Guo agreed.

‘Okay, you’ve been doing these quests too. How many points does your character have?” Ye Xiu asked.

“280 points.” Chen Guo said sadly.

“280 points and you’re saying it so sadly. I reckon that something like this has only happened in our room.” Ye Xiu sighed and then added: “Out of the 1600 skill points, you seriously only managed to get 280 points? The issue of them having already completed the quests is a serious problem. We should leave them some room for hope!”

Chen Guo listened and didn’t say anything more: “Then when will you be going?”

“The sooner the better!”

“I’ll take a look at the tickets there.” Chen Guo said. These sorts of expenses were naturally paid for by the boss.

“Do you know who to look for in Samsara? You’d better not get kicked out of the place immediately.” Wei Chen said.

“If you went, you would definitely get kicked out. How could I be like you?” Ye Xiu retorted.

“Will the plane tomorrow morning be okay?” Chen Guo checked the ticket and called out.

“Sure.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“What’s your ID number?”

Ye Xiu sent over his ID number on QQ to Chen Guo, who quickly finished up the rest of the preparations.

Chapter 631 – Visiting Samsara

The city’s temperature in May was neither high nor low, and the air was humid and comfortable.

However, Ye Xiu was the type who stayed indoors for long periods of time, so his reaction towards the difference in the climate was quite slow. He didn’t realize that there was any change. After arriving from the plane, he called for a taxi and went straight to Club Samsara, not even stopping at the hotel beforehand.

The unsuccessful trade with Loulan Slash caused Ye Xiu to be much more careful with the upcoming discussion. After discussing the issue with Wei Chen and the others again and again, they came to the conclusion that Samsara had no reason to reject their offer. Their intentions on becoming the champion this season was very obvious. It could be seen from their marketing during the two week break before the playoffs.

It was impossible for them to reject this guide for skill points. The only possibility was that they might refuse to buy it out completely. As for this problem, Ye Xiu had been discussing it with the team these past few days. If they didn’t buy it out, it meant they would be letting Ye Xiu go to another team to sell the guide. If that were the case, then Samsara wouldn’t have any advantage over the other teams. After thinking about it over and over again, everyone felt that the possibility of Samsara buying it out was the highest out of all the teams.

Ye Xiu would arrive at Club Samsara soon. Of course, he wasn’t planning on breaking through their front entrance. After all, he couldn’t use his face as a pass. Wei Chen’s worry wasn’t for nothing. He had a high chance of being driven out by the security guards before even entering.

Ye Xiu made a call from a public telephone booth outside the Club and then paced back and forth in front of the entrance. Not long afterwards, a person jogged out from within the Club building and glanced around outside the gate. When Ye Xiu waved towards him, that person hurried over.

“Long time no see.” The two greeted each other.

Tong Lin, an ex-pro gamer of Glory, was currently employed at the Club. He had retired three years ago and worked in Samsara Club’s technology department.

The professional circle for Glory wasn’t too big. There were around 200 people total. In the initial stages of the professional scene, the scale had been even smaller. There weren’t even 20 teams and not all the teams had ten people, so at that time, there were even fewer people, so the pro gamers were much more familiar with each other. Ye Xiu had been in the scene from the very start until now, so it was evident that he knew everyone in it. It was just a matter of how deeply he knew everyone. Some people he only nodded his head at, while some he could chat well with.

Tong Lin belonged to the latter.

Although he wasn’t a God, his love for Glory wasn’t any less than any other pro. After retiring and joining the technology department, he continued to work diligently and tirelessly. Ye Xiu contacted his old friend for his trip to bring in his message and enter the gate. Tong Lin was far from having the influence to make any decisions in the trade though.

As the two chatted, they walked through Samsara’s entrance. With Tong Lin there, the security guards by the door didn’t ask any questions. When Ye Xiu had previously been walking around the entrance, they had cautiously kept an eye on him. After all, the playoffs were coming up. They couldn’t risk distracting the pro gamers, who were vigorously preparing and training for the upcoming competition. The Club’s work requirements in various departments had become much more strict these past few days.

“What business do you have here? You were so secretive on the phone.” Tong Lin asked as he guided Ye Xiu along.

“It’s definitely something good for Samsara.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha, what good could you possibly bring to Samsara?” Tong Lin laughed.

“You’ll know when I show it to you later.” Ye Xiu said.

“Alright!” Tong Lin didn’t ask any further. He directly brought Ye Xiu up to the Club’s third level, which was where his office in the technology department was located.

“Tell me! What are you going to show me? I’m waiting!” After telling Ye Xiu to sit down, Tong Lin smiled.

“You have spare Glory account cards here, don’t you?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Would you believe me if I said no?” Tong Lin spoke, “What class do you need?”

“The class doesn’t matter, but the fewer quests completed, the better.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“We haven’t been keeping track of that.” Tong Lin said.

“Then just give me any two!” Ye Xiu said.

Tong Lin opened the drawer and randomly grabbed two account cards.

“Is here okay? Or do you want to head for the lab?” Tong Lin asked.

“Lab?” Ye Xiu laughed.

“That’s what everyone calls it. It’s a force of habit now.” Tong Lin explained.

“Here is fine!” Ye Xiu stood up and walked over. Tong Lin immediately stepped away from the computer and left the two cards there.

“These two accounts are yours or?” Ye Xiu casually picked one up and asked.

“Mine.” Tong Lin said.

“Then how lucky of you.” Ye Xiu smiled.

Tong Lin was still confused as Ye Xiu quickly logged onto the game. Ye Xiu didn’t care about what Tong Lin’s character was called, which server, which class, or what equipment he had. Ye Xiu only checked the character’s location and immediately looked up a direction to run towards while asking Tong Lin: “Do you still remember what sort of tasks this character has completed?”

“This…… I don’t really remember.” Tong Lin said.

“Then I’ll just try a few!” Ye Xiu said.

“What on earth are you trying to do?” Tong Lin asked.

“Don’t worry. You’ll know soon enough.” Ye Xiu kept him guessing without revealing anything. He controlled Tong Lin’s character, while sprinting towards a place that he remembered that had one of the select quests.

After talking to the NPC with the quest, it seemed like Tong Lin hadn’t completed this quest before.

After seeing Ye Xiu accept the quest, Tong Lin hurriedly moved closer to look: “Which quest is this?”

Ye Xiu opened the quest’s panel for Tong Lin to see the quest’s name.

Tong Lin looked at it and tried to recall this quest in his head, but he couldn’t remember anything odd about this quest. He then watched Ye Xiu continue to play. He followed the quest chain and completed it step by step.

“You came here to help complete quests for my account?” Tong Lin laughed.

“Don’t get so worked up yet. What’s worth the excitement has yet to come.” Ye Xiu said.

“What are you trying to do? Stop hinting and just tell me!” Tong Lin was getting anxious!

However, Ye Xiu didn’t hurry. In actual fact, he was afraid of making mistakes. After all, this had to be done precisely according to the calculations that Concealed Light and his mentor had made, so he couldn’t be careless.

“Pay attention!!” At last, the quest had reached the last stage when Ye Xiu immediately called out to Tong Lin.

“I’ve been paying attention this whole time!” Tong Lin said from the side.

After clicking the character, the task was completed and a row of congratulatory words flashed by. Ye Xiu wasn’t let down. The skill book was rewarded. The task he chose to show obviously had a high succeeding rate. For this particular quest, after being analyzed over and over by Concealed Light and his mentor, they had found that there was a 57.258% chance of a skill book being dropped upon completion.

For skill books, a percentage like that was high enough to scare a person to death.

“Skill book!!!” Tong Lin was patient and had been paying attention the entire time. The reward that flashed by didn’t escape his eyes. He clearly saw these two words. He immediately realized that the skill book must have been what Ye Xiu had been hiding from him the entire time. Apart from this, there was nothing else to see.

“A skill book with 25 skill points, how about that? Aren’t you excited?” Ye Xiu started to open the inventory of Tong Lin’s character. A 25 skill point skill book was laying there.

“It wasn’t a coincidence?” Tong Lin’s mind started to churn.

“It was a coincidence, but the same time, it wasn’t.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“Stop with the suspense and mystery! Just tell it to me directly!” Tong Lin yelled.

“It’s a coincidence because the skill book isn’t guaranteed. It wasn’t a coincidence because I used a method for a skill book to have an increased chance at dropping. If not for me, I don’t know how many times you would have to complete this mission in order to receive this reward.” Ye Xiu said.

“Stand aside and let me see!” Tong Lin pushed Ye Xiu aside and controlled his character. He checked the inventory once again and confirmed that it was a skill book without a doubt. He scrolled through the records and confirmed that this skill book, was in fact, the reward from the previous task.

Soon afterwards, Tong Lin checked a website and found the quest. In the end, he couldn’t pick out any related information that connected the quest to a skill book.

“Don’t waste your time. We were only able to get this thanks to an old friend’s many years of research.” Ye Xiu said.

“Who?” Tong Lin hurriedly asked.

“Wei Chen.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“It’s that guy!” Tong Lin was also a pro gamer from the older generation. How could he not know the former captain of Team Blue Rain?

“What you’re saying is that he found a special way to complete certain quests that give a chance for a skill book to be rewarded?” Tong Lin was in the technology department, so he figured it out quite quickly.

“Correct.” Ye Xiu nodded.

“How high is the drop rate?” Tong Lin asked.

“Around 50%!” Ye Xiu said.

“How did you come up with this number?” Tong Lin asked.

“I might scare you to death by telling you the truth, so I shouldn’t tell you.” Ye Xiu said.

Tong Lin rolled his eyes: “If you don’t say it now, someone else will definitely ask about it later.”

Tong Lin was a senior figure in the industry. After figuring out how it worked, he immediately had a rough prediction of Ye Xiu’s intentions upon visiting Samsara.

“We have an outstanding student with us. He used his mathematical knowledge and whatever to calculate this. You know that we wouldn’t be able to understand that kind of stuff. In any case, we listened and did as we were told. We don’t have the ability to perform large scale tests to confirm the drop rates. If you’re interested, you can perform these tests at a later time. Don’t you have a ‘lab’ or something?” Ye Xiu said.

“The drop rate isn’t actually too important. What’s important is its effectiveness. Do you know what I mean?” Tong Lin said.

“I understand.” Ye Xiu smiled calmly: “I believe that it’s effective.”

“It only has a 50% chance of being rewarded. As long as it’s not 100%, then it could prove to be ineffective.” Tong Lin said.

“But this is only one quest, you wouldn’t think that I would only take one task and excitedly run to Samsara to sell just this, did you?” Ye Xiu said.

“Then how many do you have?” Tong Lin asked.

“If you add all of the tasks together, it’s worth an additional 1000 skill points!” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck!” Tong Lin’s eyes went wide. In the next second, he rushed over and grabbed Ye Xiu, fearing he would run away: “Go, go, go, let’s go!”

“Go where?” Ye Xiu deliberately asked.

“Where do you think?” Tong Lin didn’t answer the obvious.

After dragging Ye Xiu out of his office, he went down from the third floor to the second floor and walked to the end of the building.

Midway through, they passed the practice room. A Samsara pro player was holding a cup of water and was walking loitering near the entrance of the practice room. When he saw Tong Lin come over, he naturally recognized him and politely called out “senior”. Tong Lin smiled and nodded, while he was grabbing onto a guy tightly as if he had caught a robber. That guy being grabbed was even walking in a weird way as a result. That guy also smiled and gave him a nod.

Who was this guy? Why did he answer me when I said “senior”? He seemed really familiar. Was he a waiter at a restaurant?

The pro player didn’t say anything, but he made a lot of guesses. Suddenly, he remembered who that person was. The surprise caused his hand to tip. The boiling water in the cup spilled out and the burn immediately caused him to loosen his grip.

“Pa!” A crisp sound was made as the cup shattered. The pro player was at a loss. He was still gazing at the silhouette that was being dragged away by Tong Lin.

After hearing the sound, Ye Xiu and Tong Lin turned back to take a look. After seeing that it was just a broken cup, they continued to walk. On the other hand, when the other pro players inside the practice room heard the noise coming from outside the door, they all came out to see what had happened. In the end, they only saw a pro player standing stupidly outside the door.

When they realized that it was only a cup being broken, everyone was about to leave, but before leaving, they saw the pro player lift his right hand and point at the silhouette that had already turned around the corner: “Ye…… Ye Qiu!!”

“What?” The pro players didn’t hear clearly.

“Ye Qiu. It’s Ye Qiu! I saw Senior Tong Lin dragging Ye Qiu away just a moment ago.”

“Senior Tong Lin, dragging Ye Qiu?” All the pro gamers were stupefied. As for Tong Lin, they obviously wouldn’t find anything strange with him, but Ye Qiu! Why would this guy appear at Samsara at this time? Their gossipping spirits had been kindled.

“Which way did they go?” Vice-Captain Jiang Botao asked.

“That way.” The pro player pointed.

“The manager’s office?” After turning that way in the hallway, there was nowhere else to go apart from the manager’s office.

“Let’s go have a look?” Jiang Botao turned his head and spoke to Zhou Zekai. They were the captain and vice-captain. At this age, only those with some status would be able go and have a look.

Zhou Zekai didn’t say anything yet, when the practice room phone rang. A pro player hurriedly ran over to receive it. He said a few words before hanging up. He ran over to Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao: “Captain and vice-captain, the manager is asking for you two to head over.”

Jiang Botao and Zhou Zekai looked at each other in the eye. Everyone thought that it had to be related to Ye Qiu’s visit. The two were prepared to go, when the phone rang again. The same person ran over to receive it, he hurriedly dashed out again to face Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao: “The manager says to bring your account cards with you.”

“Bring our account cards?” “What for?” Everyone made wild guesses. Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao didn’t understand, but nevertheless, they returned to the practice room and grabbed their accounts cards with them.

“Please enter!”

After knocking on the manager’s door, they heard the manager’s voice and entered. The manager wasn’t sitting in his office chair. In the guest sofa, he and Tong Lin sat there with another person in the middle.

“I don’t need to introduce them to you, do I?” The manager laughed.

“It’s Little Zhou and Little Jiang! Haha, you two are doing pretty well this season!” Ye Xiu smiled as he greeted the two.

Chapter 632 – One Man Team

“Hi God Ye.” Jiang Botao greeted back. Zhou Zekai simply smiled in a friendly manner. He looked as if he wanted to say something, but in the end, he remained silent.

“Little Zhou still doesn’t like to speak, ha ha!” Ye Xiu laughed.

Everyone looked towards him, but Zhou Zekai still didn’t say anything and just continued to smile.

Truthfully, someone who wasn’t good at expressing one’s thoughts like Zhou Zekai wasn’t suited to be the team captain. If he was even had a hard time greeting someone, giving words of encouragement to his team at crucial moments would be impossible, but even though he wasn’t a good speaker, he wouldn’t lose to anyone in terms of skill.

Zhou Zekai was currently considered the number one player in Glory right now by many. His skill and technique were the real deal. His performance on stage was filled with energy. It could be said that once he took control his character, the aura he gave off completely changed. No one would think that the person controlling such a stylish character would be so quiet in real life.

Whether or not he really was the best player in the Alliance was still up for debate, but if it was the difference between his playstyle and his real self, then no one would be able to contest with Zhou Zekai.

Through his performance on stage, Zhou Zekai was still someone who the team greatly relied on. They knew that even if their team captain didn’t like to speak, he would never disappointed them on stage. They just needed to match his pace and they would do well.

The tactics and strategies used by professional teams usually revolved around their team’s core player, but no other team relied on their core player as much as Samsara did. Their reliance on Zhou Zekai won their team the nickname “One Man Team” in the Alliance.

That had been true up until Jiang Botao became Samsara’s vice captain.

Samsara’s playstyle had completely revolved around Zhou Zekai, but because Zhou Zekai didn’t like to speak, his teammates would often have trouble understanding his actions, which affected their past records. However, Jiang Botao understood Zhou Zekai very well. He could accurately read the purpose of every single one of Zhou Zekai’s actions, so he became the bridge between Zhou Zekai and the rest of the team.

Samsara’s “One Man Team” style didn’t disappear. However, because of Jiang Botao, the synergy between Zhou Zekai and the rest of the team improved significantly. Samsara burst forth and many believed that they had the highest chance of becoming the champions in this season. Samsara restrained themselves the entire time. The nickname “One Man Team” was not a compliment, but through their success, they hoped to prove that “One Man Team” wasn’t impossible and erase the ridicule that was implied by the name.

Samsara thirsted to become the champions, so when Tong Lin brought Ye Xiu over to the manager and gave a brief introduction to what Ye Xiu had in his hands, the manager hastily called over the captain and vice-captain. He wanted their two strongest accounts to personally try it for themselves.

Ye Xiu saw the manager give them a call and tell them to bring their account cards. He figured out his intentions, but he didn’t stop him. When he saw Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao enter the room, he greeted them and then smiled towards the manager: “Are you trying to take advantage of me! I don’t even know if you’re going to buy it or not, and you want me to give them skill points?”

“Ha ha ha.” Samsara’s manager: “If what you say is really true, then even if you wanted to leave, you wouldn’t be able to. I’ll make you spill the beans even if I have to murder you.”

This was obviously a joke, but everyone could feel his determination. Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao were still puzzled as to what was going on. In the end, Jiang Botao asked: “What is it?”

“Skill books.” Ye Xiu answered.

“Skill books?” Jiang Botao still wasn’t sure what was going on.

“One thousand skill points worth of skill books. How many skill points does your ‘Empty Waves’ have?” Ye Xiu smiled.

Empty Waves was Jiang Botao’s character. It was the number one Spellblade in Glory and a character that Excellent Era’s Liu Hao envied the most. These characters had a difficult time getting any additional skill points, so it wasn’t any secret. Jiang Botao quickly answered: “4820.”

“If your luck is good, that number can potentially be 5000. Now do you know what I’ve brought with me?” Ye Xiu smiled.

Jiang Botao’s eyes went wide. Zhou Zekai also revealed an astonished expression. They obviously knew the importance of skill points, but at the same time, they knew even better how difficult it was to find skill books.These things couldn’t be traded.

“Shall we try it out with ‘Empty Waves’”? Ye Xiu suggested to the manager.

“Sure sure.” The manager hastily nodded his head. Tong Lin had explained it to him before. Even though he knew that Tong Lin wouldn’t come over and say such a thing as a joke, he still had a hard time believing it, so he wanted to see if it was true for himself.

Jiang Botao received the manager’s approval and handed over ‘Empty Waves’ to Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu used the manager’s computer and logged into the game. The manager, Tong Lin, Zhou Zekai, and Jiang Botao stood behind Ye Xiu.

He logged into the game and moved the character around. Ye Xiu asked Jiang Botao if he had finished the quest before. Jiang Botao naturally had no idea. No one could remember every single quest that their characters had completed, even more so for pro characters. The person using the account might not have been the one to level up the account themself.

“We’ll see then!” Ye Xiu also gave it a try like he did with Tong Lin’s character.

“So you’re saying that if this quest has been completed before, there’s no way of getting the skill book?” The manager quickly found the key point.

“Of course.” Ye Xiu said.

“If that really is the case……”

“Then you can only blame your bad luck.” Ye Xiu sighed.

Empty Waves was an All Star level character. It wasn’t Tong Lin’s private account. Once he logged into the game, he walked through the streets and the news quickly spread in the global chat. Countless players reported his whereabouts and the guild Samsara was chattering nonstop about Empty Waves as well. His friends, as well as strangers, repeatedly sent him messages. They gave him words of encouragement, expectations, etc. for this character, who would soon be participating in the playoffs.

“Wow, you’re very popular, huh.” Ye Xiu continued to move towards the quest location as he gazed at the chat.

The people behind him didn’t care about all this. It wasn’t anything new that a scene like this would occur whenever a pro character logged into the game, let alone an All Star level one like Empty Waves. So when Ye Xiu gave this remark, the others gave a laugh absentmindedly, but didn’t say anything further.

Soon aftewards, Ye Xiu reached the NPC giving the quest, but when he spoke to the NPC, the NPC didn’t give any response. Ye Xiu turned his head in regret: “Too bad. You’ll never get the chance to get this 25 skill point book.”

Jiang Botao had pretty much figured out what was going on. When he heard Ye Xiu say these words, he felt very sad too. However, Ye Xiu’s first few words gave him hope: “Didn’t you say there were 1000 skill points?”

“I pray that your character hasn’t done all of the quests!” Ye Xiu said.

“All of them are quest rewards?” The manager asked a second question.

“Yes.” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Everyone fell silent and continued to watch Ye Xiu move Empty Waves to the second location. The NPC still didn’t reply back.

Ye Xiu turned around and looked at Jiang Botao: “20 more points gone.”

“45 points!” Jiang Botao began calculating. There were originally 1000 points total, but 45 points were gone. He calculated how many points he had left and felt reassured. He only needed 180 points. There were 955 points left! No problem!

Jiang Botao thought like this. Ye Xiu already found the third NPC. This time, the quest prompt popped up. Ye Xiu accepted the quest. Jiang Botao immediately knew this time was good and became extremely excited.

Ye Xiu followed the steps according to the guide. The four people behind him didn’t take their gaze off the screen. They didn’t dare to breathe loudly. Finally, the final part of the quest chain came. Tong Lin had already seen this happen before and felt excited. He tapped the manager’s shoulder, telling him to watch carefully, but when he handed in the quest, the words that Tong Lin had anticipated didn’t come. The manager was somewhat puzzled. He looked questioningly at Tong Lin, but then he saw Ye Xiu say to Jiang Botao: “You’re really unlucky! This quest should have had a 63% chance of getting a 20 point skill book, but you actually didn’t get one!!”

“So…… that’s how it works?” Jiang Botao was depressed.

“So from the sounds of it, even if you finish the quest, it isn’t guaranteed that you’ll get the skill book?” The manager found the key point again.

“Then what’s the probability of getting skill points out of these thousand points worth of skill books?” The manager asked.

“Around 50%. In other words, if the quests haven’t been done. With the foundation that your accounts have, getting the max 5000 skill points shouldn’t be too big of a problem.’ Ye Xiu said.

“How did you get the number 50%?” The manager asked.

“It was calculated, but don’t ask me how it was calculated in detail. I can’t tell you. Even if I could, I doubt you’d be able to understand. This was a number that a specialist came up with.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then how can we believe that this number is reliable?” The manager asked.

“Take Empty Wave’s account and see if you can get to 5000 skill points?” Ye Xiu said.

“Sure!” The manager nodded his head.

“You wish.” Ye Xiu objected. He took out an account card from his pocket and waved it at them: “Let me open your eyes!”

He logged into the game and without doing anything else, Ye Xiu clicked open the skill tree and pointed at the right corner of the screen.

They obviously knew what was in this position. They saw that the number of skill points on this character was an impressive 4920!

Chapter 633 – Deadlock

4920!

Even though it wasn’t the maximum 5000 points, it was shocking enough already. This random account in Ye Xiu’s hands had already broken the 4900 point zone that had never been broken through before.

“As for your characters? True gold never fears fire. These quests will certainly improve the skill points on your characters, but my one fear is that your characters will have already done most of the quests. If that’s the case, there’s nothing I can do for you. From the looks of it, Little Jiang’s Empty Waves isn’t the case! Little Zhou, has your Great Gunner cleared any of these quests?” Ye Xiu said.

“No.” Zhou Zekai shook his head.

“What do you think?” Ye Xiu asked, “Don’t count on me trying out these quests on all of your accounts. If I do that, the skill points on your characters will probably go up. When that time comes, wouldn’t that be a huge loss in profits for me?” Ye Xiu said as he looked sympathetically at Jiang Botao: “Your luck is really bad. Even if this deal didn’t go through, your character could have gotten a 20 point skill book for free. Unfortunately, only Old Tong benefited.”

“God Ye, you’re being too suspicious! If it really works, how could we not want it?” Samsara’s manager kindly said.

Ye Xiu heard the implication in his words and smiled: “So right now you’re hoping for some concrete proof, right? After all, you heard me say 60%, but that number doesn’t seem too reliable. It looks like this 4920 character still isn’t enough proof in your eyes!”

“Ha ha ha…….” Samsara’s manager laughed without explaining himself. This had clearly been what he meant. Ye Xiu never said how he managed to get the skill points and only showed the results. It wasn’t very convincing at all. The 4920 point character was astonishing, but Glory had such a large player base and it had been so many years. Who could say whether there was a character with such high skill points out there? Samsara’s manager had seen the account card. It was a second edition card, which meant that it had been issued when Glory’s second server opened. If an old account like this account had extraordinary luck, it wasn’t impossible for it to have an incredible amount of skill points.

But just like he said, if this method truly worked, Samsara would absolutely buy it, but because they would definitely buy it, the value of this method would not be low. He had to be careful before closing a large business deal such as this one.

“If that’s the case, you can keep on thinking about it. I’ll be leaving.” Ye Xiu logged out, grabbed his account card, and got up. Samsara’s manager looked at him in alarm. He was actually just going to leave? Did he not have any intentions on marketing his product? But after thinking about it again, he quickly understood that Ye Xiu didn’t need Samsara to buy it. If he brought this method to any other Club, who wouldn’t want to buy it? Thus, Samsara’s manager thought up another issue: how many Clubs had this guy already talked to? Did the other Clubs already have a team of 5000 skill point characters by now, while they were hesitating?

If that really was the case, then they had to buy it no matter what! Thinking about this issue, there was no way Samsara’s manager could sit still. Ye Xiu hadn’t even taken two steps yet, when the manager stopped him. Seeing the manager move, Tong Lin and Jiang Botao naturally helped him persuade Ye Xiu. Zhou Zekai also wanted to help, but this sort of situation was even more challenging for him than participating in the playoffs. He walked around the other four in circles, but he couldn’t find an opportunity to say anything.

“God Ye, there’s something that I have to know.” Samsara’s manager said.

“What?”

“Have any of the other Clubs bought this method yet?” Samsara’s manager asked.

“How can I answer that?” Ye Xiu answered back.

“See….. the price is very different depending on whether or not this method has already been bought by other Clubs, don’t you think?” Samsara’s manager explained.

“Ha ha ha, if you say it like that, of course no one else has bought it yet.” Ye Xiu happily replied.

This reply made Samsara’s manager want to cry: “Are you telling the truth or not?”

“I didn’t say anything, but you had to ask. When I gave you an answer, you didn’t believe me. What am I supposed to say? Why don’t you just act like it has already been bought by others and give a starting price from there?” Ye Xiu said.

“So no one else has bought it?” Samsara’s manager was very careful.

“I’m going!” Ye Xiu threatened.

“Don’t be in such a hurry! Let’s take some time to talk about it! It must have been a long trip here. Have you eaten yet? How about we get some food?” Samsara’s manager started firing sugar-coated bullets.

“Ha ha.” Ye Xiu chuckled, “Sure, I’d be willing to stay and eat. I’m not in a hurry, but you guys should be! If you get more skill points, wouldn’t you need to do some research on how to distribute these new skill points? Wouldn’t you need to try out the newly leveled skills and get used to them? Do you even have the time to eat with me? How many days is it until the playoff match?” Ye Xiu said.

Samsara’s manager listened and thought it was reasonable. Even though he wasn’t an expert in Glory, he was the manager of the Club, so he still understood this sort of general knowledge.

Thus, Samsara’s manager grit his teeth: “Okay, let’s sit down and talk.” He had wanted to carefully probe the situation, but they were on the passive side from beginning to end. There was nothing he could have done about that! The bargaining chip in Ye Xiu’s hands was something that couldn’t be refused!

Buy out!

Once they started talking about the deal, Samsara’s manager wanted to head in this direction, but the bargaining chip in Ye Xiu’s hands was too valuable. The price for buying it out certainly wouldn’t be low. Even worse, what could they measure the price against?

If a character didn’t have a solid base like their pro characters, 1000 skill points worth of quests wasn’t enough to max out the skill points, but even if the character didn’t have a solid base, a character that surpassed any of the pro characters could still be created through this method. What the price should be was something Samsara’s manager wasn’t sure about either.

As a result, he didn’t give a price for now and instead tried to feel out Ye Xiu’s intentions. At the same time, he would tell the boss about this deal. The buyout price would be very high, but it was completely necessary, so he needed to let the boss know about it.

After negotiations officially began, Zhou Zekai and Jiang Botao left. Tong Lin didn’t participate either. This sort of deal required a certain amount of secrecy.

Because the seller absolutely needed to buy it, Ye Xiu held the advantage in this negotiation. As a former pro player, he had a strong mental fortitude. He was calm and unhurried, making it difficult for Samsara’s manager to handle. Take advantage of Ye Xiu? Samsara’s manager didn’t have any thoughts about doing so. Right now, the other side was currently showing reluctance towards his plan to buy out the guide.

“I suddenly feel like I made a mistake.” Ye Xiu suddenly said.

“What is it?” Samsara’s manager was a complete mess. Ye Xiu’s sudden comment confused him.

“I should have gathered all the Clubs together and auctioned it off!” Ye Xiu’s words were terrifying.

“Ah!” Samsara’s manager was frightened. Even though this wasn’t an easy negotiation, they at least had the advantage over the other Clubs! If it really had been auctioned, Samsara’s resources weren’t any better than any of the other powerhouses. It was hard to say whether they would be able to get it or not if that were the case. What’s worse was that for an auction, the winner wasn’t necessarily the richest, but who had the courage to stake thousands of pieces of gold in one throw. Samsara’s manager couldn’t help but think of a powerful opponent.

Tyranny!

Correct, Tyranny. Club Tyranny was currently the Club, which was the most willing to spend money. If this guide was auctioned off, it was likely that Tyranny would rely on their great courage and take the guide for themselves.

“God Ye, how about you give me a price! We can negotiate from there!!” Samsara’s manager wanted to cry.

In truth, Ye Xiu felt the same as the manager! He didn’t know how much this guide should sell for either. After all, he was just a former pro player. This deal with Samsara would very likely help Samsara win this year’s championships. It could also affect their future momentum in the pro scene as well. There were many ways to measure the worth of a character. It wasn’t something that could be measured with just a few words. Ye Xiu wasn’t sure how high of a price he could sell it for.

If he had created this guide all on his own, Ye Xiu wouldn’t care too much about selling it for the highest price possible, but the problem was that this guide had been created through the many years of effort of Wei Chen and then completed through Concealed Light’s help. From the start to finish, Ye Xiu hadn’t made a single contribution to the guide itself. If he had to split the money, he would only take a very small percentage of it for closing the deal. However, as the person responsible for closing the deal, wasn’t it his duty to sell it at the highest price possible? As a result, even though both sides had confirmed their intentions, they still hadn’t reached a conclusion. The two of them kept on probing each other for a price all the way until it became dark, but nothing came out of it.

Chapter 634 – Final Test

“God Ye, would you like something to eat?” Samsara’s manager was exhausted as he lay down on the sofa. After hearing his stomach growl a few times, he thought of getting dinner.

“Oh, sure!” Ye Xiu replied indifferently. At the same time, sounds of tapping could be heard.

Hm?! What’s this?

Samsara’s manager suddenly realized something. This was clearly his office. Why am I sitting on the guest sofa, while the guest is sitting in my chair and using my computer?

He’s using my computer?

He’s using my computer!!!!

Samsara’s manager suddenly leapt up. How could his computer be randomly used by an outsider? There were Club secrets stored inside! He strode over and went to his computer. When he looked, he almost fainted.

The other side wasn’t searching for Samsara’s secrets. He was using his computer to play Glory! How long has he been playing?

“Lord Grim…… oh…… you’ve been famous ever since the tenth server opened!” Samsara’s manager saw the name and made a comment.

“Ha ha, thanks.” Ye Xiu said.

“Level 66, tsk tsk. Leveling truly isn’t easy, huh.” Samsara’s manager said. Lord Grim was an unspecialized character. He couldn’t level past 50 unless it was done in the Heavenly Domain. As the Club’s manager, he didn’t need to be concerned about these bits of information about the game, but the people in his social circle often talked about things like this.

“Yeah, it truly isn’t easy.” Ye Xiu sighed.

“It looks like another God-level character is about to be born.” Samsara’s manager remarked.

“Ha ha.” Ye Xiu laughed, but didn’t deny it.

“How many skill points does your character have?” Samsara’s manager suddenly asked.

“That’s a secret. I can’t let you know so easily.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Haha, you’re already treating us as your opponents?” Samsara’s manager said.

“Already? Haven’t I always?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Alright…… I guess so……” Samsara’s manager said and then suddenly shifted topics: “It looks like you and Excellent Era aren’t on good terms anymore! For something as important as this, the first thing you did was contact us instead of contacting Excellent Era.”

“That’s not hard to understand, is it?” Ye Xiu said.

“It isn’t.” Samsara’s manager nodded his head. He knew exactly why Ye Xiu would think of Samsara first.

“If we just keep sitting like this, I feel like we won’t ever get anywhere.” Samsara’s manager said.

“Be more decisive! Give me a price!” Ye Xiu said.

“Why don’t you be more decisive?” Samsara’s manager was gloomy.

“Because I’m not worried……” Ye Xiu said.

“Fine!” Samsara’s manager was helpless. Ye Xiu didn’t have any other tricks. He was fully utilizing the few advantages that he had. It truly was the mark of a pro God.

“How about this! It’s quite late. You’re probably tired too, so go take rest! I’ll give you a definite answer tomorrow.” Samsara’s manager replied.

“Like that, ah……”

“Do you have a place to stay? If you don’t, we can arrange one for you.” Samsara’s manager said.

“No need. I’ll come over again tomorrow then.” Ye Xiu said as he got up. The two had been in a deadlock for the entire day, but no conclusion had been reached.

When Ye Xiu left, Samsara’s manager immediately contacted his boss and gave a report about the situation. After receiving the boss’s approval, he immediately contacted the various department heads in the Club and held a meeting that night.

They never set up a meeting time, so once Ye Xiu had gotten enough sleep, he tidied himself up and walked over to the Club once more. Chen Guo had arranged the hotel ahead of time and since she knew that Ye Xiu would be going to Samsara, she obviously picked a hotel close to it.

Samsara’s manager had been waiting for Ye Xiu to arrive, but he looked quite tired. It seemed like he hadn’t slept well the previous night.

“How are things going?” Ye Xiu smiled. He had guessed why the manager had told him he would have a definite answer the next day. The manager must have held a meeting right after he left and thoroughly measured the value of what Ye Xiu had brought.

“Two things. First, quest list. It shouldn’t be a big issue if you only provide us the quest names, right? Second, how you got that drop rate. We still hope that we can see some concrete proof.” Sure enough, the manager’s efforts yesterday night weren’t for naught. Samsara had found a reasonable price for it, but they needed to clarify some things first.

The manager’s talk with Ye Xiu yesterday afternoon wasn’t a waste of time. Samsara’s manager understood how he got these 1000 points of skill books. It was through a manipulation of small details in the quests. Just a list of names shouldn’t be an issue. And as long as Samsara knew the names of the quest, they could check their characters to see which quests they had already completed. Then, by knowing the drop rate, they could approximate how many skill points they could obtain. Of course, they would also need some concrete proof of Ye Xiu’s supposed drop rates before doing so.

“Alright!” Ye Xiu had expected this. Soon afterwards, he took over the manager’s computer and opened two files from his email.

The first file was how Concealed Light had calculated the drop rate. Ye Xiu didn’t understand it, but someone in Samsara probably had the ability to do so and check if it was real or fake.

The second file was a list of quest names.

After finding these two files, Ye Xiu also gave a requirement: “Since you’re going to test it, I want to be able to watch them do it. Will that be a problem?”

“Not at all.” Samsara’s manager didn’t object.

He printed out the two files. Samsara's manager looked at the data and felt his head hurt. He and Ye Xiu went over to the technology department and handed it over to one of their experts. As for the quests list, he printed out another 11 copies and wrote the name of a Samsara character onto each of them. The eleven pro account cards had already been prepared for testing.

Samsara’s employees began checking the quests for each of the characters.

This caused a huge commotion in Glory. The message soon reached the ears of the other teams, who heard that Team Samsara had all of their characters wandering around in-game that morning. Their footprints included places in the normal server and Heavenly Domain. All of the characters stayed on for around the same amount of time too.

The playoffs were about to begin. Samsara wasn’t busy practicing and instead running to the game to wander around? And it was the entire pro team too. What was going on?

The players in-game were talking fervently about it. The pro teams were also at a loss. Team Samsara had a good chance of winning the championships and were naturally formidable opponents. No one dared to underestimate them. What was going on?

Because these characters were just wandering around, they didn’t follow the same steps. It was hard to see if a character was talking to an NPC, so no one could figure out what they were doing, but their movements couldn’t be without any meaning, especially right before the playoffs. Thus, the only possibility was that Samsara’s characters were being strengthened.

This was a unique aspect of an eSports based around an MMO.

If a character wanted to be strengthened, they had to do it under the same skies as everyone else. Since Team Samsara’s characters had run to the game in such a critical time period, what else could they be doing?

However, they couldn’t figure out why.

These eleven characters didn’t even do any quests. The data for the drop rate had been analyzed already. There weren’t any problems with it.

After verifying which quests had been completed, as well as the drop rate, Samsara could calculate how many skill points they could potentially obtain.

Without considering luck and only based on the data, of Samsara’s eleven characters, five of them could reach 5000 skill points, while the remaining six would be around 4960 points. With good luck, it was obviously possible that all of them or none of them would be able to reach 5000 skill points.

Ye Xiu saw these results, but didn’t say anything. This was a very good result. Besides not having enough money, Ye Xiu couldn’t think of any reason for why Samsara wouldn’t buy it.

Was it possible for them to figure out how to do the quests through the data for calculating drop rate? Ye Xiu had asked Concealed Light about this and found out that it wasn’t possible. Concealed Light had only been able to come up with this data after going through Wei Chen’s experimental data. Without Wei Chen’s experimental data, with just this data and the quest names, it wasn’t possible to figure out the method for it. If not, Ye Xiu wouldn’t dare to hand over this data to them. Wouldn’t that be the same thing as handing over the guide?

Once the results came out, Samsara’s manager and Ye Xiu left the technology department and returned to his office.

“15 million RMB.” Samsara’s manager gave the starting price. The previous test was a double-edged sword. If the results weren’t good, Samsara could lower the price, but after confirming everything, Samsara was now at ease. They would get what they paid for.

15 million was without a doubt a buyout price. If it wasn’t a buyout, it wouldn’t be so expensive. The competitive scene in Glory had developed for several years. Business deals for transferring a character or a player from one team to another were done in the millions. A business deal over ten million was a first in Glory’s history. However, this deal would not be made public.

Chapter 635 – 20 Million

(TL: Money amounts are in RMB: 1 RMB = 0.14 USD)

15 million!

Ye Xiu had a mini-heart attack when he heard this number, but he didn’t let his eyebrow twitch even the slightest bit. As a person who was familiar with the professional scene, he obviously knew what this price meant in the Glory circle.

As a matter of fact, the development of Glory’s professional scene had still been relatively short. When negotiating player transfers from one team to another, they seldom used money. The Clubs tended to prefer trades.

A pro player for a pro player.

A character for a character.

Or a pro player for a character.

A pro player with their character for a powerful character.

There were all sorts of ways to deal with such matters. As long as both sides felt that they would not lose out, they traded however they liked. Monetary exchange for a player or character only started to appear in more recent years, once the Clubs started to flourish. This was because many people had come to realize the potential of these Clubs in the market, whether it was as an investment or for signing contracts for sponsorships. These gave Clubs an increasing amount of profits. This was when Clubs began buying and selling with money.

So far, the player with the highest transfer price in Glory was Sun Xiang. He had joined Excellent Era for seven million this season. Character transfers were on a much smaller scale. God characters were all passed down starting from when the Club first formed and had never moved from their nests before, so they usually weren’t up for trade. There were a few that had been traded in the initial stages of the Glory professional scene, but that was because when the early Clubs could no longer continue operating, they had no choice but to sell one of their characters to stay afloat. It was still during the early stages of the scene and the prices were much lower, so it was insignificant to bring up the prices.

Now that the professional scene had stabilized, teams that possessed god-leveled characters wouldn’t be weak, let alone nearing the point where they could no longer continue operating, even for a disaster like Excellent Era, who had relegated.

Although no one had ever traded God characters, it didn’t stop people from discussing their value.

As of now, many people saw the glorious Battle God One Autumn Leaf as the number one character in Glory. It was generally believed that, if you didn’t put up at least 10 million, then the offer wouldn’t even be looked at.

Apart from this, those who had titles such as the King of Fighting, Sword Saint, or Great Gunner were all top tier characters of Glory, so it was reckoned that they were also worth around 10 million.

However, their estimated value remained an estimate. If it really came to the time to trade, everyone would negotiate. In the end, their transferring price might not match up with their market price. Everyone was clear about this point. In any way, everyone only estimated for fun, but those prices also, to a certain point, reflected the character’s status in every player’s heart.

15 million! It was generally acknowledged in Glory that if one offered this amount for any God character, the other side would need to give back change.

Was Ye Xiu’s skill points for Samsara really worth more than a God level character?

Samsara had been discussing how much these skill points were truly worth all last night. 15 million, was what the manager concluded from last night’s discussion.

He had given the opening price, what would followed next was Ye Xiu’s response.

As for Ye Xiu? His expression remained unmoving. He was also weighing this number in his mind.

He had nothing to measure against for this trade, but with his identity as a God, he had a rough estimate of the price too.

If all the characters in the team had an increase in skill points, which skills would they strengthen? What sort of advantages would they gain in the upcoming competition?

If there was one more God-level character on the team, what sort of change would that produce? What sort of improvement would it create?

The profits made from winning the championships and the attention that God-level characters brought to the team had to be considered! Ye Xiu wasn’t sure about how the price of such things were measured, but in terms of an increase in competitive strength, Ye Xiu was an absolute expert.

If it was only these few, Ye Xiu felt that 15 million was a good price.

So Ye Xiu nodded, just when the manager let out a breath, Ye Xiu spoke: “15 million, you’re not buying it out, right?”

The manager of Samsara was just about to relax and take a sip of tea, but ended up spitting it back into his cup. He nearly spat two mouthfuls of blood into the cup as well.

“Are you kidding me?” Samsara’s manager was getting anxious.

You could negotiate nicely if you wanted to raise the price! How could you say that this price isn’t worth buying it out? That was simply robbery.

“I think that it’s still too little for a complete buy it out.” Ye Xiu spoke unhurriedly.

The manager of Samsara realized that he lost his composure just then, so he calmed down and placed away the tea cup and said: “Then what is your price?”

“30 million!” Ye Xiu said.

If they weren’t familiar with each other, Samsara’s manager would have kicked him out of the place.

Last night, they had conducted an all night meeting and carried out a complete check on how they could benefit from this trade. After considering the benefits and risks, 30 million would only be considered if it were absolutely guaranteed.

What was an absolute guarantee?

If they bought it with a 100% chance of winning the championships, then 30 million was definitely an acceptable price.

That kind of guarantee wasn’t possible, so 30 million was also impossible.

“Come on, God Ye. Let’s go over this together.” Samsara’s manager said. He was determined to clearly reveal to Ye Xiu what 30 million stood for, so this bluffing guy would feel ashamed.

However, Ye Xiu didn’t intend to hear his explanation. He only sighed with regret: “What? Is that no good?”

“Of course not!” Samsara’s manager spoke without needing to think, “This thing won’t guarantee that we will win the championships! And even though the data is real, it still depends on luck! What if we have really bad luck and fail to receive any skill books even after clearing all the tasks? Even 15 thousand would be a loss, let alone 15 million!!”

“How could you say such unlucky words? Are you a spy?” Ye Xiu said.

“I was just giving an example……” Samsara’s manager didn’t know whether to cry or laugh, “Fine, that was a bit too extreme. Then, let’s say that our skill points go up similar to what you showed us previously. I’m sure you’re very clear as to how much that would improve the team’s strength. If we take that improvement and convert it to what would be required in character trades, what would that amount be? If you’re not too sure about the current market, I can show you, for example……”

“Alright, alright, you don’t have to tell me. I have to admit, 30 million was a joke.” Ye Xiu said. Samsara’s manager was just about to let out a sigh of relief, when Ye Xiu continued on with his sentence: “But you also have to admit, 15 million is also a joke.”

“How can 15 million be a joke!” The manager for Samsara was anxious, “I’ll show you the calculations.”

“Why are you always trying to calculate? Did you spend all of last night calculating this?” Ye Xiu said.

Samsara’s manager was startled. He hadn’t needed to say it out loud, but they actually did spend the whole of last night calculating this…...

“We’re professionals in this industry, no? If we really were to figure out who’s right and wrong, do you really think 15 million is actually reasonable?”

“How is it not reasonable?” Samsara’s manager said worriedly.

“22 million!” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” Samsara’s manager was startled.

“If both 30 million and 15 million are considered as a joke, then take the middle, which would be 22.5 million , but since I’m a generous person, I’ll let you keep 0.5 million, which makes it 22 million!” Ye Xiu said.

“You’re saying that 22 million is more reasonable?” The manager asked.

“You don’t think it’s reasonable?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Not at all!!” The manager said.

“Why don’t we find someone else to evaluate this for us?” Ye Xiu suggested.

“Find someone else to evaluate this?”

“For example, Tyranny, Blue Rain, or Tiny Herb.” Ye Xiu said.

“......” The manager was starting to panic. He was very annoyed at Ye Xiu’s pressure and needed to dispute a bit more: “Each team has their own situation. They might have cleared all the tasks for their characters in the team, so if you take that to them, it might not be worth a penny at all!”

“Worth less than a penny? Are you kidding me? Keeping the other teams from using this couldn’t be worth less than a penny. Anyone would buy it out. No matter what, buying this out would only bring you benefit and no harm. Take you guys as an example. Do you guys need the skill points? No, what you guys need is an advantage. Buying this out would automatically give you an advantage. For this, you would naturally need to give more.” Ye Xiu said.

“22 million is too much.” The manager said.

“Then what do you think?” Ye Xiu asked.

“18 million.” The manager was finally letting go of the price for 15 million.

“21 million!” Ye Xiu said.

“Do you have any point in doing this?” The manager didn't know whether to cry or laugh. This was a big trade we’re talking about. Could we not bargain bit by bit like how you would at a flea market? Every little bit was in the millions. If you wanted to change the price you have to give a reason. If there wasn’t a solid reason, who would be willing to give away a few million?

“Fine, fine, 20 million. I know this is an acceptable price for you.” Ye Xiu said.

“20 million……” The manager was a little gloomy.

In actual fact, 20 million was a sum that matched their calculations, but no one would reveal their upper limit right at the start. They had to start with a lower price, so they decided on 15 million. In terms of the negotiation, the manager originally had quite a lot of confidence. This was because he thought that Ye Xiu would only be clear about how much the skill points could improve their team’s strength. In terms of the other benefits produced by the result of the upgrade, even a manager like him couldn’t simply weigh it all out, let alone a former pro player like Ye Xiu.

He thought that if he explained it to Ye Xiu, he would easily convince the latter into thinking that 15 million was a reasonable price. Even if it didn’t work, he could handle with an addition of one or two million.

Who would have thought that Ye Xiu would refuse to listen to his explanation and only argue about 15 million being too little? Ye Xiu had even threatened him with 30 million and the other teams. The manager wasn’t useless. He could tell that Ye Xiu himself wasn’t too sure what the amount should be and how to measure it either. He must have realized instinctively that 15 million must have been lower than their bottom line, so he found reasons to lift the price up. He was daring and wasn’t afraid of making a fool of himself. He rose the price violently, treating the 15 million like 15 yuan and just multiplied it by two.

The manager’s face was filled with tears! He felt like he had lost in terms of being too reserved and lenient……Why didn’t he just shamelessly offer 5 million in the beginning?

“20 million…… then let’s make it 20 million……” The manager nodded helplessly.

Chapter 636 – Final Resolution

Samsara agreed on twenty million. However, Samsara’s manager had a request. The twenty million wouldn’t be paid all at once. Five million would be paid in advance, while the other fifteen million would be paid monthly over 24 months.

The total number seemed to be fixed, but there could still be ways around it. Ye Xiu had to try and fight for it. With the number already agreed upon, the two sides were much more relaxed. You give in a little bit, I give in a little bit and so on. In the end, Ye Xiu was able to get eight million in advance and twelve million paid monthly over the next 12 months.

After the negotiation finished, Ye Xiu suddenly had an idea. He asked if he could use a portion of the money to be paid in materials from the game. Samsara’s manager brightened up at this proposal, but when Ye Xiu listed his requirements, the manager shook his head.

No way. If it were normal materials, perhaps they could discuss it, but nearly all of the materials that Ye Xiu had asked for were only dropped from wild bosses. If these materials could be bought, Samsara’s manager would have easily spent that twenty million to buy what they could. The only reason that they would sell their materials would be if Samsara lost their ambition to win the championships, but with Samsara’s current momentum and resolve, how was that a possibility?

So when he heard Ye Xiu’s proposal, the manager immediately rejected it. When the manager proposed enormous amounts of materials that could be found in dungeons, Ye Xiu also refused. He shook his head just like what Samsara’s manager had done towards his proposal.

One was a manager, one was a pro player. Neither of them were stupid. Both of them knew that the value of dungeon materials and wild boss materials were on a completely different scale. Dungeon materials could be easily bought if one had money, but wild boss materials were difficult to buy even if one had the money for it. This negotiation was different from before. Previously, Ye Xiu had something that Samsara needed, so he had the advantage. With the overall deal finished, small arguments over minor details wouldn’t stop the deal from being renegotiated, so most parties would slowly discuss the following matters. Samsara didn’t have the time though. After buying the method, they needed to immediately use it and upgrade their characters. They didn’t have much time left until the playoffs, so the manager didn’t dare delay any longer over small details.

From his observations, when Ye Xiu had rejected the dungeon materials, Ye Xiu had shook his head, but he hadn’t been too resolute. So after talking about it for awhile, the two sides began figuring out how to trade the materials for money. They obviously wouldn’t be going according to market price. Ye Xiu tried to lower the price, while Samsara’s manager naturally wanted to raise the price. The manager talked about all sorts of troubles that Samsara was going through. He sounded as if they would be out on the streets if they went with Ye Xiu’s prices.

Ye Xiu obviously wouldn’t trust him. He hard-heartedly fought back, occasionally reminding the manager that Samsara was busy and didn’t have time. If not, he would threaten the manager by asking about the storages for Tyranny, Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, etc and ask whether or not they might take the offer.

Samsara’s manager listened to him. Ye Xiu was being so shameless! The two sides had already agreed on the deal, but they hadn’t officially signed anything yet, so he was playing the back out card! Ye Xiu was saying it to his face too! Shouldn’t he feel embarrassed!

However, Samsara’s manager had a certain amount of confidence in this deal for materials. Don’t look at how Ye Xiu was constantly telling them that they needed to hurry. The manager also knew that Ye Xiu was in a hurry too. Since he planned on building a team from scratch, he needed materials very badly. They wouldn’t be able to enter the pro scene with a bunch of Purple and Orange equipment. Wild boss materials couldn’t be bought, but researching self-made equipment also required lots of dungeon materials. Even though dungeon materials could be readily bought with money, Samsara’s manager was certain that as long as they gave a price lower than the usual market price, Ye Xiu would be tempted.

The manager’s analysis was correct. After going back and forth for awhile, Ye Xiu didn’t continue to persist. He also knew that if he traded dungeon materials in this deal, he would be saving a lot of money in the future. As for whether or not these materials would have a lower value in the future, Ye Xiu didn’t care. His job wasn’t to invest in the material market. After taking these materials, he would be using them and he needed to use them immediately. There was no time to wait for the prices to rise or fall.

In the end, Ye Xiu and Samsara’s manager agreed upon a trade of two million RMB for dungeon materials. Ye Xiu gave a call and had Wei Chen send them a copy of their needs, whether it was for his Death Hand or other self-made equipment requirements.

The copy that Wei Chen sent over also had wild boss materials, but Samsara wouldn’t budge on this point. Ye Xiu could only erase them.

Because it was just for dungeon materials, the amount of materials traded for two million RMB wouldn’t be a small amount. After talking about it for awhile, they finally reached a deal. The exact amount of money wasn’t definite yet, but Ye Xiu had gathered together his requirements. After giving the list of materials over to Samsara’s manager, the manager handed it over to the specialists, who gave an estimate for the materials according the manager’s prices. After doing some rounding, they finalized the amount that they would receive for two million.

When Ye Xiu saw these huge quantities of materials being traded without Samsara even blinking an eye, Ye Xiu was inwardly surprised at Samsara’s resources. Their explosive growth this season wasn’t without reason.

The other details took another half day to finalize. That night, the two sides drew up a contract and signed their names. Once Samsara arranged to transfer over the advance, Ye Xiu finally relaxed. He downloaded the guide from his e-mail and handed it to Samsara.

“Tsk tsk tsk……” Samsara’s manager personally inspected the goods to make sure that the quest list Ye Xiu had given them was the same as in this document. When he saw that they had spent twenty million for this document, the manager sighed repeatedly.

After inspecting the list, he had the specialists verify the content with the drop rate data that Ye Xiu had provided beforehand. This wasn’t an easy task, but it was necessary. The contract had a stipulation, meaning that if the guide didn’t match the drop rate data provided, Samsara had the right to adjust the price accordingly.

Because of this clause, Ye Xiu couldn’t help but feel nervous, waiting for the confirmation. If Concealed Light had made a silly mistake and somehow messed up a digit or two, it could be troublesome, but when he thought of Concealed Light’s diligence, he managed to calm himself down a bit.

This examination took place all night. Samsara’s manager deserved to be in the gaming industry. He didn’t have any problems staying up all night with Ye Xiu to watch over it.

Finally, at 4:37 AM, the data verification was completed. There were no mistakes. Samsara’s manager shook Ye Xiu’s hand. The largest deal in the history of Glory had officially concluded. It was only a pity that this deal wouldn’t be announced to the public. From here on out, Samsara had full authority to do what they wanted with the guide. If Ye Xiu wanted to use it, he would need Samsara’s permission too. Of course, Ye Xiu had guaranteed that it wouldn’t restrict their team’s strength. He had stressed this and Samsara also understood, so they didn’t have any overly excessive demands. They just made sure that Ye Xiu would not be able to sell this method to anyone else.

“It’s been a long day. Let’s get some rest. Come over tomorrow afternoon. We should host a feast for you!” All of the issues had been resolved. Samsara’s manager naturally loosened up. He didn’t immediately kick Ye Xiu and instead maintained his cordiality.

“There’s no need for that! I’ve got to hurry and return as well. I will have to come back anyways sooner or later.” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha, that’s true. I hope that time comes soon.” Samsara’s manager said.

“I’ll see you then.”

“You don’t want to stay for dinner?”

“No need!” Ye Xiu waved his hands and left Samsara.

When he walked out of the elevator and turned around to look back. There were quite a few rooms still lit. Ye Xiu reckoned that Samsara would be staying up all night to upgrade their characters. When Samsara’s players woke up, they would have characters with skill points unrivaled in the Alliance.

Seeing how Samsara was spending the night working, he guessed that knowledge of the guide wouldn’t be passed down to the pro players. After all, pro players moved teams. Even if they signed a non-disclosure agreement, it was still another potential source of uncertainty. It would be better to simply keep the knowledge from spreading to as little people as possible. As for what Samsara was planning on doing with this in the future, Ye Xiu didn’t know either, but he was certain that Samsara was well aware of the issues with this guide. The reason that they bought it out was for their goal of becoming champions. Ye Xiu didn’t think that Samsara would use this guide as a money-making tool.

Only studios would think of using it for profit. The Clubs were at the top in terms of making money. Those below them were making far less too.

A player or character transfer easily went into the millions and with how fast the scene was growing, it wouldn’t be long until it broke into the tens of millions. The characters in the Alliance relied on the existence of the game, but because of the Alliance, the value of these characters far surpassed those of normal game accounts. The Glory Alliance was a brand name even higher than the game itself.

When Ye Xiu returned to the hotel, he bought a plane ticket home. That night, Ye Xiu returned to Happy Internet Cafe. He went to the practice room and saw everyone gathered there. Seeing Ye Xiu return, everyone quieted down.

“How much money did we get!” Wei Chen’s voice was dry and rough. Ye Xiu had been in touch with them these past two days. They obviously wanted to know the results, but Ye Xiu wouldn’t tell them. This was because the deal hadn’t been completely closed yet, so Ye Xiu didn’t want to get their hopes up. In order to prevent them from having their worlds turn from heaven to hell, Ye Xiu had kept it a secret. He would finally reveal the price to them now.

Chapter 637 – A Large Sum of Money

(TL: Money is in RMB. 6.9 RMB : 1 USD)

The practice room was silent. No one ever thought that they could ever have too much money, even someone like Steamed Bun.

Everyone looked nervously at Ye Xiu in anticipation. Ye Xiu slowly poured himself a cup of water to drink, took a sip, then grabbed a cigarette from his pocket and slowly lit it…...

“If you don’t spit out the answer, I’m going to kill you!” Wei Chen had been anxious all day. When Ye Xiu finally returned, he kept on stalling. How could Wei Chen not be furious?

“2 million worth in materials.” Ye Xiu calmly answered.

“2 million…… materials?” Wei Chen’s face twisted in disgust. To put it plainly, did Ye Xiu even have the right to split the earnings? Of course not. This was considered Wei Chen’s goods. Concealed Light would have a much greater split of the earnings than Ye Xiu. All Ye Xiu did was run errands. It would be nice of Wei Chen to even give him a share. Wei Chen obviously wasn’t planning on keeping the money for himself. However, it seemed like Ye Xiu only cared about himself and traded his years of effort for a bunch of materials. It was clearly for the team to use, but Wei Chen still didn’t feel comfortable.

Even though Ye Xiu had contacted him asking about what materials he needed, he had expected something like this, but he didn’t think Ye Xiu would be so aggressive. 2 million! In materials…..

Even Chen Guo felt Ye Xiu had been too excessive, when she heard Ye Xiu’s response. This guy seemed to take Wei Chen’s things as his own and only thought about his own interests! If it was just a small amount, it didn’t matter, but this was 2 million they were talking about!

But things had already gotten to this point. Wei Chen was a grand person. Two million? In the end, he laughed: “Ha, that much materials should be more than enough for us to use.”

“Enough my ass. They’re all dungeon materials. They refused to give us any wild boss materials.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck! Just because they won’t give any, doesn’t mean they won’t sell any. What the f*ck were you doing!!” Wei Chen heard this, he had a hard time enduring it any longer. They spent two million, but didn’t even get any of the materials he urgently needed. Ye Xiu had done a real sh*t job this time.

“You you you…… sigh…….” What could he do though? Wei Chen could only sigh. He had given Ye Xiu full authority to settle this deal and he was very unhappy with the results, but he felt bad saying anything. In the end, he could only sigh with regret.

Chen Guo couldn’t stand it any longer and was ready to ask a few questions. Was he planning on selling these materials for money? He wasn’t going to use all of the materials, right? Even though, Chen Guo didn’t call Ye Xiu out for being so despicable, she didn’t feel happy either at only getting materials.

“Apart from materials, they’re also paying us six million in advance.” Ye Xiu said indifferently.

“What?” Wei Chen had been shaken up by the results, but after hearing this piece of news, he suddenly became excited again.

Chen Guo, who had also been about to say something, froze. She heard it clearly and didn’t need Ye Xiu to repeat it. She suddenly felt gratified. Ye Xiu hadn’t just gotten materials. Six million!

“You really are quite capable!!!” Wei Chen grinned widely and gave Ye Xiu a strong slap on the back.

At this moment, Tang Rou noticed the words that Ye Xiu had specifically used: “Six million is just the advance?”

Wei Chen stared blankly. Six million was already enough to make his head spin. There was still more to it? Wei Chen stumbled backwards and held himself up using the table. He was afraid he would faint.

“Yeah. There’s also another 12 million that will be paid monthly over the next year. That’s it.” Ye Xiu finally took out the contract. Wei Chen grabbed it and flipped through it madly. He didn’t care about all the clauses and what not. He just kept on flipping it, while mumbling: “Where where? Where does it talk about the money?”

Wei Chen wanted to verify that this number was correct.

Ye Xiu had drawn up the contract line by line with Samsara, so he was obviously very familiar with it. He went over and found the line talking about the payment. Wei Chen’s eyes sparkled, when he saw the startling number. He yelled out: “Oh my god. F*ck me.” and went back to collapse in his seat.

Chen Guo, Tang Rou, and even Steamed Bun were shocked.

Two million in materials, six million down payment, and another twelve million paid over the coming year. The total value was twenty million! They knew that that the guide would be bought for a considerable amount of money, but who would have thought that it would be such a large amount? Chen Guo kept up with the competitive scene and had previously been an Excellent Era fan. Sun Xiang’s transfer for seven million had been the highest ever seen in Glory, but now, this guide was worth almost three times as much as a God. Chen Guo couldn’t help but raise her eyebrows. In any case, as long as it was better than Excellent Era, Chen Guo would be happy. A bigger number making her happy was a mark of her mentality as a fan. As a team manager, whether it was spending or earning money, it was all a business strategy. There was nothing to be so excited about.

“In two days, the down payment should arrive. Starting from next month, they’ll be paying us one million every month. The money will be transferred directly to your bank account. Okay, have you got any more questions?” Ye Xiu said.

“Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!” Wei Chen laughed wildly as he continually patted Ye Xiu’s shoulder.

“This guy’s already gone crazy.” Ye Xiu hastily ran away.

Chen Guo felt gratified too. Such an insane deal was definitely something to be satisfied with. As for how Wei Chen was planning on splitting the money, no one had the right to ask. If he wanted to invest in the team, that would be obviously be great. If he didn’t want to, they didn’t have any right to say anything. Chen Guo could only remind him that he shouldn’t forget about Concealed Light! If Concealed Light hadn’t helped, would they have been able to get this deal?

Ye Xiu also agreed. If they didn’t have Concealed Light’s precise drop rate data, even selling it would have been an issue in and of itself. After all, Wei Chen’s previous data had been a complete mess. If they had given it to Samsara to look at, Samsara would ask what the drop rate was and he wouldn’t even be able to give a definite answer. When Samsara had inspected the goods for their exact value, if it was Wei Chen’s original data, it wouldn’t even be possible to test it.

If Samsara couldn’t verify the value, it meant that there was an unknown risk and the price would certainly be much much lower.

“Of course.” Wei Chen showed his spirit of loyalty. Even though he acted shameless, he would never act in such a way for important business.

Twenty million! Concealed Light wasn’t an internationally-renowned mathematician, why would he refuse? Wei Chen messaged Concealed Light in the group chat. At this moment, Steamed Bun came over, sized up Wei Chen, and commented: “Who would have thought Old Wei was so smart! To think you could casually earn so much money.”

“Ha ha ha ha, ha ha ha ha.” Wei Chen laughed madly.

“In the future, I won’t fight over who will pay the bill.” Steamed Bun expressed.

“Who’s going to fight for it. I’ll pay!” Wei Chen replied magnanimously.

At this moment, Concealed Light replied. He saw that it wasn’t Ye Xiu, but another team member. Concealed Light was surprised and carefully greeted Wei Chen.

“Scientist! Thank you very much! That guide sold for 20 million! Tell me! How much do you want?” Wei Chen said.

“Oh? That much! Amazing!” Concealed Light replied. Because they were talking online, they couldn’t tell if he was excited or not from his words.

“Without you, we wouldn’t have gotten so much.” Wei Chen said.

“No way. I didn’t do anything. I just organized everything.” Concealed Light said.

The two talked for awhile, but it seemed like Concealed Light didn’t care about the twenty million and insisted that he didn’t contribute anything to the guide, so he didn’t have the right to any of the money.

After talking back and forth, Concealed Light refused to budge. Wei Chen couldn’t do anything about it. He wanted to give Concealed Light money, shouldn’t that be an easy thing to do? It was a huge number like twenty million too. Even if it was just one percent, two hundred thousand was still a good amount of money.

“This scientist is so enlightened…….” Wei Chen couldn’t persuade Concealed Light. Later, Concealed Light explained that he should tell his professor about it and see what his professor said.

No one had any objections, of course. Soon afterwards, Concealed Light went offline.

That night, Wei Chen didn’t go back to the apartments to rest. He stayed up all night in the practice room. He was too excited to sleep.

The next day, Concealed Light came back. He had asked Professor Zhang, who said he didn’t need any money. He didn’t seem to care that he had helped them earn such a huge sum of money. He just hoped that Wei Chen would use this money appropriately.

“Use it appropriately…….” Wei Chen studied Professor Zhang’s words and asked everyone: “Is he telling me to use it to help run the team?”

F*ck! There was no saving him. Professor Zhang clearly wasn’t talking about funding a professional gaming team, when he said to use it appropriately.

“Innovation!”

“The advancement of mankind!”

Everyone reminded him that this was what Professor Zhang meant.

Wei Chen heard their responses and froze. He never imagined that he would ever do anything related to “innovation” or “the advancement of mankind”. How was he supposed to do that? Wei Chen felt vexed. It seemed like he was about to have another night of insomnia. Ye Xiu sighed: “Don’t think about it from a scholar’s perspective. Just do what you think is appropriate! He just hopes that you don’t waste your money on worthless things.”

Chapter 638 – Guarding Against the Unexpected

Wei Chen glanced at Ye Xiu. Wasn’t Ye Xiu basically telling him to use the money to finance the team? How shameless, but then again, he would just be making a fool of himself if he attempted to get into things like “innovation” or “the advancement of humanity”. Helping the team had been his original intention all along. This time, he would be financing his dream, so Wei Chen would happily to do so.

“Ahem, we need to hurry and improve the strength of our characters right now.” Wei Chen cleared his throat and spoke. With the money in his pockets, his tone of voice became much brighter. He acted like he was some great sage, completely different from his usual hoodlum self.

“Oh, how do you say we improve them?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Equipment. What else?” Wei Chen said.

“Doesn’t that require materials? Two million worth of materials isn’t enough for you?” Ye Xiu asked. Such a large amount of dungeon materials was more than enough for their team to use. They hadn’t received these materials yet though because they were still individual players in the Heavenly Domain. They didn’t even have the ability to receive these materials. The materials in Samsara were stored in their guild storage, not carried by individual characters. All of these dungeon materials were more than enough to use for improving their current equipment.

“You didn’t get any wild boss materials. What’s the point?” Wei Chen hadn’t slept last night. He had carefully looked over the contract. There wasn’t anything rare in those two million worth of materials. For self-made equipment, the higher the level, the more stringent the requirement for the materials would be. Even if one could find dungeon materials to replace the rarer materials, the creator wouldn’t be happy to do so. Different materials might be able to form a self-made equipment, but how much would it affects its stats?

The shape of the equipment was crucial, but the stats were the most important. It’s similar to building a PC. The PC will have a CPU, RAM, hard disk, video graphics card, but there were differences in quality. A PC made with higher-end components would certainly perform better than one with lower-end components. Self-made equipment strived for the best stats. If one used low-grade materials to create a piece of equipment with the stats of an Orange equipment, what was the point?

Using these materials to replace higher-end material was just a way to save on costs, but some things just couldn’t be replaced. And this was just based on the upgrade process alone. When the equipment needed to be upgraded to Level 70, if the conditions permitted it, it was best to completely use uncommon materials to create the equipment. Only then would the stats be at the peak.

If one didn’t use uncommon materials, the equipment created wouldn’t be considered truly self-made equipment.

“Can you get uncommon materials even if you have money?” Ye Xiu asked in return.

Wei Chen couldn’t answer him. There were very very few uncommon materials amongst the normal player base. Even studios couldn’t compete with the Clubs. Uncommon materials were completely monopolized by Clubs, and as a core component of self-made equipment, as long as the Club wasn’t about to go bankrupt, no Club would ever sell them. Even if they weren’t going to use the material, they could still use it to trade for other uncommon materials.

When a team dissolved, their storage would be thoroughly cleaned out. However, these sort of dissolved guilds wouldn’t have many materials to begin with anyways. In addition, the other Clubs would have swarmed over to buy the materials first. Ye Xiu and the others would never even get the chance to buy them.

They had money, but this money couldn’t be used to buy uncommon materials. Of course, if you put up a high enough price like ten million for material, no Club would refuse, but who would be so wasteful?

Their need for dungeon materials had been met, but the crucial uncommon material still had to be obtained through the game.

“Little Tang, Steamed Bun, try and enter the Heavenly Domain as soon as you can. Once you do that, finish the rest of those quests.” Ye Xiu said.

“What? Are you afraid Samsara is going to pull some sort of trick?” Wei Chen noticed.

“Just in case!” Ye Xiu said.

“Didn’t you say that, with a foundation like Samsara’s, the game company won’t be able to figure out the reason?” Chen Guo said.

“But what if they intentionally revealed it to the game company to establish their advantage?” Ye Xiu said.

Everyone was startled.

“For Samsara, the most important thing is to maintain their advantage over all the other teams. They aren’t going to use the guide to make money, so once they use it, they’ll throw it away. That would be the safest way to ensure they maintain their advantage. From then on, no one else will have this guide to improve their skill points and they would keep their advantage in skill points until who knows how long.” Ye Xiu said.

“Even though they have restrictions set in the contract, this sort of thing isn’t too easy to control, so just in case, we should hurry and get as many of those skill points as we can.” Ye Xiu said.

“Why didn’t you say so earlier!” Chen Guo panicked and hastily urged Tang Rou and Steamed Bun to step it up.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun weren’t max leveled yet, but with their skill, they shouldn’t have any difficulty finishing the Heavenly Domain Challenge. After all, their skill far surpassed normal players. Even if they somehow weren’t able to complete it, wasn’t Ye Xiu there? He could finish it at Level 50 and he wouldn’t have any problems finishing it for them if they were incapable.

When the two heard Ye Xiu’s words, they also began to hurry.

Tang Rou had taken the quest chain at Level 50, but she had trouble completing it at that time, so she decided to put it on hold. Afterwards, as she leveled up, she went back to the quest chain and had finished the majority of it already. Steamed Bun hadn’t received the quest originally, but when she saw that Tang Rou was already doing it before she was Level 70, he also learned from her and occasionally completed parts of the quest chain. However, Steamed Bun’s progress wasn’t as smooth as Tang Rou’s. In a few places that required precision, it wasn’t that Steamed Bun couldn’t do it, but rather, he always wanted to try to succeed in some sort of weird way, which always resulted in failure.

As a result, Ye Xiu supervised and urged Steamed Bun to hurry and finish the quest chain.

Tang Rou focused and finished the quest chain that day. Following after Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash, there were now three characters from the tenth server in the Heavenly Domain.

Afterwards, she went to do the skill point quests that she hadn’t done yet in the Heavenly Domain. After receiving a quest, she completed it and received a skill book, which meant that Samsara hadn’t pulled a dirty trick just yet. It had only been a day or two. No matter how fast Samsara was, they couldn’t be that fast.

The game company might not decide to change the quests, even after knowing about this skill point farming method. Let alone Samsara, even the Alliance could only communicate with the game company. They didn’t have any way of forcing them to do anything if they didn’t want to do it. More often than not, the Alliance had to adapt to whatever changes the game made.

That night, another 5000 skill point character was birthed from Happy Internet Cafe. According to Concealed Light’s data, of the 1650 skill points possible, a character would get around 965 skill points on average.

From this number, Ye Xiu’s and Tang Rou’s luck were already extremely good. They hadn’t even finished all of the quests yet and they already received 1000 skill points.

Wei Chen didn’t stay idle. His Windward Formation had finished all of those quests, but didn’t he still have a Warlock account on hand?

However, this account had been obtained along with Unrivaled Super Hottie when Ye Xiu won the wager. The skill points were very average, 4210 points. Wei Chen had run quests all night. Quests already completed couldn’t be done again. In the end, he ended up with a total of 4480 skill points…..

This was pretty good for normal players, but for them, Wei Chen’s efforts were for nothing.

“What do I do? Do I buy a hundred Warlock accounts?” Wei Chen was starting to panic. Windward Formation had 4920 skill points, but it wasn’t good enough! Now that he was rich, he started with an estimate of a hundred accounts.

“A hundred? A thousand wouldn’t even be enough. These are normal accounts. Do you think all of them have the same base stats as a pro characters?” Ye Xiu said.

“It looks like I’ll have to specially order a few, but what if the accounts come out and the quests are wasted?” Wei Chen was worried.

“4920 skill points isn’t bad. Even Samsara won’t have all of their characters maxed with 5000 skill points.” Ye Xiu said.

“No, I refuse. Let me think.” Wei Chen hadn’t slept the previous night and had been focusing hard the entire day, but he was still full of energy!

Tang Rou was done and it was just a matter of time before Steamed Bun finished as well, but there was also Concealed Light and Little Cold Hands.

Concealed Light’s issue lay in his mechanics. He wouldn’t be able to reach the Heavenly Domain in a short amount of time either. There were also a few places in the guide, which required a certain level of mechanics too. It would be a waste if Concealed Light didn’t get the same treatment. With no other choice, Ye Xiu took Concealed Light’s account card and completed it for him.

As for Little Cold Hands, they had only been in touch with him for a short amount of time. The trust between them was still extremely limited, so he didn’t feel confident in giving showing the guide over to Little Cold Hands. Even more so, Little Cold Hands was an old account. If he had finished all of the quests before, he wouldn’t be able to get receive any skill points. Would his account be like Wei Chen’s or Chen Guo’s accounts and only be able to get around max out at 4500 skill points? That was far from being good enough to compete with the pros.

Just thinking about it wouldn’t get anything done. Ye Xiu contacted Little Cold Hands on QQ.

Little Cold Hands had 4170 skill points. As expected, it was only a normal account. As for which quests he had done before, Little Cold Hands was an account that had been gifted to him, so he didn’t know either. With no other choice, Ye Xiu gave the handed over a list of quests to him to and have him check which quests he had done before. If he hadn’t, then he shouldn’t touch them for now.

“It’s very important. Please hurry and check.” Ye Xiu said.

“What’s so special about these quests?” Little Cold Hands wasn’t like Steamed Bun, who wouldn’t think to ask before doing something.

“It has to do with improving your character’s strength, but it requires a special method, so I need to make sure your character hasn’t done all of these quests already.” Ye Xiu explained.

Chapter 639 – Playoffs

“By improving strength, are you referring to skill books?” As expected, Little Cold Hands wasn’t Steamed Bun. It wasn’t hard to arrive at this answer. He was a max leveled character. If he wanted to strengthen his character, there were only two ways: skill points and equipment. Ye Xiu had just asked him about his character’s skill points and now, he wanted him to do some seemingly random quests. It was only to be expected that he would put two and two together.

“Yes. First, verify which quests you’ve already completed.” Ye Xiu didn’t hide it. Even though they weren’t too familiar with one another, Little Cold Hands would still be a member of their future team. It wouldn’t be good to treat him like a complete outsider.

“Sure, give me a moment to check.” Little Cold Hands replied.

As a result, the team began to hurry and improve their skill points as if they were participating in the upcoming playoffs as well. After Little Cold Hands circled around the Heavenly Domain and the normal server, he reported the results to Ye Xiu. His luck was quite good. Little Cold Hands hadn’t done many of the quests yet. Of the total 1650 skill points possible, he still had 1220 skill points that he could potentially obtain. His character only needed 830 skill points to max out, so if his luck was good, he just might be able to do it.

This type of normal account made Chen Guo very envious. Her Chasing Haze had completed most of these quests already, so she hadn’t gained much from the guide. However, Chen Guo had created a new account in the new server earlier and made sure to leave all of these quests open, but with the quest guide being bought out by Samsara, by the time her new Chasing Haze reached the Heavenly Domain, it was hard to say if she would still be able to utilize the guide.

Chen Guo was upset. She only regretted that she hadn’t spent enough time on the new server account to level this account faster.

“That’s pretty good. You have a lot of quests still available. If it’s okay with you, could you leave this account with me? I’ll help you finish these quests.” Ye Xiu said.

“I can’t do them myself?”

“It requires a special method.” Ye Xiu said.

Little Cold Hands didn’t ask any further questions. Ye Xiu had expected this to happen because the other side was an astute person, who had certainly realized that this method couldn’t easily be given away. Little Cold Hands wasn’t just astute either. He was also smart. Ye Xiu trusted that Little Cold Hands wouldn’t blame him for not giving him the guide to see. The question was whether or not Little Cold Hands was willing to entrust him with his own account. It had to be known that this guy had initially suspected Ye Xiu of trying to swindle him. Ye Xiu hadn’t asked him for anything like a cash deposit, but the first thing he asked him to do was send over his account card. It seemed very much like a scam.

“Are you in a hurry?” Sure enough, Little Cold Hands was a bit hesitant.

“The faster the better.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Uh……” Little Cold Hands left this message and then became silent.

The conversation had been conducted in the group chat, so everyone else saw it too. Apart from Steamed Bun, everyone could tell Little Cold Hand’s misgivings. Thus, Wei Chen suddenly spoke impatiently: “Stop wasting time! How much could your account possibly be worth? I’ll give you a down payment.”

Wei Chen’s wealth was considerable right now, and he had no qualms using it.

“Oh, if that’s the case, how about 2000!” Little Cold Hands actually gave a number. His account was very average, but it was still a member of Tyrannical Ambition. Amidst the normal playerbase, it wouldn’t be considered too bad.

“F*ck, you actually dared!” Wei Chen was surprised.

“What?” Little Cold Hands asked in doubt.

Wei Chen was speechless. When he said he would give a down payment, according to Wei Chen’s understanding, the other side would usually be too embarrassed to ask for the money and would just happily send over the account card. It turns out he had met someone on a completely different wavelength than himself. The other side immediately answered back and actually gave a price.

But since things had already reached such a stage, Wei Chen felt awkward, but he couldn’t back out, could he? Plus, after having received 20 million, 2000 was nothing to him.

“Alright, send me your bank account info.” Wei Chen didn’t say anything more.

Little Cold Hands didn’t hesitate and sent over his bank account info.

“Check your account tomorrow.” Wei Chen coldly said and turned his head towards Ye Xiu: “I don’t like this guy.”

Not many people would like what Little Cold Hands had just done. Even Chen Guo wasn’t happy. Although they didn’t trust Little Cold Hands and didn’t send him a copy of the guide, the difference between their exchanges were completely different. Chen Guo was certain that if it were anyone else in Little Cold Hand’s position, they wouldn’t have done the same thing that Little Cold Hands had done.

Thinking about it in this way, Chen Guo felt more comfortable looking at Little Cold Hands with disdain and began expressing her discontent with Wei Chen.

In any case, they were now busy attending to improving these characters. As the days passed, the start of the playoffs finally arrived.

Blue Rain, Samsara, Tiny Herb, Tyranny, Misty Rain, Void, Thunderclap, 301. These were their final placings in the regular season. The seedings for the playoffs were decided by these placings: 1st vs 8th, 2nd vs 7th, 3rd vs 6th, 4th vs 5th.

This was also the order of the matches. Blue Rain versus 301. Samsara versus Thunderclap. Tiny Herb versus Void. Tyranny versus Misty Rain.

Four matches would be conducted across the span of four days. To make it easier to stream the matches, the matches would take place separate from one another. The matches would cycle between the home arenas of the the two teams to give equal opportunities for each team to share the profit for the revenue generated by playoff tickets.

Thus, the first round of the playoffs would take eight days total. In the second round, the four teams that won would move on and finish another four matches in four days. The finals would be two matches over four days as well. Because the matches would take place at different arenas, the players had to move around, so they didn’t want them to become too tired.

The competition format was the same as before: an individual competition, group competition, and a team competition. The total points in the home and away matches would be added up. Because there had to be a winner, when totaling up the points, there would be a few subtle differences than they had in calculations during the regular season.

The start of the playoffs received a large amount of attention from Glory players, so it usually started on a Saturday, but because many watched the matches, many of them would hold off on playing the game during that time, which affected the number of people playing the game.

For the match on the first day, Blue Rain versus 301, everything went as expected. Blue Rain had a huge lead. With such a huge gap in skill and placing, it was unrealistic for 301 to catch up to Blue Rain in their own home arena. Blue Rain’s performance immediately drew comments such as “killed the competition”. Such a quick victory made it seem like the playoffs would not be suspenseful, making people looking for a profit not as happy, but for the team, having such a large lead early on was a good thing.

For the match on the second day, Samsara versus Thunderclap, a lot of people were looking for an upset. Samsara had gained more and more momentum as the season went on. When the playoffs arrived, Samsara was believed to have the greatest chances of winning. Naturally, a lot of people didn’t want this to happen and were waiting to see them fail. Despite not having an incredible ace player, but one of the Master Tacticians, Xiao Shiqin, leading them instead, Team Thunderclap was often a team that gave powerhouses a lot of trouble.

But the results made them disappointed. Samsara maintained their usual dominance after the All Star Weekend and crushed Team Thunderclap in their home arena. This result made many surprised. Even if Thunderclap lost, with Xiao Shiqin’s tactics, they shouldn’t have lost so badly.

Everyone in Happy Internet Cafe paid more attention to this match than the first match. They naturally wanted to see how much of a difference the skill points would make and the results didn’t disappoint them.

“What a pity. If they didn’t have those skill points, Thunderclap wouldn’t have lost so badly.” Ye Xiu hit the nail on the head. Team Thunderclap often lacked the strength to dominate opponents, so they usually won through meticulously studying their opponents and finding a strategy to win. As a result, no one ever underestimated Thunderclap. However this time, Samsara had sudden improvement in skill points. This type of change significantly impacted Thunderclap’s plans. As expected, Thunderclap appeared to be underprepared and their tactics didn’t seem to be on point. In reality, it was impossible for their tactics to be on point because the data and information used by Xiao Shiqin to form the strategy were all wrong.

No one but insiders would realize this point.

After this match, the only person who would realize this point would be Xiao Shiqin himself. In the press conference afterwards, he talked about how the other side had some unexpected improvements. As for what these improvements were, Xiao Shiqin probably had a few rough estimates, but he didn’t say anything. For the next match, Xiao Shiqin said a few words that could be regarded as half-hearted.

For the match on the third day, the match between Tiny Herb and Void was actually very intense. The synergy between the Ghostblade duo of Team Void was immaculate. When Ye Qiu retired this season, the two had received the Best Partner reward in the regular season. In the end, Team Void and the previous champions Team Tiny Herb fought an even match, but despite Team Void having the home field advantage, Team Void was still on the losing side.

However, the most intense match would be between Tyranny and Misty Rain. The two teams fought for the longest. In the end, Misty Rain relied on their home field advantage to gather more points. Their second match would only be more intense. After Ye Xiu watched this match, he was quite baffled.

“Han Wenqing isn’t performing too well……” His long-time rival unexpectedly made him feel like he was a stranger.

Chapter 640 – You Can See That Too!

“Really?” Wei Chen heard Ye Xiu’s remark and asked.

Han Wenqing had been playing since the beginning of the professional scene, so Wei Chen obviously knew him. They had fought against each other many a time before, but it had been many years since then and no matter how deep of an impression he had of him, there was no way it could compare to the deep rivalry that existed between Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing. Ye Xiu had noticed a problem, but he hadn’t noticed anything wrong at all. In his eyes, the two sides had fought intensely. It was a very high skill match and he hadn’t seen any issues with Tyranny’s ace player, Han Wenqing.

“Uh, I guess he’s not playing badly, but something doesn’t feel right!” Ye Xiu said.

“What doesn’t feel right?” Wei Chen immediately asked. He wasn’t nervous for no reason. As a retired pro player, his reaction speed and hand speed was declining, but he was certainly still at a pro level in terms of experience, knowledge, and perceptiveness.

“I can’t say exactly right now……” Ye Xiu furrowed his brow and shook his head.

Happy Internet Cafe would, without question, stream the playoffs, but they were currently watching it in the practice room. Because of their differences in skill levels, their discussions were at a different level. Ye Xiu and Wei Chen gave their opinions on the matches. Chen Guo knew a bit more about the game, so she could understand some of what they were saying. As for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, they had only played for several months already, but weren’t complete noobs anymore. However, if they had to discuss the very fine details of the match, the two probably wouldn’t be able to keep up.

The two were at a complete loss when Ye Xiu said that something was wrong with Han Wenqing. Both of them looked at Ye Xiu, waiting for him to continue.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything further though. The stream was already showing the post-match interview. Tyranny and Misty Rain hadn’t made any major mistakes. Both teams had gone all out that match and neither team would feel too regretful if they lost. The interviewed players practically said the same thing. They expressed their confidence in their respective teams, praised their opponents, and spoke of their faith in being able to win the next match, etc.

Tyranny’s captain Han Wenqing naturally participated in the interview. Because Ye Xiu had specially called him out, everyone else paid close attention to what he said and also stared at his facial expressions. However, everything seemed to be normal. It didn’t look like there was anything abnormal with Han Wenqing’s condition. When the interview ended and the stream went offline, everyone turned to look at Ye Xiu, waiting for him to say something.

Ye Xiu only shook his head and returned to his computer.

Everyone else returned to their seats too. Wei Chen went back to his seat and saw that Ye Xiu still seemed to be thinking hard. He didn’t bother him and handed him a cigarette instead.

Ye Xiu received it and quietly lit it. He still didn’t say anything. He opened up a web browser and typed in a few words.

Wei Chen watched from over his shoulder and saw that it was a site for downloading VODs. It seemed like Ye Xiu was planning on studying the match. However, since the match just ended, it would take some time before it would be uploaded. Seeing that it couldn’t be downloaded yet, Ye Xiu opened up a folder and began looking through Tyranny’s previous matches.

He watched match after match, closely spectating Han Wenqing’s Desert Smoke. Ye Xiu gradually began to relax. Soon afterwards, he went back to the site and downloaded the most recent match.

Wei Chen had been paying attention to Ye Xiu’s actions the entire time, so when he saw the change in expression, he asked: “Did you figure it out?”

“Pretty much!” Ye Xiu replied.

Chen Guo went over and asked: “What’s the situation?”

“He’s changing.” Ye Xiu said.

“Changing?”

“Yeah, he’s changing his habits and Striker movements. He’s researching a new style of playing his class.” Ye Xiu said.

“He really refuses to give up!” Wei Chen sighed.

Creating a new style wasn’t an easy task. Even though every few levels brought new skills or new equipment, there was always a certain amount of variance, but the change from these new skills or equipment could only be considered adjustments. They wouldn’t cause a player to significantly change his or her playstyle. The classes in Glory were very balanced, so updates didn’t bring much change to a class’ core.

If Ye Xiu said someone of Han Wenqing’s caliber was researching a new playstyle, it wasn’t going to be just a simple numbers adjustment. A slight adjustment like that wasn’t anything difficult for a pro player to adapt to. It wouldn’t be something that Ye Xiu would be so surprised about either.

Han Wenqing was clearly trying to do something completely different.

Soon afterwards, Ye Xiu finished downloading the VOD. Ye Xiu immediately replayed it. Wei Chen also watched. Even though Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were interested, it wasn’t something they would be able to comprehend.

To put it plainly, pro players specialized in PvP. The biggest difference between PvP and PvE was how deep one’s understanding of all the classes were, whether it was your class or any other class. What skills, combos, playstyles, strategy, etc. were all something that pro players needed to know very thoroughly. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were quite familiar with their respective classes, but their understanding of other classes was still limited. Let alone someone trying to create a new playstyle, let alone them, even Chen Guo wouldn’t be able to say much.

Sure enough, Chen Guo was also at a complete loss when Ye Xiu paused and commented on a segment, but this time, she felt gratified that even Wei Chen was at a loss too.

“See, here.” After watching several of Desert Smoke’s matches, Ye Xiu had grasped the general line of thinking and pointed out the changes in his playstyle: “If this had happened in the past, he would have most likely stepped forward and began pushing forward using Reinforced Iron Bones or jumped backwards and sent a Whirlwind Kick back. Instead, he stepped sideways and used a Collapsing Fist. It seems like he plans on initiating with an Empty-Handed Block. I’ve never seen him do something like that before.”

“Really?” Wei Chen was really at a loss because Ye Xiu’s comment had been too detailed and random. Every player would react differently depending on each situation. How could Ye Xiu guess all of that?

“Over here too.” Not waiting for Wei Chen to understand, Ye Xiu pointed at another place: “Here. Don’t you think this Dual Tiger Fists is too sudden?”

“Really? I feel like it’s a good choice……” Wei Chen continued to be at a loss.

The screen was currently playing the most recent match between Misty Rain and Tyranny. Two melee characters closed in under the protection of the bombardment by Chu Yunxiu’s Windy Rain. However, Desert Smoke closed in on them faster and sent the two flying away with a Dual Tiger Fists.

“Cloud Body Dual Tiger Fists. Isn’t that a common combo?” Wei Chen said. Cloud Body was a movement skill for Strikers. Cloud Body followed by Dual Tiger Fists was called Cloud Body Dual Tiger Fists. It was one of the most commonly used Striker combos.

“Cloud Body was used a bit later, but Dual Tiger Fists was used a bit earlier.” Ye Xiu said.

“.......” Wei Chen rewatched the segment twice and then gave up :”Okay, who else here actually sees that?”

Wei Chen looked towards Chen Guo, who shook her head too. Cloud Body Dual Tiger Fists was a common combo that she also knew about, but everyone used it slightly differently. Han Wenqing’s usage of the combo seemed to have a good effect, but she couldn’t see anything weird about it.

“If it was before, he would have never played like this.” Ye Xiu said.

“How did he do it before?” Wei Chen asked.

“Is it better or worse now?” Chen Guo asked.

Ye Xiu only shook his head: “I can’t say. It seems like he’s still figuring it out too.”

Ye Xiu continued to watch and found several other segments to talk about, but Wei Chen and Chen Guo were completely at a loss. They listened and listened and got a general understanding of the changes. Han Wenqing’s changes were in the small details. Some of the places were just his intentions, but Ye Xiu could actually see through these intentions and analyze them.

“He’s a bit late here…..”

“That’s not something he would have done in the past…….”

“He’s probably thinking of……”

In the end, Chen Guo couldn’t help but feel moved after hearing Ye Xiu come to these conclusions: “The person who understands you the best is your enemy. This saying really isn’t wrong.”

“Not wrong at all.” Wei Chen nodded his head. He wasn’t nervous anymore. Not being able to see what Ye Xiu was seeing wasn’t an issue with his skill level, but rather his understanding of Han Wenqing himself. Ye Xiu was also nicknamed Glory’s Encyclopedia and he probably had a better understanding of the various classes, apart from Warlocks, than Wei Chen.

And from the sounds of it, Han Wenqing’s new playstyle wasn’t something at a fundamental level. If not, a new skill combo would have easily been noticed by any experienced player, let alone a pro, but for these minute changes, there were very few people besides Ye Xiu who would notice them. At the post-match interview, Misty Rain’s players never mentioned this change. It meant that Han Wenqing was still in the midst of changing it!

Once he figured this out, Wei Chen didn’t want to watch any further. He patted Ye Xiu and said: “You should have Little Tang and Steamed Bun listen to your chatter. It’ll definitely increase their understanding of Strikers.”

“Mm, those two need to improve in this area.” Ye Xiu heard his advice and nodded his head.

Chapter 641: Times Have Changed

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun had leveled their characters from Level 1, so they each had a good grasp of their respective classes. However, their understanding of the other classes were far from enough. Even though they had an incredible win record in the Arena, that was mostly through reliance on their superior mechanics. Just their mechanics alone allowed them to stand at the top of the game. However, in the pro scene, their mechanics weren’t good enough to beat others.

Their characters were almost max leveled, but because they had decided to enter the pro scene, there was no need to study things like dungeons or bosses. PvP had its own set of knowledge that needed to be mastered. They didn’t have much time on their hands, so they couldn’t waste their time studying pointless things.

“It seems like an encyclopedia like you, who is proficient in all of the classes, is finally finding some use.” Wei Chen patted Ye Xiu’s shoulder.

Directly practicing PvP was the most enjoyable way to learn. Ye Xiu had to agree too, but if Tang Rou and Steamed Bun tried to accumulate experience through the Arena, their harvest wouldn’t be very fruitful. Their skill level surpassed the scope of difficulty that the Arena could provide them with. They could overwhelm opponents with just their mechanics alone. Very few players could provide any sort of challenge for them. It was like killing Level 30 monsters as a Level 60 character. The experience gained couldn’t even be considered a consolation prize.

In-game leveling, as well as improving one’s PvP skill, were similar in this way. At this point, Ye Xiu might need to personally train them.

“This type of practice is necessary.” Ye Xiu didn’t avoid the subject, “It looks like we’re going to need another set of accounts.”

“Ha ha, that shouldn’t be a problem.” Wei Chen was a rich man now. He looked online and bought a set of accounts.

Ye Xiu had finished watching Tyranny’s VODs, so he closed them. It was a pity that no one could share the same feelings that he felt right now.

Once the match between Tyranny and Misty Rain ended, the first half of the first round had been completed. Each team would play two matches in the first round before their points were tallied up and the winner was declared, so for these first matches, no one would really win or lose them. People looked at their total points and examined which team had the advantage or which was at a disadvantage. Whether the team was playing in their home stadium or in an away stadium mattered. The team that could choose the maps for the match had a large advantage, especially in the playoffs. The teams would naturally choose their most proficient maps.

On the fifth day, the second match between Samsara and Thunderclap began. This time, the match took place in Samsara’s home stadium

Samsara had already obtained a huge lead in their away game. All of the pressure was on Thunderclap, who relied on analyzing and planning appropriate strategies to counter their opponents. With Samsara’s sudden improvement in characters, even after a four day rest to adjust their strategies, it didn’t seem likely that Thunderclap would be able to defeat Samsara. Even Xiao Shiqin wouldn’t be able to calculate exactly how much of an advantage the skill points that Samsara’s characters had gained would give them. In addition to that, a strategy-centered team like Thunderclap relied greatly on the map that was chosen. It could be seen from their regular season that Thunderclap won significantly more home games than they did away games.

In their second match, Samsara won handily. This match could be considered an effortless victory on their part. However, after the first match ended, when others analyzed the match, quite a few people, along with Xiao Shiqin, had noticed that the skill points on Samsara’s characters seemed to be different. After all, when a skill was leveled up, there would be a slight change in the effects. This sort of change was easy to perceive by experienced players.

In the post-match interview, the keen reporters asked about this issue. Unfortunately, they encountered Samsara’s team captain, Zhou Zekai. Everyone wanted to know the answer to this question, but all they got was a “Mm.” Was that “Mm” a “Mm?” Or a “Mm!” No one understood what he was trying to say. All of the reporters wanted to slam their heads against a wall.

Seeing the reporters want to cough blood when they heard Zhou Zekai’s response to their question was a sight that Samsara enjoyed very much. Today, they had won the first round of the playoffs, so they were even happier right now, but they couldn’t ignore this question forever. In the end, the vice-captain Jiang Botao came forward for an interview and gave a definite answer.

This definite answer confirmed that Samsara’s characters had improved in terms of skill points, but Jiang Botao obviously wouldn’t say the exact increase in skill points. It would soon be figured out, but the longer they could keep it a secret, the better!

As for Thunderclap, after Xiao Shiqin expressed his feelings for being eliminated in the first round, he didn’t immediately convey his confidence for the future, like what most players usually did. Instead, Xiao Shiqin suddenly began talking about his career.

Xiao Shiqin had been a player, who had become famous early on. Starting from when he was first discovered, he had become well known for his decision-making and control rather than his mechanics. The Thunderclap players, who had noticed his potential, regarded him as a team player.

Xiao Shiqin didn’t fail to live up to his expectations. Starting from the fourth season, he soon became the cornerstone of Team Thunderclap and took over the team as the captain. He and his character Life Extinguisher were frequent guests at the All Stars. Along with Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie, Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou, and Excellent Era’s Ye Qiu, he was the last of Glory’s Four Master Tacticians.

But compared to the other three Master Tacticians, Xiao Shiqin’s career was less successful.

He was an incredible tactician and strategist, but it was a pity that he didn’t have an ace player on his team. This was what most people felt towards Xiao Shiqin. Team Thunderclap wasn’t a powerhouse. Apart from Xiao Shiqin and his Life Extinguisher, there were no other All Star level players or characters on their team.

As for the other three?

Zhang Xinjie had Han Wenqing and the King of Fighters, Desert Smoke, by his side. Yu Wenzhou had Huang Shaotian and the Sword Saint, Troubling Rain, by his side. Ye Qiu was even better. He himself was considered the Alliance’s number one attacker and controlled the legendary Battle God, One Autumn Leaf. These three were not only incredible tacticians and strategists, but all of them had God-level teammates or God-level accounts to support them. Only Xiao Shiqin didn’t have any strong helpers. He could only rely on his tactics to utilize his team’s lackluster potential to its fullest.

Unfortunately, this wasn’t enough to become the champion, let alone maintain a stable position at the top of the standings in the regular season.

“Times have changed.” After reminiscing about his career, Xiao Shiqin sighed.

The experienced reports instantly sniffed out a few leads.

Times have changed.

Is he talking about Team Thunderclap making changes? Or is Xiao Shiqin talking about himself making changes?”

From how emotional Xiao Shiqin was being after recalling his career, it was more likely that he himself would be making changes.

Before the reporter could ask any further questions, Xiao Shiqin already began speaking: “That was my final match with Thunderclap. I am grateful for the Club that I’ve been with for so many years, my teammates, and my fans. I have grown with this team for my entire career and it has not been an easy decision for me to come to. I am sorry that I cannot continue moving forward with everyone for another season, but no matter where I go in the future, Thunderclap will always be the team that raised me.”

The reporters immediately became excited. An ace player like Xiao Shiqin was actually going to transfer teams. It was as if a huge bomb had been dropped. From the reactions of his teammates, it seemed like they already knew about this decision. They didn’t look shocked. They wished him well and gave him their blessings.

“I hope everything goes well for him!”

“He has the ability to become a champion. We’ve been dragging him down.”

“No matter where he goes, I’ll always be his number one fan!”

All of Team Thunderclap’s other members expressed their good will towards Xiao Shiqin’s departure. Even though none of these players were stars in the pro scene, through the tactics and teamwork that brought them together, they had a deeper relationship with one another. No one felt betrayed by Xiao Shiqion’s departure. They sincerely gave him their blessings.

His departure was saddening, but also warm. Xiao Shiqin thanked his teammates for the support they gave him and his words were sincere.

“He’s actually planning on transferring.” Xiao Shiqin was someone in the younger generation, who Wei Chen had never fought against before. He was currently at the peak of his career, so Wei Chen had obviously heard of him before, “I don’t think the core of a team like him has ever transferred to another team before, no?”

“Sun Xiang?” Ye Xiu said.

“That monkey came out of a thatched cottage. Does that even count?” Wei Chen expressed.

“That doesn’t count?” Ye Xiu said.

“Fine!” Wei Chen didn’t argue, “Where do you think he will go? Blue Rain? Tyranny? I don’t think any of those teams will take him. His capabilities would collide with Yu Wenzhou or Zhang Xinjie. He wouldn’t be able to fully display his strength. Tiny Herb has Wang Jiexi. They probably don’t need him, unless Tiny Herb plans on having Wang Jiexi change playstyles and become an offense-oriented Witch. Oh, that’s actually quite possible if you think about it.”

“There’s another team who needs him even more than Tiny Herb does.” Ye Xiu said.

“Which team?” Wei Chen was thinking.

“Excellent Era……” Ye Xiu said.

“Sh*t!!” Wei Chen was startled, but he immediately realized the likelihood of it happening.

“Excellent Era’s future core will definitely be Sun Xiang. In order to get him to be accepted by the team or develop a good set of tactics for him, they need someone like Xiao Shiqin.” Ye Xiu said.

“Excellent Era just got f*cking relegated. Would he actually be stupid enought to run over to Excellent Era?” Wei Chen shook his head.

“With Excellent Era’s foundation and Sun Xiang still there, no one doubts that they will return to the Alliance next season, no? If they had Xiao Shiqin, they will definitely have the strength to directly win the championships, or perhaps that isn’t his thoughts?” Ye Xiu said.

“No, no, that’s not good. He can’t think like that.” Wei Chen was still shaking his head.

“Why not?” Ye Xiu said.

“Then that f*cker wants us to die!!” Wei Chen cursed.

Chapter 642: Top Four

Wei Chen’s worry was sincere. Team Excellent Era with Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf was already terrifying as is. Now, there might even be a Xiao Shiqin too.

For someone like Xiao Shiqin, it didn’t really matter what type of character he played. His value wasn’t measured in his battle strength. If he successfully joined Excellent Era, if Sun Xiang could be melded to dance to his tune, Excellent Era would absolutely be at a level where they could take the championships.

Having a team that hadn’t even gathered all of its team members yet challenge a championship-level team? Wei Chen felt like their hopes were only diminishing as more time passed.

“What are you scared of? In any case, you have plenty of money now. Even if you lose, you won’t be starving.” Ye Xiu said.

“This senior would rather be starving.” Wei Chen humphed.

Chen Guo and the others had listened to their discussion. Steamed Bun was as calm as ever. Tang Rou felt even more motivated after hearing that there would be another formidable opponent to face. Chen Guo was more worried than anyone else like usual.

“In any case, we’ll have to face them. You’ve already become so nervous just thinking about the possibility of Xiao Shiqin joining Excellent Era. What if Excellent Era didn’t stop there and obtained several more amazing players. What would you do? Jump out the window?” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck, besides this guy surnamed Xiao, who else would be that stupid?” Wei Chen had originally been indifferent towards Xiao Shiqin, but after discovering that he might be a potential enemy in the future and a formidable one at that, he immediately viewed him with distaste.

After the post-match interview ended, the community instantly erupted. Samsara’s victory had been too easy, so no one talked too much about the match. Suddenly, a huge bomb was thrown out, shaking various levels of Glory.

Xiao Shiqin had said that he would be transferring teams out of his own mouth. The discussion within the community was naturally focused on which team he would be joining. There were all sorts of analyses. Wei Chen read them and criticised: “Stupid, too stupid.”

Ye Xiu turned his head and gave a glance. It was a post talking about Xiao Shiqin’s likelihood of joining Excellent Era. The poster’s analysis was quite reasonable. If an expert like Xiao Shiqin joined Excellent Era, he would be sacrificing a year, but afterwards, the team would become a first-rate championship team. Wei Chen simply didn’t want to see this type of situation happening, so the more reasonable the analysis was, the more he hated it. It was as if acting like this would kill any chances of Xiao Shiqin joining Excellent Era.

Compared to the commotion within the community, Ye Xiu looked at the pro player group in QQ. There was a bit of a discussion going on there, but the players speaking were those that hadn’t made it to the playoffs. The playoff teams were nervously preparing for their matches. They didn’t have the free time to chat. For them, no matter which team Xiao Shiqin ended up going to, that team would become a formidable opponent. For the first round, the key issue that they needed to look into was Samsara’s improvement.

Samsara would be the most formidable opponent that they would be facing in the near future. As a result, the various teams needed to hurry up and figure out Samsara’s exact situation.

The more Wei Chen looked at the analyses, the angrier he became. Many of them pointed at Xiao Shiqin possibly joining Excellent Era. Eventually, Wei Chen finally slammed the table: “Steamed Bun, what level are you?! Hurry up! There’s no time! Hurry up and get to max level so we can start practicing.”

“Okay okay. I’m leveling right now.” Steamed Bun replied energetically.

“Sigh, the bad news comes right after the good news. What an ordeal.” Wei Chen sighed. His incredible joy at earning so much money had been completely wiped away.

“Be a bit more calm. You’re always panicking. You’re over 30 already. Pick two young players out of the competitive scene and their ages combined would be less than yours. They wouldn’t be as nervous as you either. Don’t you feel ashamed of yourself?” Ye Xiu said.

“I have to express my feelings somehow. Holding it in would affect my condition too much.” Wei Chen said.

Soon, they witnessed how Wei Chen planned on expressing his feelings. Samsara had easily pranced through the first round of playoffs. The entire guild was full of joy. On the other hand, Wei Chen seemed to have eaten an explosive. When he led his team, he shouted at them furiously as if they were lower than dogs. Ye Xiu glanced at Wei Chen’s screen. His team had just started killing a small mob of monsters. By the time they reached the boss, his entire team would have probably disconnected from being lectured so miserably.

The sixth day, seventh day, and eighth day passed. The playoffs wouldn’t stop because of the commotion. The matches continued. Blue Rain and Tiny Herb defeated 301 and Void without a hitch. (Oh, Blue Rain and 301’s match should have been before Samsara and Thunderclap’s. I forgot, but it shouldn’t matter too much as long as everyone knows……) However in the match between Tyranny and Misty Rain, Misty Rain maintained their advantage in their away game and won against Tyranny.

Even though Tyranny was a powerhouse team, being eliminated by Team Misty Rain wasn’t too shocking. After all, Tyranny’s ace player Han Wenqing was old. At the start of the Alliance, he had fought for three championship titles against Excellent Era. In the fourth season, they ended Excellent Era’s dominance and Tyranny’s golden age had begun.

Now, as the seasons went by and the next generation of players were taking over, Tyranny and Excellent Era began to decline in the eyes of others.

In addition, no team in the playoffs could be considered weak. If not, wouldn’t the playoffs be boring?

When Tyranny was eliminated, their captain Han Wenqing expressed his sorrows, but he didn’t seem to be in low spirits: “We’ll be back next year.” His words seemed to cover Team Misty Rain’s victory spotlight.

Be that as it may, the media generally reported it as the end of an era.

Of the two top Gods in the past, one had retired and the other was struggling to hang on.

Of the two former dragons, one had been relegated, while the other had been eliminated in the first round of the playoffs.

When Han Wenqing said “We’ll be back next year”, everyone considered it to be his stubbornness to continue. It was admirable, but some things couldn’t change by conviction alone.

Tyranny might be able to stand on stage for the playoffs again, but few believed that they still had the competitive strength to take the championship home, especially after witnessing Excellent Era falling and getting relegated. Some even wondered if Tyranny would quickly collapse and never recover.

The Tyranny fans strongly opposed this view, of course.

“You’re joking!” Some of the fans scoffed, “Don’t forget who our captain is! He’s someone who wasn’t discouraged after failing to win the championships three years in a row. Then, in the fourth year, he dethroned Excellent Era. As long as Han Wenqing is there, our Tyranny will never end up like Excellent Era!”

As Tyranny’s fans, they weren’t polite at all with Excellent Era They had laughed as Excellent Era declined during the regular season. People were now grouping Tyranny with Excellent Era. How could they bear it?

When the first round of the playoffs had ended, there were countless questions left unanswered.

The four that that advanced were Blue Rain, Samsara, Tiny Herb, and Misty Rain and were without a doubt powerful teams. Among the eliminated teams, many of them had been moved.

But time didn’t stop for anyone. The four advancing teams quickly began the next round.

Blue Rain versus Misty Rain, Samsara versus Tiny Herb. The outcome of these two confrontations would decide who would advance to the finals.

At Happy Internet Cafe, they were also in a discussion when they saw Tyranny get eliminated.

“Didn’t he change? How did they still lose?” Chen Guo found it hard to understand how Tyranny had lost.

“Did you think he would go Super Saiyan?!” Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry, “He’s changed, but he’s still trying to figure it out. The strengths and weaknesses of his changes haven’t shown yet!”

As Ye Xiu explained the reason to Chen Guo, he contacted Little Cold Hands.

“I’ve received your account card.” Ye Xiu reported to Little Cold Hands.

“Okay.” Little Cold Hands replied.

“After I increase your skill points, you should know that the value of your account card will be very different.” Ye Xiu said.

“I know.”

“So this account can no longer be considered solely yours.” Ye Xiu said.

“I understand.” Little Cold Hands replied.

“You punk. When we give back the account card, shouldn’t you hand us a down payment?” Wei Chen suddenly popped in. He didn’t care about the two thousand. Let alone Wei Chen being rich now, even when things had been difficult, Wei Chen had never placed much importance on money. Because of this, he hadn’t liked how Little Cold Hands had bickered about it.

“Then how much should I give?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“That depends on how many skill points we get once we finish clearing all the quests.” Wei Chen said.

“But isn’t giving a down payment improper practice?” Little Cold Hands said.

“Hm? You punk. When you asked for a down payment, what was proper about that?” Wei Chen flared up.

“You were the one to propose the down payment!” Little Cold Hands said.

“Stop speaking nonsense.” Wei Chen retorted, when he discovered that everyone else was staring at him.

“What? I proposed it?” Wei Chen scratched it. Everyone nodded their heads.

“Fine. I was just trying to show some goodwill. Who would have thought that this punk would actually agree?” Wei Chen said.

In the group chat, Ye Xiu asked: “Student An, what are your thoughts?”

“Usually, if a team needs a player’s account, don’t they usually buy out the account?” Little Cold Hands said.

“Usually.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then I won’t return the 2000 and I’ll say that you guys bought it out?” Little Cold Hands said.

“F*ck me. The first thing you do is earn 2000 from us! How capable of you!” Wei Chen shouted.

“It’s just an account transfer, that’s all. If it isn’t clear who owns the account, that isn’t good, no?” Little Cold Hands said.

Chapter 643: The Standard Way

“Comrades!” After Little Cold Hand’s reply, Ye Xiu gave a sincere and heartfelt lecture: “If our team plans on developing itself in the long term, this is the correct attitude to have! Everyone correct yourself! My Lord Grim, Steamed Bun’s Steamed Bun Invasion, Little Tang’s Soft Mist , Old Wei’s Winward Formation, who do these accounts belong to? For an old player like Old Wei, after playing for another two years, he’ll most likely retire again. Will he be taking his account with him? Will we wait until the time comes before talking about it? What if negotiations don’t go well? Without accounts, how will our team continue to compete?”

“In addition, Old Wei currently has twenty million on him and he’s already invested two million in materials for our team. When our team registers and forms a Club, how much of a percent share does he get for that investment?” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ll consider the two million as your pay for closing the deal.” Wei Chen waved his hands.

“Okay, I’ve already invested two million worth of materials into the team. When our team registers and forms a Club, how much of a percent share do I get for that investment?” Ye Xiu corrected himself.

“F*ck, you’re not nice at all.” Wei Chen said.

“None of it matters if we don’t get through the Challenger League. If we officially enter the pro scene through the Challenger League, all of this needs to be cleared up in order for our team to continue operating without us being there.” Ye Xiu said.

Wei Chen didn’t say anything. He had been a part of the pro scene before. He had witnessed these types of situations before with his own eyes. In the early years, a lot of ideas weren’t fully developed yet. Quite a few teams with potential relied on their passion alone to carry the team, but without proper management, all of them collapsed and had to leave the stage preemptively.

In truth, Wei Chen liked that sort of pure passion. At the time, he had quite a few conflicts with this sort of management. However, reality slapped him in his face. They could share trials and tribulations, but they couldn’t share the riches and honors. No one liked this sort of situation, but this was how everything was done. It would be hard to find even a single special exception.

With the issue laid bare, Wei Chen felt a bit awkward listening to it, but he knew that Ye Xiu was correct.

“Ahem!” Wei Chen was a former pro player and a senior, so he felt like he had to give an example. He cleared his throat and spoke: “What’s there to talk about? My account belongs to the team. This is how we’ll settle it.”

“I’ll do the same too!” Tang Rou immediately followed. Even though she didn’t have any experience in the pro scene, she was an understanding person. What Ye Xiu talked about wasn’t just something that happened in the pro scene either. It was a very normal occurrence. Tang Rou understood the reasoning behind it and didn’t hesitate to hand over her account to the team.

“What does that mean?” Steamed Bun was confused. Declaring his stance without understanding the situation was Steamed Bun’s style though. As a result, Steamed Bun quickly followed: “Well, you guys are all doing it, so I guess I’ll do the same too. My account now belongs to the team?”

“Good Steamed Bun!!” Wei Chen praised.

“Thanks!” Steamed Bun was excited.

“Boss, look. These accounts belong to you from now on.” Ye Xiu said to Chen Guo.

“Ah…..” Chen Guo didn’t know how to react.

“You’d better not scam us!” Ye Xiu said.

“What are you talking about?!” Chen Guo was furious. He dared to question her morals!

“I’ll let the team use these accounts for now. If you guys want to leave in the future, how could I trouble you guys?” Chen Guo expressed her goodwill.

“If you’re planning on managing the team, that isn’t something that you should be saying, no? If we suddenly come up one day and ask for these accounts, will you actually give them to us? When that time comes, what will the other player use to compete?” Ye Xiu said.

Who would have thought Chen Guo would actually laugh: “The question is will there ever be a day like that?”

Everyone happily handed their accounts to the team. It was symbolic of their trust in her. At the same time, her expression of goodwill was a symbol of her trust in everyone else. She believed that none of them would dare to do anything to trouble the team.

“That’s hard to say.” Ye Xiu just had to damage the beautiful scene: “There are some really shameless people here.”

“Yeah! You have to be extremely careful of him.” Wei Chen immediately stood up. The two started insulting each other again…...

Chen Guo wouldn’t bother with their trash talking. As the boss, she looked for Little Cold Hands in the group chat and talked about a few issues.

The discussion went smoothly.

Little Cold Hands had even more thoughts than Chen Guo. She couldn’t be blamed though. After all, apart from Little Cold Hands, her relationship with everyone else had developed through their friendship. With Chen Guo’s personality, she had realized a few issues, but she felt too embarrassed to talk about them.

As for Little Cold Hands, he talked in a very business-like manner. Chen Guo realized that a lot of issues were easily resolved. For example, in the Challenger League, everyone went in as a team, but most of the teams in the Challenger League had participated in it before. Getting into the pro scene? For most people, this was just a dream. Besides the Club teams regarding it as a revival tournament, very few teams had serious plans on actually becoming a pro team. The vast majority of teams were made up of good friends in the game. Before the tournament began, they would hastily form a team, register, and have a fun time.

Or sometimes, a few outstanding players would be noticed and then taken away by the pro teams. Up until now, no new teams had stepped into the pro scene through the Challenger League.

As a result, Chen Guo and Little Cold Hand seriously discussed the issue of whether or not they were considered a pro team, while they were participating in the Challenger League.

If they were considered a pro team, then the team would need contracts and wages. Under normal circumstances, most of the participants were there to have fun. Having wages was a joke. Who would beg their friend to come with them? And even pay him?

Chen Guo originally had this attitude towards Little Cold Hands, but then she thought about how difficult it had been for Ye Xiu to find Little Cold Hands. Although he wasn’t as precious as an actual pro player, Ye Xiu had been a spy in Tyrannical Ambition for such a long time and had played with many Clerics, yet even so, wasn’t Little Cold Hands the only one that he picked?

Little Cold Hands wasn’t good enough to be at the top, but he was much better than everyone below him. Saying he was irreplaceable would be too much of an overstatement, but saying he was useless would be treating Ye Xiu’s efforts as Unrivaled Super Hottie as a waste of time.

This issue was a lot harder to resolve with Little Cold Hands compared to Wei Chen and Steamed Bun. Those two were friends. If they were invited over, they would come. Chen Guo had attended to their living needs during this time. They didn’t care about what happened during the Challenger League, but what should she say to Little Cold Hands?

Chen Guo hesitated for a long time before saying anything. Everything went unusually smoothly. This was because Little Cold Hands was very clear on his own position. He knew the difference between heaven and earth. Before entering the pro scene, everyone was just like soy sauce to the pro teams. He accepted this fact, but the issue was that their team’s goal wasn’t to be soy sauce. The team had players, who definitely weren’t at a soy sauce level.

In the end, it was Little Cold Hands who reminded Chen Guo: you’d better not treat God Ye Qiu like soy sauce. If you treat him like soy sauce, the entire team will end up being soy sauce.

Clearly, Chen Guo was used to treating Ye Xiu as if he weren’t a big deal, but Little Cold Hands didn’t know that Ye Xiu had been inadvertently picked up by Chen Guo. She hadn’t gotten him through praying and burning incense. There was still some time before the Challenger League. Little Cold Hands was quite nervous that something would happen to the God.

Chen Guo thought about it and understood. A normal person would think that there was no need for Ye Qiu to form a team and enter the pro scene through something as risky as the Challenger League.

With Ye Qiu’s identity, if he wanted to return to the pro scene, he just needed to say the word and he would grab all sorts of attention. A one year break wouldn’t be enough of a deterrence. Finding a team to join wouldn’t be a problem. Wasn’t that a lot more reliable than going through something like the Challenger League?

As a result, Chen Guo felt like Little Cold Hands was being a thorn in the side, but in Little Cold Hand’s eyes, Ye Qiu was the thorn.

“You don’t need to worry about that. Ye Qiu is the person leading the team.” Chen Guo said to Little Cold Hands.

“Then he’s the main investor?” Little Cold Hands asked.

“Yes, yes.” Chen Guo hadn’t thought about this. Because of the question that Little Cold Hand had about his account, today became a day where everyone seriously discussed about everyone’s share in the team. Before, they had talked about Wei Chen’s investment in the team. With Little Cold Hand’s reminder, Chen Guo realized that Ye Qiu could be considered as an investor and his investment was very high. Apart from that, Wei Chen’s investment had been in the form of skill books. Both of these investments were being used right now.

Figuring out their share would really be troublesome!

Chen Guo didn’t really know how to calculate it, so she asked for Ye Xiu and Wei Chen to help. These two had both experienced the days when the first teams were being created, so they had some knowledge about starting a team. Chen Guo finally understood after listening to them. In the early days, there were a lot of teams, which relied purely on passion without any real funds. Having food to eat and a place to live was already considered not bad. No one had any additional wages. Their income was solely from what the team earned.

As for their share, it was based on their investment in the team. At that time, their investment was mainly just their accounts.

Chapter 644: Finals

Investing in an account and then buying it out were the standard steps that any Club would take during the initial stages of the Glory professional scene. However, those were no longer suited for use nowadays. This was because the difference between the current pro characters and online characters had become two extremes. The most a normal player could get would be a few Orange equipment no matter how hard they grinded. Who would invest in such a character, when all the characters in the pro scene had self-made equipment? It clearly wasn’t a possibility.

During those initial stages, having a top character meant you were a top-tier player in Glory, so of course people would invest in them. Now, no matter how skilled you were online, you would just be cannon fodder in the professional scene. Who would care about you? Even if you weren’t cannon fodder and had skills worthy of the professional scene, with how powerful the Clubs were, they still wouldn’t trade the account for stock instead of money. They would just purchase the account and finish the matter once and for all.

Frankly speaking, the initial stages of the pro scene were like this because everyone was poor. When everyone was rich, it would be best to avoid this kind of method. As for Ye Xiu and the others, they handed over their accounts to the team for free, which would save them a lot of trouble in the future. Chen Guo still wanted to talk about their future investments though.

“The Challenger League hasn’t even started yet. Isn’t it a bit early?” Ye Xiu expressed, “Once we enter the pro-scene and register, a professional from the Alliance will investigate our assets. It won’t be too late to decide it then.”

“Oh, I think I heard Loulan Slash talk about it before. It really is like that.” Chen Guo recalled.

It wasn’t like she had never managed anything before. She had chatted with Loulan Slash, who had just formed his team as well. It was just that, at the time, she had been frightened. Loulan Slash used his vast amount of wealth to make various maneuvers, making her feel apprehensive towards managing the team.

“Relax! There’s no need to worry about all of this. We just need players and accounts for now!” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh.” Chen Guo immediately felt relieved upon hearing Ye Xiu’s words.

As for Ye Xiu, after resolving any issues with Little Cold Hands, he had begun upgrading his Cleric account.

He originally had 4170 skill points. There were a total of 1220 points that could be obtained through the guide. Little Cold Hands was pretty lucky. If not, Ye Xiu wouldn’t have bothered upgrading the account at all. He would have just found and leveled up another Cleric account.

One, two, three…...

Ye Xiu completed the quests according to the guide. The account’s foundation was decent and his luck was quite good. The skill books quickly piled up. His luck was quite good.

“I’m done.”

Ye Xiu announced after consuming all of the skill books.

“How many?” Wei Chen carefully asked.

“Haha.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“What are you laughing about?” Wei Chen was puzzled.

“4925 points.” Ye Xiu announced.

“F*ck!” Wei Chen became pale. The skill points on this annoying guy’s account had even managed to surpass his Windward Formation. Furthermore, it was not too much or too little. It was only by a measly five points. Wei Chen wanted to cough up a mouthful of blood to cover up the five points.

“My luck’s pretty good, isn’t it?” Ye Xiu sighed.

“......” Wei Chen didn’t know what to say. It was the team’s account, after all. It was good to have more skill points. Wouldn’t it be petty of him if he cursed now? He had been a team captain before, so he had always prioritized the team before anything else. He wouldn’t ruin the team’s cohesiveness all because of his selfishness.

Within the group chat, Little Cold Hands was anxiously awaiting the results. As calm and cool-headed as he could be, he still hoped his account would have more skill points. The more points he had, the stronger he would become.

Soon after hearing Ye Xiu say 4925 points, Little Cold Hands was shocked.

“So high!” Little Cold Hands exclaimed. He wasn’t someone who didn’t play Glory. As a fan of Team Tyranny, he obviously knew that Han Wenqing’s character, Desert Dust, possessed the highest number of skill points in Glory with 4880, but now, his Little Cold Hands had actually surpassed the number one character in Glory. This was something completely out of his expectations.

“Little kid, you’d better work hard.” Wei Chen suddenly said with a mixture of emotions.

Little Cold Hand’s account already belonged to the team. Evidently, this wasn’t something that could be passed over by talking. Chen Guo had already spoken with Little Cold Hands and the latter would sign an agreement to transfer his account later. They would naturally return the account for Little Cold Hands to use afterwards.

His skill points had soared from 4170 to 4925 at once, increasing by 755 points total. This was a huge leap in terms of strength. Speaking of professional accounts, which were already around 4800 points, even if they got the points to the maximum, it would only be a 200 point difference. The scale of improvement couldn’t even be compared to Little Cold Hands. It was unknown if An Wenyi was too excited, but Ye Xiu had to call for him several times in the group chat before he finally responded.

Soon afterwards, Ye Xiu discussed with An Wenyi about his account. Naturally, they talked about the skills. Through his knowledge of An Wenyi’s playstyle, Ye Xiu gave some advice towards how he should allocate his skill points. Having a lot of skill points, but being unable to fully utilize them would just be a waste.

Naturally, no one would watch him give a lecture, so everyone went back to what they were previously doing. A day passed and the playoffs continued, the match between Blue Rain and Misty Rain progressed. Containing the word “rain” in their name was the only joke between them. Apart from the two matches against each other in the regular season, the two rarely interacted with each other. This made it difficult for the reporters because they couldn’t find anything interesting to talk about. In the end, they could only write about boring things like their preparations for the upcoming match.

Before the beginning of the match, the interviews between the two teams were also quite dull. There weren’t any overly bold statements. They just said typical things like they would try their best and such.

This was meant to be the semi finals where they had to fight for a spot in the finals, but it was miraculous that the two teams didn’t give off any sort of tense atmosphere. Upon that, the reports couldn’t help but blab about experiences or things like staying reserved and such.

The matches were, undoubtedly, at a high level, but it didn’t have too many twists and turns. This could be seen from the news release conference after the match. Blue Rain would say that their opponent was outstanding, but they had better luck that day. Whereas Misty Rain would say that they did pretty well, but the opponent performed even better.

Sparks were flying in the air! Where are the sparks!

The journalists were close to tears.

Chu Yunxiu, the trump card and team captain of Misty Rain was a girl, so she didn’t have an aggressive aura. As for Blue Rain, their captain Yu Wenzhou was a gentle guy, so he was always courteous and polite during interviews. All the questions were answered appropriately, but the journalists failed to pick anything out from his answers.

As for Huang Shaotian, although he owned a god-level character, that guy was able to stretch the topic from what he ate for breakfast to the shower from last night that turned cold and such during the interview, but everyone only wanted to know about things relative to the competition…...

Thankfully the match between Samsara and Tiny Herb was about the start on the second day, so they could finally find things to talk about between those two teams.

Since Tiny Herb was the champion from the previous season, it was obvious that they were planning to hold the title for another one; whereas Samsara had a high chance to win the championships. The clash between the two teams were evident. The writers finally had a place to release the pent up sentiment after holding it in yesterday. The semi finals between these two teams were treated like a final battle in the reports.

In the end, this match lived up to everyone’s expectations. The match between these two was much more vigorous than the previous games. The match fluctuated often, especially during the team battle, Samsara’s “One Man Team” style was presented distinctively. They were able to seize the victory in the end by using the sheer force of Zhou Zekai’s strong performance.

It was very easy to stir up the audience’s passion when a single player was able to decide the competition's situation. Every forum in Glory was filled with heated discussions that night. Zhou Zekai’s popularity continued to grow at an insane rate. He became the indisputable MVP of the second day. All comments agreed that it had become a generation for stars.

Yes, a generation for stars.

Wang Jiexi of Tiny Herb sacrificed his own style to change and blend in for his team’s sake. This was, undoubtedly, a strong notion for teamwork, but now, such a team was defeated by Samsara, whose style was based on a single player’s performance. Although the home and away regulations didn’t finalize after the first match, the result of this kind of individualistic heroism earned a lot of favor among the audience members. The only regret was that Zhou Zekai wasn’t able to say something arrogant and ambitious like many other players during the press conference following the match. He could only answer the interviewers with “yup, ah, oh”, which left this stage with endless regret.

The fixed picture afterwards caused the bystanders’ blood to boil with passion, but the hero they cheered for stared back at them with no emotion…… The scene was…… very contrasting.

The burning zeal of this day had passed and it returned to the peaceful match between Blue Rain and Misty Rain. Blue Rain came out as the victor. After the match, Misty Rain expressed their blessings to their victorious opponent and Blue Rain expressed their gratitudes to the respective side. Blue Rain took the lead upon entering the finals.

As for Samsara and Tiny Herb, under countless of expectations, Zhou Zekai didn’t let anyone down. In the end, Tiny Herb, who tried to defend their championship, was eliminated.

The finals for the Eighth Season in the professional league was now finalized to be between Samsara and Blue Rain.

If Samsara won the championships, they would become the fourth champion team in the league’s history.

If Blue Rain were to win, they would receive their second trophy.

During the break before the finals, all sorts of reports were spread around. It was the finals. Even if there weren’t any gimmicks between the two teams, they had to find something to talk about. Let alone that there were many things that could be said between the two teams.

After receiving major attention after the four matches in the playoffs, Samsara’s skewed skill points had been detected early on. There were all sorts of predictions online and it was certain that all the clubs were having attentive research for this matter, but they wouldn’t reveal what they had discovered.

Speaking of the two teams’ players, or precisely, the two trump players, Zhou Zekai and Huang Shaotian. Although their classes were different, the two were always compared. This was because the two player’s style were complete opposites.

Chapter 645: Excessive Improvement

Zhou Zekai and Huang Shaotian were complete opposites of each other, whether that was on stage or off stage.

Off stage, one of them was so quiet that people wanted to take a stick and pry his mouth open, while the other was so noisy that people wanted to take a stick and beat his mouth shut. Onstage, Zhou Zekai was the absolute core of the team and the main attacker. Where ever he was, that was where the most intense battle was taking place. Using his firepower, he pushed his team forward.

As for Huang Shaotian? Team Blue Rain’s strategies didn’t completely revolve around him. He was like a specter wandering the battlefield, giving the feeling that he didn’t exist. However, every move he made would leave a rain of blood behind. This was his opportunistic style. His numbers weren’t impressive at all, but when looking at the content of a match as a whole, his existence could not be ignored because without him, the match would have ended with a completely different result. The other part of him, which definitely showed he existed, dominated the entire field.

People could easily compare the similarities between the two players..

At the same time, people could easily compare the differences between the two players as well.

Huang Shaotian had become famous earlier than Zhou Zekai, but after Zhou Zekai became famous, these two names were frequently spoken about together.

However, as of now, most people considered Zhou Zekai to be a bit better. After all, an opportunist like Huang Shaotian required a precondition: an opportunity.

If his opponents never gave him that sort of opportunity, his presence instantly diminished. This wasn’t something that had never happened before.

During the match, it would seem as if he didn’t exist, but those familiar with his style would wait for him to suddenly jump out and give a fright. However, when the match ended, everyone realized: What! This time, he really didn’t exist!

Finding an opportunity was just one matter. Seizing the opportunity was another. Even for a master like Huang Shaotian, he couldn’t guarantee that he could seize every opportunity that passed by. There would be moments where he did nothing, and with his style, if he failed to grasp the opportunity, he would be useless during the match.

Because of the weaknesses in his style, Huang Shaotian was less consistent than Zhou Zekai, so most people considered him slightly worse. However, Huang Shaotian had a championship title under his belt. At that time, he played the decisive role in their victory, so no one completely counted him out.

This time, these two Gods would be meeting up in the finals. Whoever won would not only defeat his opponent, but would also take the championship cup as proof. This debate would finally come to an end here.

All of the fans had been waiting for an entire year for this day to come. The fans of the both teams had done all sorts of things to support their teams. The game was the most direct way way of confrontation. The two guilds clashed with each other constantly, making the guild leaders exhausted from their efforts.

Yes, they were exhausted.

Because the day before the finals, any conflict would erupt into an all-out war! Peacefully settle it and retreat? This was how the Club guilds usually handled conflicts, but it didn’t suit the particular occasion. At this moment, they needed to show their strength. The team needed to, as well as the team’s fans. Even if they wouldn’t gain any benefits, they absolutely couldn’t back down.

Wei Chen was the group leader for Samsara’s fifth group. This period of time hadn’t been easy for him either. He had very little free time to begin with. For the past few days, as soon as he got online, the guild leader would call for him and then have him rush towards a certain location. In an intense battle, how could there be any shortage of elite players?

But because of the crises during this particular period of time, Wei Chen was being noticed by Samsara. In their eyes, Wei Chen’s ability to lead was very high. Even amidst the chaos, he was sharp and decisive. Using a talent like him to lead teams in dungeons was a waste. He should be used to fight for wild bosses! That was a battlefield between players. If they didn’t utilize such talents, wouldn’t that be a waste?

The upper echelons of Samsara discussed with each other.

A portion of them believed that he should be used to fight for wild bosses. Another portion of them still didn’t fully trust him.

However, these doubts were eventually dispelled after a bunch of reverse reasoning. Samsara’s core members discussed this issue and unanimously felt that sending such an expert to be a spy was way too wasteful. If he were placed in any other guild, he would, without a doubt, be taking the lead in the wild boss fights. What could he gain from being a spy?

Samsara’s core members pondered over this question. They couldn’t think of any reason for an expert like Wei Chen to be a spy for such a long period of time. He couldn’t be trying to vie for the guild leader position, right? It was impossible. The main guild leader was appointed by the Club. It wasn’t something that one’s performance or the public opinion could decide.

Samsara’s core members couldn’t think of any other reasons. The probability of Wei Chen being a spy was very small. The guild would always considered the value of a spy in terms of the competition between guilds. After getting rid of their doubts towards Wei Chen, his value became even greater than the potential risks.

As a result, during the restless days before the finals, Wei Chen was appointed group leader for Samsara’s second elite group.

In a wild boss fight, guilds usually dispatched more than two groups. The first group would be led by the guild leader. This was just a matter of the guild leader’s authority. As for the second group, their chances of participating in a wild boss fight were about the same as the first group. For Wei Chen to reach this position, he had reached the peak of his career as a spy.

However, after becoming the second group’s leader, it wasn’t easy to find a place for his friends. The members of the first and second group weren’t randomly placed. Even though the skill levels of his friends weren’t bad under the guidance of Wei Chen, they still weren’t better than the top players of these Club guilds. These were the top experts in the game. In terms of skill level, they were better than Wei Chen’s friends, and they far surpassed them in terms of equipment.

“What should I do?” Wei Chen asked Ye Xiu. His plans couldn’t keep up with the changes. His rise in position far exceeded his expectations.

“Second group…… that’s not easy to control.” Ye Xiu said.

“Exactly! I can’t get any of my people into the group either. If I wanted to do a sudden betrayal, it wouldn’t be convenient anymore! If I give an unreasonable order, let alone the group not following my order, it might expose me too.” Wei Chen said.

“Don’t worry. I didn’t say it completely depended on you. You’ll just be coordinating with us. We have a few helpers already. We’re about ready to act now.” Ye Xiu said.

“Where are the helpers?” Wei Chen asked.

“Over there.” Ye Xiu nudged his head to point them out.

“Just those two?” Wei Chen was a bit speechless. Ye Xiu had pointed to Tang Rou and Steamed Bun. They had both just entered the Heavenly Domain. With the huge experience rewards in the Heavenly Domain, Tang Rou had reached Level 70. She had a maxed out five thousand skill points and was figuring out how to allocate them.

Steamed Bun’s Steamed Bun Invasion wasn’t max leveled yet, but with his skill, a level or two difference wouldn’t make too much of a difference. Even though their skill levels far surpassed normal players, if they went to join a wild boss fight with countless players, wouldn’t their influence be too little?

“Little Cold Hands can come with us too.” Ye Xiu said. After upgrading Little Cold Hand’s account, they had sent it back to him.

“Couldn’t you at least get five people?” Wei Chen said.

“Don’t we also have our boss?” Ye Xiu said.

“Her?” Wei Chen said.

“What about me?” Chen Guo raised her eyebrow.

“To put it plainly, you kind of suck.” Wei Chen wasn’t scared of Chen Guo’s threat. He spat out the truth, not giving her any face.

“Better than nothing!” Ye Xiu also said the truth and didn’t give her any face.

“You two can both go die!!” Chen Guo was furious!

“So now we have five.” Ye Xiu said.

“Five! Wow, how amazing.” Wei Chen nodded his head.

“Could your friends help us out too?” Ye Xiu asked.

“It wasn’t easy for them to get into Samsara. Isn’t that just asking for them to be exposed as spies?” Wei Chen said.

“You can use your original accounts. Hasn’t the danger passed already?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Oh, those accounts never regained their experience!” Wei Chen said. At that time, they had ravaged the guilds and had been killed many many times in return. Who knew how many levels these accounts had gone down by. In any case, if they were ten levels below the max level, they couldn’t come. Even if it were ten levels, going from 60 to 70 wasn’t a matter of a few days, even in the Heavenly Domain.

“Or I could have them leave. In any case, with my current position, they can’t really help me anymore.” Wei Chen said.

“That’s hard to say. Getting in wasn’t easy. If we can have them there, we should let them stay there. If we need helpers, you can send them a batch to use!” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s fine too.” Wei Chen nodded his head. Even though he didn’t have any on him, he had more than enough money to buy them.

“Are there still any wild bosses that haven’t spawned this week?” Ye Xiu asked.

“How would I know? I just got the position.” Wei Chen said.

“If one spawns, we’ll immediately act and try our luck!” Ye Xiu said.

“With just you lot? Don’t joke. Even if no one touches you guys, you guys won’t be able to gain the boss’s aggro. How much damage can three people output?” Wei Chen said.

“Three is too few. We’ll find someone to collaborate with.” Ye Xiu said.

“Who?”

“Heavenly Justice!” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 646: Let’s Steal a Boss

“What an unsurprising answer!” Wei Chen commented on Ye Xiu’s reply. From an overall view of the Heavenly Domain, only Heavenly Justice’s infamous name could match Lord Grim’s.

All of the other Club guilds had suffered under Ye Xiu’s hands starting from the tenth server and stretched all the way to the Heavenly Domain. No one would feel at ease if they wanted to collaborate again. Only Heavenly Justice had kept good relations with him the entire time. They constantly worked together in their mutual interest. Furthermore, Loulan Slash spoke for Heavenly Justice. The guild leaders of other Club guilds were just young household members who went out for work. In order to profit, they were willing to do whatever was necessary. On the other hand, with Loulan Slash’s status, if he mercilessly committed terrible acts just for a boss, he would stand out too much.

With the decision made, Ye Xiu contacted Loulan Slash. He had the game open on his computer, and checked to see that Loulan Slash was online, so he messaged him: “What are you busy with?”

Ye Xiu had used this greeting who knew how many times, and he never thought of changing it up.

“Nothing really. Ha ha!” Loulan Slash replied.

“Let’s go steal a boss!” Ye Xiu went straight to the point.

“Which boss?” Loulan Slash asked.

“Wild boss!” Ye Xiu said.

“Where?”

“How would I know? You don’t have that type of information?” Ye Xiu asked.

Loulan Slash felt awkward: “What type of situation is this?”

“Oh, is Heavenly Justice developing smoothly in regards to wild bosses?” Ye Xiu asked.

“It’s so-so……” Loulan Slash said.

“What does so-so even mean? How many bosses did you get last week?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Three……”

“Three is so-so?! You’re not modest at all!” Ye Xiu sighed. The Heavenly Domain was huge. There were so many maps and if each map had a wild boss, Ye Xiu didn’t know how many wild bosses spawned per week. However, he was certain that three was a very small number. Calling that number so-so was not being modest at all.

“That’s so-so for us.” Loulan Slash forced a smile.

Ye Xiu was happy. It wasn’t that he was happy at their misfortune. Heavenly Justice clearly wasn’t too successful at obtaining bosses, to which Ye Xiu wasn’t surprised. The Club guilds had a much stronger foundation. Just by comparing their guild storages, the average quality of equipment in the Club guilds was certainly higher than the average quality of equipment in Heavenly Justice. Better equipment meant more strength. The weaker forces would obviously have a harder time getting wild bosses. If they couldn’t get wild bosses, Ye Xiu could use this as a bargaining chip. Otherwise, if they already won bosses easily, there would be no reason to negotiate at all!

“I’ll help you. Let’s collaborate. How about we split the drops fifty-fifty?” Ye Xiu proposed.

“If we can actually get the wild bosses, then that won’t be a problem.” Loulan Slash agreed. His guild could only successfully steal three bosses across the span of a week. How could things get any worse? He was willing to agree with anything Ye Xiu suggested. Try everything when you’re desperate.

“Good. If you learn anything, let me know!” Ye Xiu said.

“No problem.” Loulan Slash said.

Ye Xiu closed the chat window. Not long afterwards, Loulan Slash messaged him. Ye Xiu wasn’t too surprised at the quick response. Wild bosses spawned randomly. In this business, every second, starting from midnight on Monday, mattered. You had to be ready to go into battle at any moment. The elite groups of the Club guilds were responsible for the wild bosses and it wasn’t an easy task. They weren’t professional gamers. When a boss appeared, they had to act immediately, as if it were an emergency.

When Ye Xiu looked at Loulan Slash’s message, he discovered that it wasn’t about a boss, but about the skill book guide.

“Oh, that. It’s gone. It’s already been sold.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ah…… is that so? That’s too bad.” Loulan Slash was a bit regretful, but he wasn’t too surprised. At that time, he was very clear about why Ye Xiu had come to him. Even though he had rejected the offer, he knew that there would certainly be buyers. In the end, Ye Xiu didn’t look for him again, so he guessed that Ye Xiu had successfully sold it. Loulan Slash simply confirmed his guess and now he didn’t need to think about it anymore.

The two didn’t say anything more and went on with their own business. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim wasn’t max leveled yet, so he naturally spent most of his time leveling. As he walked around, the Heavenly Domain really was chaotic! Samsara and Blue Rain didn’t only fight with each other as a guild. Their fans often argued with each other on their own basis too.

Apart from these two teams, Tiny Herb and Misty Rain weren’t happy after being eliminated either. If they received any sort of taunting from the winners, they wouldn’t endure it. There were also the teams that had been eliminated in the first round. No fan would feel happy about their own team being eliminated and would often want to gain back some face through the game. If there was nothing to dispute about, they would find something to dispute about.

The Heavenly Domain didn’t have any safe zones apart from cities. A player could kill another play anywhere at any time. Everyone was on edge because of the playoffs.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim hadn’t even left the city yet when Loulan Slash messaged him again. This time, a boss had appeared, but when Ye Xiu looked at the name Sewer King, he suddenly lost interest.

Sewer King Lookashoo. His name sounded domineering. King! But in reality, he was just some rogue in the sewers. It’s not like Ye Xiu had anything against him, it was just that this boss was only Level 55.

There were materials that they needed from low-leveled bosses, but Ye Xiu didn’t have many helpers. The amount of time and effort that they could put in was very limited, so he hoped for a high-leveled boss. Even if they didn’t have any low-leveled boss materials, they could use high-leveled boss materials to trade.

Wild boss materials were difficult to buy, but trading for other materials wasn’t that hard. Each team had different classes and different equipment that they used, so they each required different materials. All materials were welcome, but they would need some materials more than others. The market for trading uncommon materials for other uncommon materials was very active.

With this sort of background, no matter what they actually needed, Level 70 bosses were always more valuable than Level 55 bosses.

Unfortunately, Loulan Slash only reported a Level 55 boss. Even though it was a bit regretful, it was better than nothing. Ye Xiu called for Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Chen Guo. They headed towards Loulan Slash’s meeting location. As for Wei Chen, he hadn’t received any message from Samsara. It wasn’t that Samsara didn’t know, but it was more likely that this Level 55 boss wasn’t something that the main guild’s second elite group was needed to deal with.

Lookashoo was the Sewer King. The sewers were a city facility, so it wasn’t in some desolate area. Instead, the sewers had turned into a leveling area at Heshin City. Ye Xiu and the three others found a teleport location in the nearest cities to them and teleported to Heshin City. They saw quite a few players heading towards a single direction and all of them had guild tags above their heads.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had a guild tag too. Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and Steamed Bun Invasion were all under Heavenly Justice’s name, mainly for the stat points and benefits of being a part of a guild.

“There are a lot of people already!” Ye Xiu sighed. The top guilds had their own methods for killing wild bosses. On Monday, everyone would be spread out all across the Heavenly Domain. Every time a wild boss was killed, they naturally wouldn’t search that area again. As for the bosses that hadn’t been cleared yet, there would always be guild members wandering in that area. This wasn’t just a game. It was important work for the Clubs.

“Shouldn’t we…… keep a low-profile?” Chen Guo was the crowds of people and was worried that Lord Grim’s name would stand out too much. The amount of attention towards him was much higher than Sewer King Lookashoo.

“Mm, low profile is better.” Ye Xiu agreed. They took a roundabout route and messaged Loulan Slash about their situation.

“There are quite a few people.” Loulan Slash replied. His group had arrived earlier than Ye Xiu’s had.

They naturally knew about the boss’ exact location, so they moved towards that location. This Level 55 city didn’t have many players inside, but the closer they got to the location, the more people they saw. Ye Xiu wasn’t too interested in this Level 55 boss, but the Club guilds still considered it important work.

“How many guilds are present?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I’ve seen five so far.” Loulan Slash said.

“Have they started fighting the boss yet?” Ye Xiu asked.

“They should be starting soon.” Loulan Slash said. Level 55 bosses weren’t difficult to beat for the Level 70 Heavenly Domain players, so they usually wouldn’t waste time facing the boss. Once there were enough people, they would start attacking. Beating the boss was easy, so whoever started first held the advantage.

“Ah, they’ve started!” Loulan Slash reported.

“Which guild?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Blue Brook Guild.” Loulan Slash said.

“They have a lot of energy after making it into the finals!” Ye Xiu replied, “We should move out too.”

“Where are you? I still don’t see you.” Loulan Slash said.

“We’re not there yet. They’ve started, so you should start too. Put out damage and kill others if there are any opportunities.” Ye Xiu said.

“What about you?”

“We’ll cut them off en-route.” Ye Xiu said. He called out to Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Chen Guo. They rushed forward and just happened to bump into two Blue Brook Guild players.

“How lucky!” Ye Xiu said.

The two players saw Lord Grim and were startled too. When they heard Ye Xiu speak, they thought he had something to say, but in the next second, several attacks shot towards them and one of them died immediately. The other one was alarmed. He hastily tried to defend himself, but the brave Steamed Bun Invasion had already pounced on him.

The two Blue Brook Guild players instantly fell. Ye Xiu led the three towards the sewers to continue player hunting. The guilds were still sending their players towards the boss, so they all arrived at different times. The players hadn’t gathered together into large groups yet, so the four of them blocked off small parties. They worked especially hard against Blue Brook Guild’s players.

The boss fight had already started down in the sewers. The guilds didn’t have enough people, so they were carefully fighting the boss, while waiting for their reinforcements to arrive. However, the guilds soon received information about their players being ambushed.

“Who?” They obviously had to ask this question. When they heard the answer, they turned pale with fright. Lord Grim had been quiet for a long time. Why did he start acting up again all of a sudden?

“F*ck!” The person leading Blue Brook Guild’s side slammed his keyboard, “Why am I so unlucky?”

Chapter 647: Are you seeking your own death?

Blue River or Blue Bridge Spring Snow, as he was more commonly known as in the Heavenly Domain, had been pretty depressed after all the ruckus in the tenth server. The top guilds had finally gotten back on track after Lord Grim left for the Heavenly Domain.

Although Team Samsara had the most momentum this year, the one at the top was still Team Blue Rain. Guild Samara relied on their momentum in the pro scene to gain popularity among the new players in the tenth server. However, first place was still first place. Blue Brook Guild’s development in the tenth server continued smoothly.

Managing a guild in a normal server seemed to be less glamourous than working in the Heavenly Domain, but in reality, to those in the Clubs who treated the game as their job, it was a more important role than being another top expert or elite group leader in the Heavenly Domain. Having experienced the hardships of starting up a guild in a new server, Blue River was tired of all the various schemes and competition between the guilds. After Blue Brook Guild finally stepped onto the right track in the tenth server, Blue River immediately went to Changing Spring and resigned. He would much rather give up the better position of a normal server’s guild leader and just be an elite expert in the Heavenly Domain.

Changing Spring obviously couldn’t force someone to do something that he didn’t want to do, so after handing over the account for the tenth server guild leader, Blue River became the Blade Master Blue Bridge Spring Snow once again.

Tired of all the fighting between guilds, Blue River didn’t even participate much in wild boss fights, the most direct form of guild competitions. He spent his days leisurely bringing teams into dungeons.

Blue River had given up something that many would fight for, but as one of the veterans in Blue Brook Guild, he still enjoyed his fair share of respect from his fellow guild members. On the other hand, even though he no longer actively involved himself with PvP anymore, if there were some kind of emergency, he wouldn’t sit back and do nothing.

Once Team Blue Rain got into the finals in the first place, the fans of the eliminated teams along with Team Samara often clashed with Blue Brook Guild. Any kind of small argument would quickly evolve into a full-scale war. Being active in the Heavenly Domain, Blue River had been dragged into plenty of said fights. The good thing was that these battles were based entirely on emotions, so they didn’t require a lot of effort to deal with.

Still, these sort of conflicts and wild bosses had to be handled properly. Upon receiving the news of the appearance of the Sewer King Lookashoo, the main guild leader Changing Spring immediately searched for any core members nearby. Someone from the core of the guild had to lead the wild boss fight.

Blue River couldn’t be any closer to the boss when Changing Spring sent out the rallying call, so he answered it since he wasn’t shameless enough to pretend to be offline. The guild had absolute trust in Blue River. Therefore, he immediately became the commander for this battle.

Even though he hadn’t done this kind of work in a while, Blue River wasn’t unfamiliar with it. Thinking back about it, he had once been cannon fodder too. Over time, he had climbed up, from main attacker to team leader to group leader to the overall commander for an entire operation, and finally he was tired of doing it. As he sighed incessantly, his people had arrived and started acting already. For low level bosses like this, the competition was much more direct.

Blue River didn’t think anything strange would happen when fighting for a wild boss, but something just had to happen. Shortly after the boss fight had started, Blue River received reports that the people who were rushing over here were being killed before they could arrive. He didn’t pay much attention to it, until he noticed the names mentioned.

Why am I so unlucky?

Hadn’t that guy gone into hiding? How come the moment I show up he appears again?! Slaughtering anyone he sees? Why is he so unruly?!

But was killing players on the way unruly? Not exactly. To get the boss, the guilds would use all means necessary, so there were no rules to speak of. There were only tricks that couldn’t be carried out, and no tricks that couldn’t be thought of.

The top guilds rarely tried to kill players who were en route. It wasn’t because they didn’t want to do that, but it was because it had never yielded good results in the past.

The biggest reason was because they didn’t have Ye Xiu’s level of skill.

The four-person team led by Ye Xiu consisted of Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Chen Guo. They overwhelmed any teams with a similar number of people. They would slaughter one group swiftly and then immediately move onto another. For any other normal player, they wouldn’t be able to move on from one group to another so quickly, even in an ambush. Without the advantage of numbers, there was only 50% chance for a successful interception. If you wanted an advantage in numbers, then you would have to put in more people. This would result in the other side putting in more manpower as well. In the end, the boss fight would spiral out of control on the way. Most importantly, even if the conflict got out of control like this, neither side would gain an advantage.

Ye Xiu’s team, on the other hand, was another matter entirely. With their vastly superior skill, he and his group could guarantee an easy 100% win rate. There were few players dwelling around Heshin City normally and most people arriving had the same destination in mind, so they were all taking the same route. As Ye Xiu’s group swept through the area, players from various guilds were sent back to their respawn location. It wasn't until they saw everyone else respawn with them that they noticed something wasn’t right. The effects of their ruthless slaughtering was clear, when the four people finally slaughtered their way to the boss. Every guilds’ troops had been scattered around loosely except for Heavenly Justice, whose organized and complete lineup made the other guilds look even more miserable.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything upon arrival and led the other three straight into the fray, but they didn't even target the boss - instead, they went straight for the players. Noticing that the “lord” had arrived, Loulan Slash sent support in right away. With support, especially the help of Clerics, Ye Xiu and the others became even more brutal. They swung their blades indiscriminately against anyone who didn’t belong to Heavenly Justice.

“What a vicious way to snatch a boss…” Loulan Slash sighed as he watched the other guilds fall into complete disarray. Ye Xiu looked as if he wanted to clean the entire field! How domineering!

The guilds only had so many people and none of them could stop the four effectively. Cooperation, on the other hand, wasn’t something that could be achieved easily among them.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was charging around, when a blade came out of nowhere, trying to interrupt his offense. Based on the timing of that attack, it was clearly one of rare strikes in this huge mess that had a clear purpose. Lord Grim jumped back to dodge it and swung his view towards the attacker.

The team was extremely short on people, so Ye Xiu would pay extra attention to those with exceptional skill. When he turned around, he found that the attacker’s ID was Blue Bridge Spring Snow. What a familiar name!

Where have I heard this name before? Ye Xiu arrived at the answer after some time with the help of the guild tag “Blue Brook” before Blue Bridge Spring Snow’s ID. Without it, Ye Xiu probably wouldn’t have remembered.

“Hm? Isn’t this… what’s his name’s account? How has Blue River been doing recently?” Ye Xiu finally said something other than a battle shout: a greeting.

“ I’m Blue River…” The opponent replied bitterly.

“Oh! It’s you! So you’ve returned to the Heavenly Domain? Then don’t you know who I am? Are you seeking your own death?” Ye Xiu asked.

Blue River was on the verge of bursting into tears. Did he want to come? No! However, in his current position and facing such adversity, he had no choice but to stand up and do something.

“2 o’clock!” But before Blue River could answer his question, Ye Xiu sped off towards the 2 o’clock direction after giving a shout.

“Stop running!” Blue River chased right after him with a Triple Slash, but Lord Grim easily dodged with a side step. At the same time, Thousand Chance Umbrella transformed into a spear with a shake of his hand and pierced straight toward Blue River’s character with a Circle Swing, slamming its victim into the ground.

“Run? This is called strategy. If you can’t appreciate it, then don’t comment.” Ye Xiu commented, leading the other three away in the 2 o’clock direction.

Indeed, those who didn’t understand the situation well would think that Ye Xiu and the others were just randomly killing people. All their slaughtering was planned out by Ye Xiu with deliberation. Every action had a purpose behind it: to create openings for Loulan Slash to snatch the boss.

Ye Xiu had told Loulan Slash before hand. A few players from Heavenly Justice would help out Ye Xiu and his group, while the others would take the boss.

Despite being slammed into the ground, Blue River not only got right back up, but he also gave chase immediately. There was no way he could just lay on the ground and pretend to be dead.

“Again? Hurry up and leave with your people. There is no way you’ll get this boss.” Ye Xiu sighed at Blue River, who was chasing after him.

Blue River didn't answer. Instead he simply pointed his blade at Lord Grim again. However, before he could reach his target, a flying kick sent him stumbling away and followed by a storm of fists and kicks mixed with some bricks. These were clearly the skills of a Brawler and the attacker was none other than Steam Bun Invasion.

“Kiddo! I’m beating you up to save you! If the boss is being so kind to you, then you have to appreciate it! If you make him mad, the consequences will be very severe!” Steam Bun lectured while beating Blue River. Blue River’s skill level was among top of the regular players and he had plenty of experience. Even though Steamed Bun was improving very quickly, he couldn’t render experts like Blue River completely powerless yet. This one-sided battle only took place because of Steamed Bun’s ambush. Before Blue River could even pick himself back up, Steam Bun overwhelmed him with a wave of chaotic attacks.

Steamed Bun had incredible mechanical skill. When he got the first hit, there was no chance for Blue River to escape the following onslaught. After being slammed into the ground by Lord Grim, he was now being kicked around like ball on the ground. There was no words that could describe the depression that Blue River felt. Looking around, he realized that all the people from Blue Brook were nowhere to be found, so there was no support.

The more he thought about it, the more he admired himself. Where did I find the bravery to charge at all four of them? Did I really come here to kill myself?

Chapter 648: Boss Spawn

Steamed Bun didn’t kill Blue Bridge Spring Snow. Ye Xiu called for him to come over, so he followed after the team to continue with their tactic.

Ye Xiu’s tactical intentions were very clear and precise. He didn’t plan on completely controlling the situation. He just wanted to create chaos amongst all of the other guilds besides Heavenly Justice, leaving them as the sole guild that still had their calm and clear-headedness. They would be able to smoothly execute their plan by taking advantage of the chaos to snatch the boss.

The other guilds were having trouble facing Ye Xiu’s team. How could they still have the energy to deal with Heavenly Justice?

Blue Bridge Spring Snow once again got up from the ground. He turned around and watched the chaotic battle going on. He opened up the list of names in his group. He could still see Blue Brook Guild members alive from this list, but he couldn’t even see half of his people on the field. Blue River didn’t know what to do in this situation. He could only continue charging forward recklessly. Cheering on the sidelines and pretending to be dead didn’t suit his personality…...

“How’s the boss going?” Ye Xiu messaged Loulan Slash.

He had kept a clear mind from start to finish. The chaos that they had brought to the field would only last for awhile. During this time, Heavenly Justice needed to establish their advantage over the boss. This was extremely crucial.

“Don’t worry!” Loulan Slash replied. His skill level was much higher than normal players. Even Steamed Bun or Tang Rou wouldn’t have an easy time against Loulan Slash. Because Loulan Slash and the rest of his team were unrivalled in the game, they thought that once they entered the professional scene, they would immediately be able to be a runner up for the championship title. Otherwise, if they could only barely win against normal players and thought that they had the strength to be champions, it would only indicate their stupidity.

After dispatching a few of his players to support Ye Xiu’s team, everyone else focused on the boss. He and his team members were very noticeable compared to normal players.

“Hurry up.” Ye Xiu saw that the guild players were continuously streaming in. As the enemy numbers rose, the effects of their killing would diminish.

“Understood.”

After reading Loulan Slash’s reply, he noticed a sword light flying towards him. Ye Xiu had Lord Grim dodge. He turned his head helplessly: “When did you become so shameless?”

Shameless????

Blue River was about to go crazy! What type of evaluation was that?! Everyone was fighting for the boss! You’re causing chaos everywhere. I’m attacking you for a completely logical and proper reason and yet you call me shameless?

“If you really want to die, there’s nothing I can do to stop you!” Ye Xiu sighed.

“Senior, leave him to me!” Steamed Bun shouted as he threw a brick.

This time, Blue River was prepared. How could he let Steamed Bun surprise him so easily? He stepped to the side and countered with a slash of his sword, but another brick smashed into his face.

Steamed Bun obviously couldn’t throw a second brick so quickly. Skills had cooldowns. This brick had been thrown by Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. Unspecialized characters could still use this Brawler skill.

Blue River was stunned by this brick. His character couldn’t move, but he could still hear. He heard Ye Xiu lecture Steamed Bun: “Steamed Bun, this is a team battle, not a 1v1. We have to attack as a group and use the quickest method to kill the targets. No matter how weak the opponent is, you can’t get careless.”

Blue River really wanted to die!

He was weak compared to a God, but he was still one of Blue Brook Guild’s Five Great Experts! In the Heavenly Domain, whether it was in terms of equipment or skills, he was at the peak! How could he stand being called weak!

Then, he heard Steamed Bun reply: “Senior, that makes a lot of sense. Tang Rou and I will go up together.”

The three second stun from the brick cleared up. Blue River immediately wanted to move, but the other side had listened to their teacher’s lesson and moved forward together. No matter how skilled Blue River was, he wouldn’t be able to defend against the both of them at the same time. Steamed Bun and Tang Rou quickly killed him. Ye Xiu said, soon after Blue River died: “His equipment is pretty good. Make sure you take any items that he dropped…….” Blue River completely collapsed after that.

After hearing Ye Xiu’s reminder, Blue River saw that he had dropped equipment. When he respawned, he immediately opened his inventory. He hadn’t dropped just one equipment, but two: his shoulder piece and his necklace equips.

No one would be completely unfazed upon losing equipment, even a top-tier expert like Blue River. And because of his high skill level, he rarely died, so his equipment didn’t often drop. As a result, when he lost equipment, the feeling of loss was even worse.

But against a God, how could he say anything after being crushed? Blue River could only sigh at his poor luck. Soon afterwards, he messaged the players still alive: “Retreat!”

His heroic efforts made him feel like he had already tried his best. With his skill level, he could figure out Ye Xius intentions. He tried to block him, but wasn’t that the same as trying to stop a train with a mantis? Continuing on was pointless.

Blue Brook Guild withdrew. Blue River reported back to Changing Spring.

“It’s fine. It’s just a Level 55 boss.” What a rare sight! Changing Spring typed a few words to console him. Changing Spring felt it was shame that Blue River suddenly stopped working in the normal servers and didn’t want to PvP in the Heavenly Domain. In this day and age, it was very hard to find high skilled players. High skilled and reliable players were even more difficult to find. Blue River was undoubtedly one such person. If not, Changing Spring wouldn’t have picked him to lead Blue Brook Guild in the new server. However, this new server unexpectedly caused their guild to lose a valuable asset. Changing Spring was unhappy, but also helpless towards Blue River’s condition. He could only hope for his mentality to return to normal. The fight for the boss didn’t go well, but Changing Spring obviously wouldn’t scold him. He had to console him at this moment.

“Sigh, Lord Grim suddenly popped up and made a mess.” Blue River said. If it weren’t for Lord Grim, Blue Brook Guild probably would have gotten the boss.

“!!!” Changing Spring was shocked. He clearly hadn’t received any information about Lord Grim suddenly showing up in this boss battle. He had went into hiding for so long that everyone had almost forgotten about his existence. Of course, they would never forget about him, but because he hadn’t done anything in a long time, they pretended like he had disappeared. In the past, they had attempted to suppress this God, but time after time proved that the correct thing to do was pray and hope this God wouldn’t cause trouble for them.

The expenses invested into suppressing one person had been very large and the results were miniscule, so no one really wanted to do it.

Unless the God provoked them, they wouldn’t take the initiative to bring trouble for themselves. This God had been quiet for a long period of time, so everyone was able to live together in harmony, but now, he suddenly popped up again. In this instant, Changing Spring had an ominous foreboding. After coming out of hiding, he probably wouldn’t be going back into hiding so fast.

The guilds had predicted this God to come out sooner or later. He was planning on forming a team, which directly conflicted with the interests of the Club guilds, so they would have to clash sooner or later. Why else did they want to suppress Lord Grim, when he entered the Heavenly Domain?

Unfortunately, they failed to suppress him and eventually settled the matter by leaving him alone. Now, he had appeared again! A true boss has respawned!

Changing Spring’s worries weren’t over yet! A message on QQ popped up.

Changing Spring looked and saw that it was a message from the discussion group, which had been quiet after Lord Grim went into hiding. It was the discussion group between the top guilds about how to handle Lord Grim.

Changing Spring checked the message. The person who sent the message was Tyrannical Ambition’s Jiang You. He only said five words: “Did you hear about it?”

Changing Spring could feel the seriousness in these five words. He was certain that the others felt it too because Herb Garden’s Arisaema replied: “F*ck.”

“He’s back……”

“All of us knew he’d return eventually.”

“Sigh……”

“There’s a difference this time. A total of four people have reached the Heavenly Domain from the tenth server. All of them are his people.”

“And all of them entered without being max leveled too.”

“How did he find all of the experts in that server?”

The guilds clearly hadn’t stopped paying attention to Lord Grim’s side. They just hadn’t said anything about it.

“I didn’t see the Ghostblade though.” Someone said.

“He’ll appear sooner or later.”

“What do we do now?”

“What’s the situation so far?”

“What else? Let’s just go to bed……”

“This time, he seems to have allied with Heavenly Justice.”

“Weren’t they always partners?”

“Doesn’t this complicate things even more then?”

The guilds were at a loss! This God alone was already difficult enough to deal with, and Heavenly Justice wasn’t easy to bully either. In terms of strength, the top guilds were still quite a bit stronger than Heavenly Justice, but Heavenly Justice was aware of this fact as well, so they looked for other places to fight. They tussled using their identity as Clubs. Using several good opportunities to bring up hype about their guild, Heavenly Justice pushed themselves into a very subtle position.

Even though the top guilds wanted to ally together and eliminate them, they didn’t dare to. They were afraid of public opinion on this matter. They were afraid the players would accuse them of suppressing all enemies. The guilds couldn’t openly suppress Heavenly Justice, so they could only do it in the dark. The reason Heavenly Justice was having a hard time getting bosses wasn’t just an issue of strength. Right now, they were the enemies of every guild, so it was difficult for them to find any foothold in these kinds of competition. When the guilds cooperated with each other temporarily in these sorts of chaotic battles, they would never cooperate with them.

The top guilds could only pressure them in this way. If they were too obvious and direct, with Heavenly Justice’s previous actions, Heavenly Justice would certainly blow it out of proportions and gain the sympathy of many fans.

Heavenly Justice’s actions truly made the other guilds envious and disdainful. However, the Clubs had given them the order to not give Heavenly Justice any more opportunities. Under this order, they couldn’t make any big movements against Heavenly Justice.

Now that these two difficult opponents had allied together, the guild leaders were about to go bald from stress.

Chapter 649: The Day Before the Finals

While the guilds smashed their heads against the walls thinking about how to deal with these two difficult opponents, the Level 55 wild boss Sewer King Lookashoo was killed.

The battle concluded without any suspense. In the end, Heavenly Justice snatched the boss away. The top guilds didn’t care too much about a Level 55 boss, but their indignance wasn’t because of this boss, but because it was a new era of dark times.

When Ye Xiu’s party had rushed over to the boss fight, Loulan Slash had added them to his guild. In the group channel, everyone could clearly see what items Loulan Slash had obtained.

“God, which ones do you want? You pick first!” Loulan Slash privately messaged Ye Xiu.

“Sure!” Ye Xiu wasn’t polite. He didn’t take too few or too many. He picked out enough materials that were equivalent in value to the few he didn’t take.

This was a tacit agreement between the two sides. Loulan Slash was generous and Ye Xiu was aware that if they wanted their good relations to continue in the long term, there would need to be many subtle agreements.

“Today went very smoothly. If I get any more information, I’ll notify you immediately.” Loulan Slash was in a good mood.

“No problem. As long as I’m online.” Ye Xiu replied.

This was one issue that couldn’t be resolved. Because they only had a limited number of hands, Ye Xiu couldn’t stay in game for 24 hours like the top guilds. Ye Xiu’s group needed to rest. There was nothing they could do about letting many of the bosses go. Why else would Ye Xiu hope to encounter higher levelled bosses?

“There are still a lot of bosses left! Keep up the hard work!” Loulan Slash said.

“Oh? How many are left?” Ye Xiu lacked information about wild bosses. When a wild boss was killed, the system would publicly announce it, but keeping track of the remaining wild bosses required someone to do so. Furthermore, it was possible that he might not be on or simply failed to notice the system announcement.

“I’ll send you the list.” Sure enough, Loulan Slash was very active with this kind of work. He had an organized list of which bosses had been killed for the week.

A list of data was sent over.

The Heavenly Domain continued to expand. There were currently 69 maps between Level 55 to Level 70. Apart from the wild boss in each map, there were also wild bosses that appeared under special circumstances. Adding it all up, the total number of wild bosses amounted to 74. Among these, 20 of them were Level 70 bosses. These Level 70 bosses were, without a doubt, the most important ones. When more than one boss appeared, the top guilds would prioritize these 20 bosses over the rest.

These 20 bosses were the most difficult PvE content available in Glory. Even without outside interference, a Club guild couldn’t guarantee certain victory against one. It wouldn’t be the first time a boss had swept up in a river of blood and completely wiped the field.

Ye Xiu opened up the boss count for this week. Of these twenty bosses, seven of them had already been killed and thirteen of them still remained. Adding that together with the other wild bosses, there were a total of 43 bosses remaining, over half.

“It seems like we’ll be pretty busy.” Wei Chen took a glance at the list and made a comment.

“The more we meet the better.” Ye Xiu said.

“We can’t miss a single opportunity!” Wei Chen added.

They continued to level while waiting for Loulan Slash’s news, but everything continued to be silent. Ye Xiu paid attention to the system announcements on the global chat, but he didn’t notice any announcements of a wild boss being killed, so it wasn’t Heavenly Justice’s fault.

Nighttime soon arrived and not a single boss had spawned. Lord Grim had finally reached Level 70 though, so he no longer needed to worry about being suppressed because of his level anymore.

“How sad! To think not a single boss would spawn!” Loulan Slash messaged in sorrow.

“There’s nothing that can be done.” Ye Xiu was also helpless. It was all by chance. You would think that, with so many bosses available, one of them would appear, but no matter how much you wanted one to spawn, it just wouldn’t. What could you do?

“I’m going to go watch the match.” Loulan Slash said his goodbyes. The finals were about to start.

“Keep a watch on the bosses!” Ye Xiu hastily reminded.

“Finals!!” Loulan Slash stressed as if Ye Xiu didn’t know.

“Watch the game while watching the match!” Ye Xiu said.

“The problem is that it isn’t just me. At this time, I won’t be able to get anyone under me to keep an eye out for them……” Loulan Slash said.

Ye Xiu thought about it and had to agree. It was almost 8. Usually, it would be peak hours for the game at this time, but looking at the Heavenly Domain right now, it was as if it were the middle of the night. For an important match that only took place once a year, if you said you weren’t going to watch it, you would certainly be looked down upon. How could you even be considered a Glory fan after saying that?

It wasn’t just casually taking a look either. It was a put-everything-aside and watch. For Wei Chen, there wasn’t anyone left for him to lead. All of them had gone to watch the finals! As guild members of a participating team, if they didn’t watch the match, they would be suspicious of pretending to be a fan of Samsara.

However, Club guilds were still Club guilds. The core elites were semi-professional gamers. Watching wild bosses every day was part of their regular work. Most of the guild members could take breaks to watch the finals, but did that mean employees could? As a result, there were still people from the big guilds wandering about.

This wasn’t something Loulan Slash could do. Even though their team was planning on officially joining next season, their guild was still a player guild. There was nothing he could do if no one wanted to work at this time.

“This is the sort of time when an opportunity might appear! Everyone is watching the finals, so if we focus on looking for bosses instead, we might reap enormous profit. Don’t forget that a lot of the bosses haven’t spawned yet. What if several suddenly spawn during the match? You’re about to become a pro player and you still care about watching the match live? When you study matches, you have to keep on replaying them until you want to vomit. Missing a match isn’t going to be the end of the world.” Ye Xiu urged Loulan Slash.

“The content of the match is secondary. More important is getting to know who this season’s champion will be!” Loulan Slash said.

“Samsara.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hm?” Loulan Slash immediately realized: “You sold the guide to Samsara?”

“Isn’t that obvious? Didn’t you notice that Samsara’s characters suddenly improved drastically?” Ye Xiu said.

“I heard about it…….” Loulan Slash said.

“And now you know the reason.”

“But that doesn’t necessarily mean that they’ll win the finals for certain, no?” Loulan Slash said.

“If they play badly, then there’s nothing to be said.” Ye Xiu said.

“So you’re saying that as long as they play normally, Samsara will definitely win?” Loulan Slash said.

“I don’t want to say it’s guaranteed, but I favor Samsara.” Ye Xiu said.

“Now I want to see the match even more……” Loulan Slash said.

“Just leave your game open on the side. If some information comes up, just notify me. It’s not like everyone in your guild is gone? Just have them be on the lookout for wild bosses.” Ye Xiu said.

“Alright alright!” Loulan Slash gave in.

“I hope to hear some good news.” Ye Xiu said.

“I hope a boss doesn’t appear……” Loulan Slash only had the match in his heart.

It hadn’t been easy to convince Loulan Slash to not miss this opportunity. Ye Xiu obviously had to keep an eye out in game as well. When they watched matches in Happy, they usually didn’t go downstairs. They used the projector in their practice room. Everything had been set up already, but Chen Guo wasn’t there.

The Internet Cafe naturally became more crowded because it was time for the finals. As the boss, Chen Guo personally went down to watch over everything in case something unexpected came up.

“You’re not going to watch the match?” Wei Chen saw that Ye Xiu was still playing the game. The match would be starting in a few minutes. The two sides were already seated.

Ye Xiu once again explained to Wei Chen how good of an opportunity it was right now. Wei Chen was slightly moved by his words, but he still refuted: “I’m still Blue Rain’s former captain. I feel like I should seriously support my mother team.”

“You just sold a huge advantage to your mother team’s opponents.” Ye Xiu reminded.

“Uh oh!” Wei Chen slapped his forehead. He suddenly seemed to have just realized what he had done.

“That’s why I’m saying. Let’s dungeon instead.” Ye Xiu said. His Lord Grim headed towards a Level 70 dungeons. When he got to Level 70, he needed to carefully pay attention to his equipment. Self-made equipment was his final goal. For now, he could only make do with what the game currently provided for him. Ye Xiu had some ideas of what Orange, Purple, and Blue equipment that he wanted.

“What dungeon?” Wei Chen asked. He looked towards Ye Xiu’s screen and raised his eyebrows. He immediately cursed: “F*ck, how am I supposed to watch while clearing this dungeon?”

Ye Xiu was standing outside a 5-person Level 70 dungeon entrance. Wei Chen knew that with their skill, the two of them could beat the dungeon, but it wouldn’t be that easy for them either. They still had to pay attention and not make any mistakes. Under that sort of situation, how could he give any attention towards watching the match? If he wanted to watch, while playing, he would need to be playing in one of those low-leveled dungeons, where he could close his eyes and still clear it easily.

“It’s not just us two, so it’ll be a bit easier.” Ye Xiu said and called over Tang Rou and Steamed Bun.

Tang Rou wasn’t too conflicted about not watching the match. Steamed Bun was the same. When he heard the call, he immediately rushed over. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion had been Level 70 for some time now, but their equipment still wasn’t any good. They were all equipment from small five-player dungeons. Their equipment was far from the quality of those that came out of hundred-player dungeons.

The three players entered a dungeon. The clock hit eight and the finals officially started. Ye Xiu started by pulling the first wave of monsters in the dungeon.

“We don’t even have a Cleric…… no matter how many people we have, it won’t be enough to watch the match at the same time!” Wei Chen grumbled. He felt like he had been scammed by Ye Xiu. Without a Cleric, he would need to be careful to not get hit. In this kind of situation, he couldn’t get distracted.

Chapter 650: Doing Two Things at Once

“Left left left!!!”

“Interrupt interrupt interrupt!!”

“Retreat retreat retreat!!”

The constant yelling that was coming from Happy’s practice room almost completely drowned out the commentary for the finals. It was hard to believe that these guys were running an easy five player dungeon, even more so with two former pros and two mechanically skilled players.

After taking care of another chaotic situation, the four of them released a sigh of relief.

It wasn’t that the dungeon was hard, but rather that the none of them were fully focused on their playing. Even Ye Xiu, who had urged everyone to run the dungeon, also gave a few glances at the ongoing match from time to time. A slight misstep and the situation devolved into chaos.

Their progress through the dungeon was not going smoothly. Every small wave of monsters was as if they had encountered a final boss. If not for their high skill levels, who knew how many times they would have died already? In the end, they failed to clear the dungeon with still a third of the dungeon left to go!

“I say if we really need equipment, instead of running dungeons, why not just find a few players wandering around and kill them?” Wei Chen said angrily. In his eyes, obtaining equipment like how normal players got theirs through running dungeons was a complete waste of time. Instead, if they saw good equipment on a player, it would be more efficient to just directly treat that player like a boss and kill him for his equipment to drop. In addition, this method was less reliant on luck. If you wanted a certain class’s equipment, then just kill a player of that class. A Battle Mage obviously wouldn’t wear a Blade Master’s equipment.

Finding a specific piece of equipment by running dungeons was much more troublesome. There were a total of 24 classes in Glory and each class had their own respective equipment. Very few classes shared equipment. In the dungeon that they had just run, they hadn’t found any suitable equipment from the two bosses that they had managed to kill. The only thing they could do with equipment for other classes was sell them or find someone to trade with, which was also very time-consuming. Wei Chen felt that doing this sort of proper and upright practice was beneath him.

“Aren’t you afraid of the boss kicking you out if you randomly kill people for equipment?” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s not like she’s here right now! Steamed Bun, Little Tang, you won’t tell her, right?” Wei Chen said, “It’s you guys who will be getting the equipment!”

“Stop with your nonsense.” Ye Xiu said.

“This really isn’t a good way of doing things. Even using money to buy equipment is more worthwhile. The time needed is too high otherwise.” Wei Chen said.

“Do you think I don’t know that? I really need an equipment from this dungeon and I didn’t see it in the market.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you need?” Wei Chen asked.

“Rising Wind Pendant.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh, that one…… you want to stack jumping power?” Wei Chen immediately understood. It was a fairly famous piece of equipment.

Anything that came out of a five-player dungeon wouldn’t be considered too valuable. Its base stats, such as its Magic Resistance, couldn’t compare to drops from ten-player, twenty-player, or hundred-player dungeons. The tiny bit of intelligence and spirit bonus wouldn’t move any magic class, but its +8 to jumping power was its only highlight. It was the highest bonus of any pendant.

However, whether this +8 to jumping power was worth sacrificing Magic Resistance and even other base stats was something that needed to be considered. Normally, any class that didn’t require intelligence or spirit wouldn’t even consider this pendant. The sacrifice was too much. However, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was an unspecialized character, which could use skills from all of the 24 classes. Any stat was valuable to him, so he had decided on this pendant.

However, even though this Rising Wind Pendant came out of a five-player dungeon, it was still an Orange equipment, so it naturally had a very low drop rate.

With a very low drop rate and a low demand, no one would treat this kind of equipment as a valuable good. This dungeon had been one of the first Level 70 dungeons to be added to the game, so few players came. As a result, it was rare to see a Rising Wind Pendant in the market. Ye Xiu could only depend on his luck.

Wei Chen was quite clear about the circumstances, so he didn’t say anything more. The finals had already reached the team competition portion. In the previous individual and group competitions, the two teams each had their own victories.

In the individual competition, Blue Rain had sent Yu Feng as the starter. This All Star level Berserker didn’t disappoint and gave Blue Rain a good opening. In the next two rounds, each of them won one. After the individual competition ended, Blue Rain had a total of two points, while Samsara had one.

The scoring for the playoffs were slightly different than it was in the regular season. The individual competition wasn’t any different. Each round was worth one point. The group arena was worth more points than normal. It was worth 2.5 points. On the other hand, the final team competition was worth fewer points than normal. It was only worth 4 points. As a result, each match was worth 9.5 points. For both the home and away games, there were a total of 19 points possible. As long as neither of the matches in the home and away games were complete opposites of each other, there would never be a situation where both teams had equal points. Of course, a tie breaker still had to be considered. If both teams tied, they would add an additional competition to decide the winner.

Ye Xiu and the other four also glanced at the group arena competition following from time to time. In the end, Samsara won. Samsara currently held the lead with 3.5 points to Blue Rain’s 2.

The team competition was always the highlight of the match, whether it was in the regular season or in the playoffs, most matches would be decided here.

After a short break, the team competition began. The two sides readied themselves as the screen showed their lineups.

On Samsara’s side, captain Zhou Zhekai and vice-captain Jiang Botao would obviously be leading the team. Next was a Grappler player, Lu Boyuan, an Assassin player, Wu Qi, a Cleric player, Fang Minghua, and their sixth player was a Blade Master player, Du Ming.

On Blue Rain’s side, the three All Stars: captain Yu Wenzhou, vice-captain Huang Shaotian, and Berserker player Yu Feng would be competing. Next was a Spitfire player, Zheng Xuan, a Paladin player, Xu Jingxi, and the sixth person was a Qi Master player, Song Xiao.

Both teams had Blade Masters, but the one on Samsara’s side, Du Ming, was their reserve player. On the other hand, Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian was their ace player. Of the two healing classes, which would directly be opposing each other, one team had a Cleric, while the other had a Paladin.

Healers were essential in the pro scene. They would almost always appear in the team competitions. It had been proven through countless matches that pure offensive teams weren’t dependable enough in the Pro Alliance. Pure offensive teams could sometimes win in an astonishing display of prowess, but consistently performing at that high of a level was way too difficult. At least, up until now, any team that had tried to attempt a pure offensive style had vanished like smoke in thin air.

Paladins and Clerics were both Priest classes. Both of them had healing skills and could be considered specialized healers. When Clerics weren’t healing, Clerics had other spells to restrict or attack their opponents. On the other hand, when Paladins weren’t healing, their defensive stats were outstanding. They would often take a damaging role or be a main tank like a Knight.

Often times, just by looking at whether the healer was a Cleric or a Paladin, one could usually guess what style the team was planning to use. Teams with a Cleric were more offense-oriented. They preferred to use damage to control the battle. Teams with a Paladin usually played a slower and steadier pace.

Samsara and Blue Rain had each settled on a style. Samsara’s offensive capabilities didn’t need to be questioned. While Blue Rain wasn’t considered a defense-oriented team, their team was more balanced.

“Are we going to be watching the match or continue with the dungeon?” Seeing that they might even miss the team competition, Wei Chen felt a bit reluctant. It was the finals! As pro players, they were still huge fans of Glory. Even if they didn’t have any emotional investment into the teams playing, watching high-level play was always a treat.

“Fine…… let’s watch!” Ye Xiu felt a bit reluctant too. He had wanted to watch the match while running the dungeon, but it seemed that they couldn’t do both at the same time. Now that it was the team competition, he didn’t want to continue either.

“Let’s watch the match first.” Wei Chen immediately let go of his mouse. The four characters stood in the middle of the dungeon as their players watched the match.

The lineups on the two teams were introduced. Each character had their own characteristics. Afterwards, the commentator and guest made predictions. Whether or not Samsara’s skill points had improved was no longer a secret. It was just that no one had an exact number and Samsara naturally wouldn’t announce it to the public. The commentator and guest made their guesses. When Ye Xiu and the others heard their guesses, they knew that they were being too conservative. None of them dared to say that Samsara had characters with maxed out skill points. They only guessed that these characters might have the most skill points in all of Glory.

Then again, Ye Xiu didn’t know if Zhou Zekai’s or Jiang Botao’s character actually reached 5000 skill points or not. According to the drop rate, it shouldn’t have been a problem, but who knows if their luck turned sour.

After listening to the commentary by the commentator and guest for a while, the match officially began. A team’s placing in the regular season could give the team an advantage in the playoffs. For example, Team Blue Rain was first place in the regular season, so for the two matches played in the finals, Team Blue Rain would play their first match as their away game and their second match as their home game. This allowed them to figure out how to fully utilize their home game advantage based on how the first game went.

The first match of the finals would be Samsara’s home game, so they had the right to pick the map. In the end, Samsara picked the map “Grass Blowing in the Wind”.

This was a map filled with tall grass, so the terrain could provide protection to the team. However, the tall grass only blocked vision. It didn’t help defend against an attack. To use this as their map, Samsara was clearly planning on making aggressive attacks.

There were many different ways a team could use a map to their advantage, but they generally followed one rule. After the map was chosen and the two teams gave their okay, they would quickly start the match. The camera swirled around the map as the audience cheered.

The two teams immediately began moving as soon as they loaded in.

Samsara were obviously very familiar with the chosen map. Their five characters headed towards the other team’s spawn point. Blue Rain wasn’t a complete stranger to this map. An old powerhouse like Blue Rain wouldn’t have a map that they had absolutely no knowledge of.

Team Blue Rain quietly set out as well. Their ace player Huang Shaotian and his Troubling Rain had already disappeared amidst the grass blowing in the wind…….

Chapter 651: Samsara’s Teamwork

Troubling Rain had disappeared!!

The first one to want to cry was the cameraman! The cameraman had the ability to focus on a single character, but from a bird’s eye view, while the other four Team Blue Rain players could easily be seen amidst the grass blowing in the wind, only Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain was nowhere to be found. When did he stray off from the rest of the team? No one had noticed it.

Fortunately, this sort of problem could easily be solved. The cameraman immediately switched to Troubling Rain’s first person point of view. His location and movements could be discerned from his surroundings.

The camera zoomed out, zoomed out, zoomed out, and then Troubling Rain disappeared once again.

The commentator followed up with the prompt. He could only brace himself and say: “Everyone, look. Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain is currently moving around, hidden in the grass. It isn’t easy to see him. Instead, pay attention to the tracks left behind in the grass.”

The commentator was just spouting nonsense. When the cameraman zoomed out, it was impossible to see where Troubling Rain was actually located. That was the only thing he could say.

Tracks left behind? The spectators looked at the screen to search for them. Those who couldn’t see it would say “Oh, I see it! Over there, over there.” If not, wouldn’t it seem like they weren’t good enough to notice?

Experienced players like Ye Xiu and Wei Chen were actually able to grasp Troubling Rain’s movements from the minute traces left behind in the grass. However, these traces immediately disappeared from the screen because the cameraman was randomly moving it around. The two of them realized that the cameraman had no idea what he was doing and was just pretending that he did.

The cameraman obviously couldn’t keep on pretending he couldn’t find these tracks, so he began shifting to other points of views, from an overall perspective to different individual perspectives. It gave off the feeling that a decisive battle was approaching.

Finally, one side made the first offensive move!

“Great Gunner, I’m behind you!” A bunch of words suddenly appeared in all chat. The person speaking was Troubling Rain!

In Glory’s eight season finals, the first attack had been Huang Shaotian’s trash talk. For people, who loathed superfluous words, it was quite a disappointing opening.

The cameraman immediately switched to Huang Shaotian’s target: Zhou Zekai’s Great Gunner, Cloud Piercer.

Cloud Piercer didn’t have any intentions on turning around. He simple flung a grenade behind him.

Whether Huang Shaotian was telling the truth or not, Zhou Zekai probably decided it would be best to defend himself just in case. The explosion from his grenade was the first sound of the entire match.

‘Uh oh, I’ve been hit.” Another string of words popped up in all chat.

“F*ck, just fight already! Why do you have to talk so much!!” The players hadn’t even reacted yet, but the commentator was already starting to become impatient. Of course, the commentator could only say this in his head. Out loud, his only choice was to say: “Team Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian has already begun verbally harassing his opponents, but is it effective against Samsara? We’ll have to wait and see.”

This commentator clearly wasn’t a fan of Huang Shaotian. He had to restrain himself from spewing out his true feelings and expressed a more neutral stance.

“Look at my sword!” Four words popped up on the screen.

Samsara’s players remained unmoved. Suddenly, a sword light flew out from a patch of grass.

Troubling Rain had begun attacking. However, his target wasn’t Cloud Piercer, but Fang Minghua’s Cleric: Laughing Song.

But if this sort of ambush was enough to cause trouble for them, Samsara should not have chosen this map for the finals to begin with. Samsara’s players had clearly been prepared for this kind of ambush. The instant the grass broke apart, Fang Minghua’s Laughing Song moved. He quickly cast a Sacred Fire at his feet and leapt to the side. He put his cross in front of him and holy white light shot out like a flashlight. The green grass was lit up by the white light and a figure could be seen hiding inside. After that sword light missed, the figure hadn’t rushed forward, but retreated instead.

Samsara’s practiced players immediately focused their attacks towards that location to clear away the field. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer leaped high into the sky and opened fired at the figure amidst the grass. Jiang Botao’s Spellblade, Empty Waves, also rushed forward. Fiery flames surrounded his strangely shaped dagger as he slashed downwards. A wave of fire immediately swept the area. The surrounding grass was burnt away, but there was no sign of Troubling Rain.

The Assassin Wu Qi and the Grappler Lu Boyuan needed to be within melee range to attack and didn’t have any mid or long-ranged moves. The two characters rushed out, executing a pincer attack.

At this moment, Laughing Song’s white light faded away and Troubling Rain’s figure could no longer be seen, but Cloud Piercer was able to infer Troubling Rain’s location from the white light and chased after him. With these attacks pointing towards their target, Wu Qi and Lu Boyuan coordinated with Jiang Botao’s Fire Wave and instantly trapped Troubling Rain.

The audience cheered loudly.

Their teamwork had to be brilliant in order to catch that sly Huang Shaotian.

Even though Samsara was known as a one man team, this was only because of Zhou Zekai’s outstanding performance. When other teams called Samsara a one man team, they were simply envious of them having such an incredible ace player. Every top team had fresh flowers and green leaves supporting one another. It was just that the flower known as Zhou Zekai stood out compared to the other players. Zhou Zekai often decided the match on his own, but it didn’t mean that Samsara didn’t have any tactics or teamwork. At this very moment, they displayed their exceptional teamwork on stage.

“Troubling Rain has been caught! Things are not looking good for him right now. His teammates still need a bit of time before they will be able to reach him. Huang Shaotian’s movements are a bit off from his team’s. This was a bit of a rash move on his part. Let’s how he manages to deal with this situation!” The commentator rejoiced at Huang Shaotian’s misfortune as he continued to commentate.

“Wow, you actually managed to catch me!!”

Huang Shaotian actually took the time to type a few words. For people who liked to talk a lot, it was quite admirable of him.

Lu Boyuan’s Grappler had extended his hands towards Troubling Rain. Grapplers relied on throws. Their damage wasn’t amazing, but throws couldn’t be blocked. Along with their displacement and knockdown effects, throws were extremely useful crowd control skills in team fights, especially for an offense-oriented team.

Huang Shaotian didn’t only talk. Troubling Rain quickly leaped away from the two hands. At the same time, he put his sword up and activated Guard to block the Heart-Piercing Stab from Wu Qi’s Assassin.

Using the momentum from the opponent’s stab, Troubling Rain slid backwards, but Wu Qi’s Assassin followed closely after him, his dagger never left Troubling Rain’s blade as he hastily kept up.

How could a God like Huang Shaotian not be experienced? He immediately realized what Wu Qi was planning to do and rolled to the side. The dagger in the hands of Wu Qi’s Assassin shot forward like a bullet, but if one looked closely, the dagger hadn’t left his hands. Only a part of the dagger had shot out. The dagger was still in his character’s hands and slashed along an arc along with the other part.

Assassin skill: Mother and Child Stab.

Wu Qi’s execution wasn’t slow. Unfortunately, Huang Shaotian had predicted it and had dodged. This sudden and insidious move failed to injure him.

Troubling Rain didn’t complete the roll as he flew up. He used a Headwind Strike and swept the area in front of him with a storm of wind, not only was Wu Qi’s Assassin unable to dodge it in time, it also stopped Lu Boyuan’s Grappler from approaching.

After using Headwind Strike, Troubling Rain landed on the ground. The instant Headwind Strike ended, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer slid past Wu Qi and Lu Boyuan. While Huang Shaotian had been defending against them, Zhou Zekai had found the perfect opportunity to attack him.

It looked as if Zhou Zekai’s Slide Kick would hit Troubling Rain, but the instant before it hit, Huang Shaotian was able to complete a Falling Light Blade to meet the attack.

Troubling Rain’s blade hit Cloud Piercer and Cloud Piercer’s Slide Kick hit Troubling Rain. It was a clash between two skills of equal levels.

Troubling Rain was kicked away, but it was exactly what he wanted. The instant he landed, he swung his sword. Instead of attacking, he used a Triple Slash to run away. As his sword slashed, the grass around him was sliced apart before he disappeared from view again.

Because Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer had been hit by the Falling Light Blade, he was briefly stunned. This brief stun was enough to stop him from following up, allowing Troubling Rain and opportunity to escape. Huang Shaotian was a master at seizing opportunities, after all.

The first confrontation between the two sides had concluded. All sorts of minute movements had happened in that short instant. It felt like even a small breath of air could have changed the outcome. The spectators didn’t dare to breathe and no matter how fast the commentator could speak, there was no way he could keep up with such a fast pace.

Everyone was still reflecting on the fight, when a string of words appeared in all chat.

“Ha ha ha, you can’t catch me! You can’t catch me! Just wait. You’ll see me soon again.”

How childish! Numerous people were thinking that it spoiled the beautiful scene. It had been such a high level confrontation, but this guy just hand to end it with some trash talk. What an eye sore!

Chapter 652: Team Blue Rain’s Tactics

Even though Huang Shaotian’s childish trash talk spoiled the beautiful scene, the brilliant escape he had made couldn’t be erased from their memories. The audience had been hoping for a slow-motion playback so they could revisit that brilliant escape once more. Instead, the camera zoomed out to let the audience see that the other four members of Team Blue Rain had quietly circled around behind Team Samsara while Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain had been distracting them.

“Ah!!” Many fans of Samsara cried out in alarm, dying to go up and warn the players. Unfortunately, this was something they couldn’t do no matter how hard they tried, even for the audience members present at the match. No matter how loud they shouted, they wouldn’t be able to penetrate the soundproof booths surrounding the players.

The players were completely focused on the surroundings of Grass Blowing in the Wind. However, even though Samsara was about to be ambushed by Team Blue Rain, it seemed as if they still had plans for Troubling Rain as they advanced in the direction that Troubling Rain had escaped towards.

Close!

The four players from Team Blue Rain had already drawn near.

The hearts of the home team’s fans leapt into their throats. The away team’s fans were also sweating nervously.

Attack!

The other four members of Team Blue Rain had finally reached a satisfactory position. Their characters were hiding among the grass, getting ready to attack using all sorts of offensive skills.

Different skills required different activations. The players also had different hand speeds, so every skill required a different amount of preparation time. However, Team Blue Rain released their offensive skills at the same time.

Crimson Storm!

Among the attacks, the one with the greatest surge of momentum, came from Yu Feng’s Brilliant Edge. He went straight for one of the level 70 Berserker skills as his opening move. Rushing Thunder Sword, the silver weapon of Glory’s number one Berserker, possessed a passive ability that imbued his attacks with the light element. In the midst of Crimson Storm’s pervading valor, a blue and white light traveled up and down the blade, causing its power to appear very great. As the sword sliced downwards, the sky and earth was covered in a vast expanse of green that swallowed everything up.

Swoksaar’s Silver weapon, Curse of Destruction, had long since filled the air with black gas. At this moment, the black gas converged overhead towards a single point. When Brilliant Edge attacked with his Crimson Storm, a black, whirling door that seemed to connect to another dimension solidified. The whirling door revolved gently. The black gas that permeated the air, mixed with wisps of blood, and converged into threatening tentacles that grabbed at different targets.

Warlock skill: Death’s Door. Compared to the damage it dealt, its crowd control effect was more valued in team battles. After the skill was released, the tentacles from the door would automatically pursue and attack targets within the range of 18 units. Once it grabbed a target, it would quickly drag them into the door and deal a high amount of damage.

Just from these two high-leveled moves alone, their momentum was already astonishing enough , but there was still a third player who still airborne.

The moment this character dashed rapidly from the grass, he formed a sphere with his two hands on the right side of his bottom. Boundless energy seemed to be condensing between his palms. Every audience present, including the commentator and even experienced pro players like Ye Xiu or Wei Chen found out to their surprise that the character who had dashed out from the grass was Receding Tides.

Receding Tides was a Qi Master character played by Song Xiao from Team Blue Rain. He was the sixth person in the list of names who would appear on stage from Team Blue Rain before the match. The list could not be falsified, so the only possibility was that he had been switched in sometime during the match. It was a great mistake by the cameraman to not notice anything this entire time. In this case, no one would have been able to notice it in front of the television without a special angle of the scene.

“Team Blue Rain’s Song Xiao unexpectedly makes a move! When was he switched in? We didn’t notice it at all!!” The commentator voiced out everyone’s thoughts. At the same time, Receding Tides launched his attack. He pushed out both his hands in midair where a blast of strong energy shot down from the sky.

Qi Master skill: Sky Piercing Strike!

Although the skill was named as Sky Piercing Strike, it wasn’t actually necessary to release it towards the sky. Whether it was towards the flat ground or at various other angles or positions, as long as you could successfully complete the required actions, then the move could be used.

Crimson Storm, Death’s Door, Sky Piercing Strike.

All the opening moves launched by Team Blue Rain were all high-leveled moves that covered a wide area. Evidently, they planned on inflicting serious damage to Samsara in one blow. No one would have thought that Team Blue Rain would take the initiative in their away-game. Huang Shaotian’s harassment drew Samsara’s attention, while the other members of the team took this chance to close in and unleash powerful attacks. In contrast, it was Team Blue Rain who took advantage of Grass Blowing in the Wind’s feature and gave Team Samsara a wave of surprises.

Accompanying those waves of attacks were fans of Team Blue Rain cheering, while the fans of Samsara clenched their firsts with handfuls of sweat. How would the home team defuse these offensive attacks?

They didn’t defuse them!

By the time Team Samsara’s players noticed what happened, the attacks made by the three Team Blue Rain players rained down on them, covering the entire area. Because of the the existence of Death’s Door, a skill that had prominent crowd control, the players of Team Samsara wanted to avoid being grabbed by the tentacles from Death’s Door while trying to fleeing from its range, so it was inevitable that they would receive damage from the other two attacks. After being restricted by the two attacks, dodging the tentacles from Death’s Door became an issue once again.

Under such coordination, dodging was most definitely not the best method.

Even though the damage from Crimson Storm and Sky Piercing Strike was fearful, at this moment, the core of the opponent’s waves of attacks was definitely the Warlocks’ Death’s Door. It was Death’s Door that caused Samsara’s players to feel trapped with no way out.

The key was to break through the control of Death’s Door!

Samsara’s Cloud Piercer rolled and escaped from the tentacles coming out of Death’s Door. His two hands glowed as he activated Sharpshooter’s Rapid Firing. The bullets spat out from his guns at a high speed and flew directly towards Swoksaar.

Team Blue Rain’s attacks had already cleared all of the grass neatly from this place. At this moment, they could no longer use the grass to hide themselves. As for Zhou Zekai, he was letting Cloud Piercer receive damage from the attacks in order to interrupt Swoksaar’s spell. With Death’s Door’s crowd control and high damage output, it was definitely not something the user could just cast and then do something else. It required the player to continue controlling it. If they received an attack at that moment, then Death’s Door would be interrupted very easily.

Zhou Zekai made a decisive action, but Team Blue Rain seemed to have anticipated this would happen. Soul Speaker, Xu Jingxi’s Paladin, had appeared at this moment and encased himself in a golden light cover. He cast a Holy Shield, which could resist any damage. He stood right in front of Swoksaar.

When the bullets flew towards the golden light cover, they were swallowed up without even a trace remaining. Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker didn’t receive any kind of damage.The Holy Shield’s light only dimmed a little after receiving such attacks.

Immediately after Cloud Piercer had shot his bullets, the Wave Formation from Jiang Botao’s Spellblade passed. Holy Shield’s light cover flickered for a bit, but Soul Speaker was still unharmed.

And after that? After that, the other two offensive type players of Samsara weren’t able to exert any of their power. The other two characters were respectively, an Assassin and a Grappler. Neither of them had any long-ranged attacks. By the time they rushed over to attack, they would already have escaped beyond Death’s Door’s boundaries. What would be the point of interrupting?

Team Blue Rain’s tactical arrangement had thoroughly thought over all factors of Samsara’s classes. A combination of mid-ranged attacks had directly disarmed the two Team Samsara players.

Their decision to interrupt Swoksaar’s spell at this time was relatively prompt, but had they considered all of the possibilities to cover? Did they consider if they could break through the opponent’s cover with their own attacking methods in the required time?

Doubt had already risen within numerous people, but they didn’t have time to discuss because the match continued to progress and many events would happen in a blink of an eye. Just when everyone doubted them and started to think about how Samsara’s style of having Zhou Zekai shoulder everything alone couldn’t deal with Team Blue Rain’s exquisite teamwork, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer continued to attack.

Under Rapid Firing, Cloud Piercer swung out a Gatling Gun. The cartridge cases of the bullets that flew out from the gun’s muzzle flew out crazily and scattered around his feet. The bullets from the rapid firing shot out in a straight line like a laser beam as it pierced through the light cover on Soul Speaker. The light cover continued to swallow up the bullets as it flickered, but it still showed no sign of being shattered. However, these attacks caused Xu Jingxi to feel a little nervous. He had already noticed Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves using Wave Formation attacks one after another. It was only when he had to dodge the tentacles from Death’s Door’s that his attacks would be displaced. The Wave Formation scraped past Holy Shield’s light cover as it passed over, so it didn’t inflicts its full damage. At this moment, the firing from Cloud Piercer’s Gatling Gun had ended, but the Hold Shield was still there.

At this moment, because of Crimson Storm and Sky Piercing Strike, a few Team Samsara players were captured by the tentacles from Death’s Door. They were quickly dragged towards the door. As for Team Blue Rain, Yu Feng and Song Xiao had already finished their attacks and were prepared to follow up with another wave of attacks.

“I managed to withstand it……” Xu Jiangxi was extremely astonished. He managed to fulfill the task of protecting Swoksaar with his Holy Shield.

“Right?” But at this moment, amidst the bloody light and black tentacles, Cloud Piercer swung his gun as he was pulled towards the door. He lifted his gun and aimed towards a reflection…...

Bang!

Thunder Snipe, a level 70 Sharpshooter skill.

The bullets exited the muzzle. Xu Jingxi saw a black dot enlarge at a rapid pace before his eyes, then he clearly saw the single bullet pause on his Holy Shield. Immediately after that, it wasn’t swallowed up because the Holy Shield had been broken.

Pu!

A spurt of blood sprayed out from in between Soul Speaker’s eyes.

“It’s enough to only break through my Holy Shield! You still have to get through me!” Xu Jingxi thought, when he heard a similar sound coming from behind him.

Pu!!!

Chapter 653: The Limit of Limits

Pu pu!!

These two sounds rang out at practically the same time. Xu Jingxi didn’t need to turn around to know what had happened. Cloud Piercer’s Snipe had elicited a Penetrate effect.

A bloody hole appeared in between the eyes of both Soul Speaker and Swoksaar. This just in the game though. If a real person got hit like that, how could he not die? Of course, if this were real life, it wouldn’t just be a hole. A powerful shot like Thunder Snipe would directly cause the head to explode…...

To think this would happen!

Xu Jingxi was surprised. He saw Death’s Door end. The black tentacles, which had grabbed Samsara’s characters, quickly released their grip and retreated into the door. The rotating door soon disappeared back into the void.

The characters released by the black tentacles were flung away according to their original trajectory. From this, it could be seen that the black tentacles had been swinging about wildly, but even under these circumstances, Zhou Zekai had used Thunder Snipe to hit his target accurately and produced the desired effects.

This was an ace player. Samsara’s ace player. The current number one player in all of Glory: Zhou Zekai.

The five Samsara players teched onto the ground and immediately stood up. This wasn’t anything difficult for pro players. Following afterwards, Team Samsara began their fierce counterattack. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer took the lead. He opened fire as he ran, sending grass fluttering away. The four members of Team Blue Rain were surrounded on all sides. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves pointed his sword and cast an Electric Wave Formation.

The bright ball of electricity caused the surrounding fifteen units of grass to shiver. Even though Electric Wave Formation wasn’t as terrifying as Death’s Door, the lightning generated by this skill was much faster than the tentacles. Unless you were outside of the fifteen unit radius, it would be nearly impossible to escape.

Under the suppression of Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer, how would it be so easy to walk out of range? Even normal attacks had a brief hit stun. Under Zhou Zekai’s control, his suppression was displayed to the limit. Team Blue Rain’s characters had difficulty moving. In the end, none of them were able to escape from the range of Electric Wave Formation and were struck by the lightning coming from the ball of electricity.

The most miserable of them was Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar. Zhou Zekai clearly placed more importance on Team Blue Rain’s captain and gave him special treatment. The majority of his bullets were aimed at Swoksaar. The other three players escaped from the Electric Wave Formation after being struck by lightning once. However, Swoksaar was hit two, three times…….

Team Blue Rain’s players couldn’t just stand still and watch their captain get struck by lightning. Yu Feng’s and Song Xiao’s characters rushed forward together, but they were blocked by Samsara’s Wu Qi and Lu Boyuan.

The tides had turned. After Team Blue Rain’s surprise attack on Samsara, Samsara countered fiercely. Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar was struggling inside the Electric Wave Formation. Even if he didn’t die, he would still be severely injured.

The spectators watched nervously. Their minds were completely focused on the characters fighting. At this moment, there was always something that had been neglected, such as the suddenly silent Huang Shaotian!

If he had really disappeared, Troubling Rain wouldn’t be called the Sword Saint.

Amidst the intense battle, a shadow suddenly appeared from behind Team Samsara. A blue light arced through the sky. Troubling Rain’s Silver weapon Ice Rain headed straight for Samsara’s Cleric: Laughing Song.

Fang Minghua noticed the attack. Laughing Song leapt away from the blade, but Troubling Rain’s attacks wouldn’t just stop there. Sword light suddenly blossomed from the blade.

Even though Huang Shaotian’s playstyle was like an Assassin’s, his character was still a Blade Master.

Blade Masters didn’t have the same dirty or insidious sneak attack skills like Assassins did. Every sword move, whether it was fast or slow, light or heavy, all of them were upright and fair.

Clerics had some ability to attack, but they definitely couldn’t face Blade Masters in close combat. Once Troubling Rain closed in on him, his health began to drop rapidly. However, as a pro player, Laughing Song may be on the losing side, the player Fang Minghua didn’t panic. If a Blade Master closed in on a Cleric, the Cleric would certainly suffer, let alone against Huang Shaotian’s Blade Master. Fang Minghua continued to calmly dodge and defend…… his weapon wouldn’t reduce much damage when guarding, but it was still better than nothing.

Fang Minghua hung on. Team Samsasra obviously wouldn’t just let their Cleric get killed like that.

A gunshot rang. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer turned his gun around. He shot at Troubling Rain as he ran towards him.

Huang Shaotian couldn’t ignore the attacks of the Great Gunner either. He also didn’t think he’d be able to kill off the enemy Cleric so easily. Clerics had to be saved, so he expected the enemy would be coming. When he saw the other side come, Huang Shaotian didn’t run away and instead faced Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer directly. He used Immortal Guides the Way to send Laughing Song flying towards Cloud Piercer.

Cloud Piercer immediately reacted by using a Slide Kick to slide under Laughing Song. His two guns never stopped firing as he closed the distance between himself and Troubling Rain.

Cloud Piercer had two guns. The gun in his right hand was called Wildfire and the gun in his left hand was called Shattered Frost. For a Sharpshooter, a dual gun user and a single gun user were played differently. Only using a single gun was easier and more steady. Using two guns was much more difficult because it wasn’t as simple as just firing both guns at the same time. The guns needed to be switched. In order to fully utilize both guns, the difficulty was more than twice as difficult as using a single gun. Even pro players couldn’t completely maintain such high level of play for the entire duration of the fight. Usually, they would use one gun as their main and support it with their other gun. If you could only use a single gun, then you had no qualifications to be a pro player.

Zhou Zekai displayed the dual gun style to the limit. He was also doing it while using Slide Kick.

Huang Shaotian didn’t dare to be negligent. Under his control, Troubling Rain swayed and shadows of him appeared all over the field. In an instant, the camera zoomed out. Everyone counted as the commentator cried out: “SEVEN!! A total of seven shadows! Huang Shaotian’s Shadow Steps produced seven shadows! Correct, it’s seven. Each and every shadow is perfect and complete too!!!”

Huang Shaotian pushed his mechanics to the limit as well to face off against Zhou Zekai, but the astonishment towards his move was more than Zhou Zekai’s dual gun style. Because previously, Huang Shaotian could only produce six and a half incomplete shadows. However, he had now displayed a complete seven.

“Tsk tsk, he’s improved again!” Ye Xiu sighed as he looked at the screen.

“Of course. He’s a first-rate talent that this senior personally discovered.” Wei Chen didn’t forget to self praise.

“What are you so happy for? He’ll be our opponent in the future.” Ye Xiu said.

“You should worry about the younger generation that you guided before saying anything!” Wei Chen remarked. He was naturally pointing towards Team Excellent Era. Ye Xiu had been the former captain, so Team Excellent Era’s players could be considered the younger generation.

The two old birds sighed. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were amazed. The two of them had experienced these two skills many times before in the Arena. Steamed Bun was a bit puzzled: “How could there be so many? I thought three was the maximum? How could there be seven?? Are two people using it?” The Blade Masters that Steamed Bun had encountered in the Arena clearly weren’t experts. The experts amongst normal players could produce four shadows at most. Steamed Bun had come from the tenth server, after all, so his real battle experience was quite low.

‘This is a real expert! Only an expert can do that!” Tang Rou didn’t know the complexities behind the move, but hearing the astonishment from the commentator voice, even she could tell that it must be incredibly difficult.

“I wonder how many I could do.” Steamed Bun said.

“Brawlers have a similar skill?” Tang Rou asked.

“I don’t think so. I wonder if I can learn it. It looks so cool. Look how scared that commentator is.” Steamed Bun said.

“......” Tang Rou.

The fight continued. Huang Shaotian’s Shadow Steps were at the peak. Seven shadows, difficult to differentiate between which was real and which was fake. In a real battle, if the real couldn’t be deduced instantly, there was no time for careful analysis. The purpose of Shadow Steps wasn’t to play hide and seek, but to seize any opening to attack.

If they couldn’t be differentiated, then attack them all!

After Cloud Piercer slid under, he shot bullets, kicked, performed elbow strikes, all sorts of attacks at the shadows. Sharpshooter skill: Firearm Martial Arts.

These were attacks that a Sharpshooter could use in close combat. Body techniques for direct attacks combined with sudden shooting out of nowhere. It was quite difficult to defend against.

Zhou Zekai’s usage of the ability didn’t need to be said. He instantly attacked five of the shadows.

The shadows from Shadow Steps weren’t like the clones from Shadow Clone Technique. Clones had real bodies with attack and health. After they took damage or the skill went on cooldown, the clones would disappear, but shadows were virtual bodies without any stats. They couldn’t take damage, but they also couldn’t deal damage either. They would only disappear after the skill went on cooldown.

Attacking was one way to distinguish shadows though. Zhou Zekai’s Firearm Martial Arts allowed him to hit five targets at once, not giving his opponent any time to adjust. However, it seemed like all of the five had been shadows. Zhou Zekai immediately turned around and saw that Troubling Rain’s real body had actually given up on the two targets in front of him. Instead, he had teamed up with Yu Feng on the other side of the field to execute a pincer attack on Samsara’s Assassin, Wu Qi.

Chapter 654: Trump Card versus Trump Card

Anyone with a starting position in Team Blue Rain or Team Samsara was definitely skilled. Wu Qi fought evenly against the All Star level Yu Feng for a single moment. Both of them were pro players. Arguing over who was better or worse wouldn’t give a definite answer. The results could only be determined once the fight concluded. In real battle, any small detail could be a deciding factor. It wasn’t something that could be predicted on paper.

Wu Qi may have been fighting evenly with Yu Feng, but once Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain joined the battle and the Blade Master and Berserker duo combined their attacks, Wu Qi could no longer endure.

Huang Shaotian and Yu Feng hadn’t been teammates for just a day or two. Their coordination with one another wasn’t as simple as one plus one equals two. Assassins had low defense and health. Facing the combined flurry of attacks, his Assassin rapidly lost health. Fortunately, Samsara’s Cleric Fang Ming Hua was able to rescue him. His character Laughing Song lifted silver weapon, Angel’s Protection, as holy light repeatedly flashed, helping Wu Qi survive for a bit longer. On the other side of the battle, Zhou Zekai had figured out where the real body was, so he wasn’t just going to sit around wasting anymore time. Cloud Piercer changed directions to rescue Wu Qi.

This was one advantage of the Gunner classes. They had long range attacks, so they could provide support faster. He just needed to lift his hands and the bullets would arrive. In comparison, if Huang Shaotian’s Blade Master had to go rescue someone, no matter how fast he ran, he would never be as fast as a bullet.

No one would ignore an attack from the Great Gunner, but taking the attack under the protection of a Paladin’s Life Activation was another matter. Life Activation increased the health regen of a character. It was especially effective for characters with equipment that had health regen effects. With Life Activation, it was possible to completely negate the effects of low damage attacks.

This skill could be used on teammates, but because the majority of characters wouldn’t stack health regen on themselves, Paladins generally cast the skill on themselves before tanking damage for their teammates.

At this moment, Xu Jingqi’s Soul Speaker activated the skill. A vigorous aura of vitality emitted from his body as he took Cloud Piercer’s bullets head on.

Blood splattered everywhere!

When the bullets hit his body, the effects were still there, but because of the quickened health regeneration, the injuries on Soul Language’s body healed at a visible pace. He didn’t move at all and just ate the bullets like a meat shield. In that instant, he looked like a Knight holding a shield, facing the boss alone.

It looked somewhat stupid, but it was effective. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer shot bullets at all sorts of angles, but Soul Language’s body was there to block them! His attacks were able to deal damage to Soul Speaker, even under Life Activation, but Soul Spekaer’s health didn’t fall as rapidly as Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence.

Wu Qi was facing the attacks from two All Star level players. Even though he was still hanging on with the help of his Cleric, it rapidly consumed the mana and skill cooldowns of the Cleric. Once enough skills were on cooldown, the two enemies might be able to inflict serious enough damage to directly finish him off in one go. This was a method that pro teams often used. A team like Team Blue Rain could obviously execute it to perfection. With the way the current battle was going, it was obvious what Team Blue Rain was planning to do.

No one stopped Fang Minghua from healing. After Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar escaped from the Electric Wave Formation, he stopped Samsara’s Jiang Botao from assisting his teammates.

Ignore a Warlock’s attacks?

That most definitely couldn’t be done. It wasn’t because of the damage, but because of the CC effects from Warlock skills.

Binding Curse, Control Curse, Hexagram Prison….. You wouldn’t die from these attacks, but being dead might be better than being alive under these spells.

Yu Wenzhou’s hand speed wasn’t fast, but his grasp of timing had reached near perfection. Wasting skills or cycling through skill cooldowns properly would never happen as long as he was in control. Yu Wenzhou rarely appeared in the individual competitions, but it didn’t mean his slow hand speed made him useless in 1v1s. With his slow and steady pace, he was able to completely control Samsara’s Jiang Botao.

“F*ck!”

Ye Xiu heard someone beside him curse. He turned his head to see Wei Chen watching the confrontation between Swoksaar and Empty Waves. His expression was ugly. He was clearly thinking of some unpleasant memories.

“You have to overcome that psychological trauma.” Ye Xiu turned his head to look at Swoksaar on the screen.

“F*ck!” Wei Chen cursed. He clearly wasn’t happy with the usage of the word “psychological trauma”. He didn’t have any such thing. He had just thought about something very unpleasant.

“What psychological trauma?” Tang Rou and Steamed Bun turned their heads and asked curiously.

“F*ck off! It isn’t something that little kids like you should be worried about!” Wei Chen shooed the two away.

“Yeah, a little kid in his teens beat him so badly, he lost all confidence and was so down-hearted, he retired. Did you really think Old Wei would blab about it casually to anyone?” Ye Xiu said.

“Tch, I was just helping a younger generation player mature and gave him confidence, so I lost on purpose.” Wei Chen jumped up and said without missing a beat. It wasn’t without reason. That time, when he lost to Yu Wenzhou, it had just been a practice bout with the team. As a senior, he could say that he intentionally went easy, because Wei Chen wouldn’t go all out against a kid in the training camp, even for someone as shameless as him.

In the end, he lost all three rounds. In the pro scene, losing three rounds didn’t prove anything. but from their positions in the team at that time, even if Wei Chen didn’t go all out, it wouldn’t change anything. Gold would always shine. Whether Yu Wenzhou won or lost those three rounds, the shell came off of Yu Wenzhou and Wei Chen would always be stuck with the feeling that he wasn’t as good as him. Losing only made the feeling worse.

“A younger generation player from your team? I don’t know where you thought of that! I’m talking about that year in the playoffs where I completely crushed you!” Ye Xiu said. When Wei Chen had still been in the Alliance, Ye Xiu hadn’t even been 20 years old yet, so he could be considered a little kid in his teens at that time too.

“So that’s what you were talking about!” Wei Chen slapped his leg: “Wasn’t that because when this senior saw your repulsively ugly face and crafty-looking eyes, with my eyes honed in the streets, I could easily see that aura of evil around you? If I didn’t let you win the championships, someone like you might take on a vengeful personality and inflict a great terror on society. As a citizen of this country, I could only throw the game and allow you to win the championships. And I had to do it three times to prevent such a great tragedy from happening. Now that you’ve grown up, this senior doesn’t need you to repay me anymore. Give this old fellow a break!”

“Are you pulling that out of your ass? I specifically looked for you to join our team so that you could win finally a championship for once. This is my apology for beating you so badly that year, but we have to get one thing straight! I only beat you up once, so I can only let you win once. The rest you have to gain with your own efforts. Look at those youngsters on the screen. Their tenaciousness and passion to win is something that you should learn from.”

“Ha ha……” Tang Rou laughed. She shifted her attention back to the match and stopped listening to their argument. The beginning of the argument seemed to have been half-truth half-lie, but near the end, the two of them began talking nonsense.

Though when Steamed Bun listened, he looked hard at Ye Xiu and mumbled to himself: “I have eyes honed in the streets too. Why don’t I see an aura of evil?”

“Ha ha ha ha, Steamed Bun, see…….. Ah!” Wei Chen heard his mumble and laughed. He was just about to say something, but his eyes had been watching the match the entire time. Team Blue Rain had control of the match, when their control was suddenly broken. Once again, the person to change the tides of the match was the Great Gunner!

Zhou Zekai fiercely turned Cloud Piercer’s gun and started attacking Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar.

This action had been planned beforehand. Xu Jingxi’s duty was to block his bullets. Now that he shifted his attention to a different target, Xu Jingxi’s Soul Language couldn’t get there in time. The Sharpshooter’s attacks covered a large range.

As for Yu Wenzhou? A battle of hand speed was his nemesis. His tempo was disrupted. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves was able to use this opportunity to escape from Yu Wenzhou. He immediately cast an Ice Wave Formation towards Troubling Rain, Brilliant Edge, and Cruel Silence, where the main battle was taking place.

The wave formation headed towards both targets and the probability of getting frozen was very high. Huang Shaotian and Yu Feng had to be wary. They could only temporarily stop attacking Cruel Silence and hastily escape the formation’s area of effect.

Under the wave formation’s protection, Wu Qi quickly controlled Cruel Silence to escape, but this battle wouldn’t give him any time to rest. Cruel Silence immediately headed towards Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar to return the favor and bully the enemy captain.

The situation instantly reversed.

Starting from Huang Shaotian’s ambush, Team Blue Rain had dominated the match until Zhou Zekai reversed the situation with a powerful snipe. Huang Shaotian then ambushed the, again regain control of the situation. Instead of facing the enemy ace player directly, he threw the enemy Cleric aside and, along with Yu Feng, focused his attacks on a non-core member like Wu Qi. Unfortunately, their control over the battle was once again disrupted by the enemy ace player Zhou Zekai.

A series of ups and downs occurred in a short period of time. The styles of the two teams could completely be seen.

Team Blue Rain had clever tactics and coordination. Team Samsara’s Zhou Zekai overturned the battle with his own power. These were their trump cards! From start to finish, they were evenly matched.

However, tactics couldn’t be executed perfectly every time, and no individual never made mistakes.

Which team would be the first to expose an opening?

Chapter 655: Trade

No one had expected that the ones to tip the scales of this even battle between Team Blue Rain and Team Samsara would be the two nearly non-existent players.

Team Samsara’s Lu Boyuan and Team Blue Rain’s Song Xiao.

Ever since the beginning of the match, the confrontation between the Grappler and Qi Master had practically been ignored. The cameraman rarely gave them any screen time.

Compared to the fast-paced team battle, where opposing teams kept on changing targets, these two seemed to almost be in their own little world. The two players had engaged in a 1v1.

However, when this 1v1 concluded, one side ended with an overwhelming advantage.

The vast majority of attention given to Samsara was focused on Zhou Zekai followed by the vice-captain, Jiang Botao. The other supporting players weren’t bad, but compared to the brilliance displayed by the Great Gunner, their plays would all appear somewhat dull. At this point, many people had realized that Team Samsara’s characters all had increased skill points. However, most of the discussion was still focused on the two All Star characters, Cloud Piercer and Empty Waves.

Only Team Samsara themselves would know the exact details. With their 20 million RMB purchase of the skill book guild, the character with the greatest improvement was actually Lu Boyuan’s Grappler: Chaotic Cloudy Mountains.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountains originally possessed 4770 skill points, an average number in the pro scene, but while clearing the quests for skill points, their luck was extremely good on this account and they had actually managed to reach the maximum 5000 points. An increase in 230 skill points had been the greatest through all of Team Samsara’. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer and Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves also managed to reach 5000 skill points, but their All Star characters had a higher starting point to begin with. Both of their characters originally possessed over 4800 points and only needed a bit more than 100 points to reach the max. As a result, amongst Team Samsara, Chaotic Cloudy Mountains had improved the most. If the opponents used data from previous matches, they would certainly realize that Chaotic Cloudy Mountains contribution exceeded their expectations.

And at this moment, the unexpected happened on Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s side.

With the help of the 230 extra points obtained through the skill book guide, Lu Boyuan was able to suppress Song Xiao. Once Chaotic Cloudy Mountains grabbed Receding Tides, he continuously used throwing skills to pressure Receding Tides. Song Xiao began to panic. He originally had confidence in breaking out of these chain throws, but during the fight, he felt that something wasn’t right. The gaps, which he could usually take advantage of to break free, were always chained together even faster than he had anticipated.

This wasn’t just an issue of the user’s hand speed, but rather a step up in the character’s skills.

Even worse, Team Samsara seemed to have expected such results. After Chaotic Cloudy Mountains successfully grabbed Receding Tides and began to continuously throw him, the other three Team Samsara attackers focused their attacks on Receding Tides.

Song Xiao wasn’t the only one to be surprised and panicked. For Team Blue Rain, this was certainly an unexpected result.

Since they hadn’t expected Song Xiao to be completely helpless against Lu Boyuan’s chain throws, they hadn’t thought that his Receding Tides would be toyed around in the hands of Chaotic Chaotic Mountains.

A character being completely controlled by a Grappler would find it difficult to react to any other enemy attacks. With the sudden attacks were focused on him, along with Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s complete control, Receding Tide’s health rapidly fell. Xu Jingxi was suddenly a mess again.

Song Xiao’s suppression affected the rest of the battle. Team Blue Rain was suddenly caught unprepared. Everything had happened too quickly.

Song Xiao’s Receding Tides was able to be saved, but it had cost Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker a huge amount of skills and mana. With a lot of his skills on cooldown, he wouldn’t be able to keep up the healing for Team Blue Rain in their fight against Team Samsara. The entire team’s health had been lowered by a peg. The series of events triggered by Song Xiao’s suppression had led to Team Blue Rain suffering a heavy loss.

“What an idiot! To think he can’t even escape out of something like that!!!” Wei Chen anxiously shouted, during Song Xiao’s suppression.

“It seems like Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s skill points have improved by quite a lot.” Ye Xiu truly deserved to be called an expert at all classes. He was able to quickly discover Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s significant increase in strength.

“F*ck.” Wei Chen angrily cursed.

“It seems like with your attitude, you want Team Blue Rain to win?” Ye Xiu said.

“Nonsense.” Wei Chen glared at Ye Xiu, “If Team Samsara loses, the twenty million that they spent would be a waste of their money. How exciting would that be? Ha ha ha ha!!”

“You beast……” Ye Xiu sighed.

Unfortunately, reality didn’t meet Wei Chen’s expectations. The first lead grasped by Team Samsara had been obtained because of their twenty million RMB investment.

“Chaotic Cloudy Mountains is a bit strange.” Song Xiao had managed to survive, so he quickly warned the rest of his teammates.

“Be careful.”

Team Blue Rain couldn’t do much about it. They had no way of slowly analyzing how their opponents allocated his skill points in the middle of such an intense match. They could only rely on their experience and intuition to deal with the problem. In an even match like this, if someone made a mistake in judgement, he would end up like how Song Xiao had previously.

After gaining their first lead, Team Samsara continued to pressure their opponents. They continued with their relentless attacks, not giving Team Blue Rain any time to recover from their earlier loss.

This type of forced fighting was exactly what Team Samsara wanted. Even though Team Blue Rain didn’t lose in a frontal confrontation, such a fast-paced battle didn’t give them any opportunity to close the gap made by Team Samsara. If this situation continued, the first one to fall would definitely be someone from Team Blue Rain.

Team Samsara gradually displayed their reason for choosing this map. By using the protective screen of the grass, they were able to force Team Blue Rain on the defensive.

“Captain, behind you!!”

A Team Blue Rain player suddenly warned during the deadlock. The spectators were able to notice it faster from their viewpoint. Team Samsara’s Assassin, Cruel Silence, had circled around to flank Swoksaar.

The warning had come too late. Against a sudden ambush, Yu Wenzhou’s reaction speed and intuition wouldn’t lose to anyone, but his execution was always a bit slower than anyone else's.

Yu Wenzhou was extremely important to the team, but his weakness was also extremely obvious. He was a contradictory existence in the team. The team’s greatest strengths and greatest weaknesses were both him. This wasn’t any secret. As a result, Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar was often ambushed by others, so he was very used to it.

Facing this kind of situation, he didn’t panic. He would always calmly resolve it.

Cruel Silence leapt out of his cover from the grass. The cold light glinting from his dagger slashed downwards towards Swoksaar. Suddenly, a Hexagram Prison appeared out of the void. However, it wasn’t aimed at Cruel Silence, but rather Swoksaar himself.

Wu Qi was depressed!!

If he continued, he would definitely hit Swoksaar, but his Cruel Silence would definitely crash into that dark-purple prison. In that case, he would immediately be trapped inside the Hexagram Prison. A single attack in exchange for getting imprisoned wasn’t worth it.

Cruel Silence didn’t continue forward and retreated instead. Suddenly, as he dodged to the side. “Ding!” The sound of two blades colliding could be heard. Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain had suddenly appeared. However, Wu Qi had been aware and used his dagger to block the attack.

The two melee classes engaged in battle. Swoksaar’s Hexagram Prison immediately began to move. It wasn’t fast, but it cut off Cruel Silence’s path of retreat.

Huang Shaotian knew what to do intuitively. Troubling Rain drew his sword and used Formless Phantom Blade.

Assassins didn’t have the ability to directly face a skill like this. Wu Qi hastily had Cruel Silence retreat, but only then did he discover that he had nowhere to run. In front of him was a Formless Phantom Blade and behind him was a Hexagram Prison. One of the lights from the Hexagram Prison touched Cruel Silence. The prison instantly formed around him. Before the duration of the effect had ended, he would have no way of escaping. Troubling Rain’s attack was already storming towards him. Blood flew everywhere from Cruel Silence’s body.

It hadn’t been easy to catch an opponent. Just one attack would be a waste. Team Blue Rain’s characters began to focus their fire on him. Team Samsara could hastily try to rescue him and Cruel Silence might not die, but this situation was similar to Song Xiao’s previous situation. Team Blue Rain would use this opportunity to make up for the gap that had previously been created.

But who would have thought that Team Samsara didn’t have any intentions on saving him? Wu Qi and his Cruel Silence had unexpectedly been completely abandoned. Samsara’s players immediately focused their attacks on Swoksaar instead.

Team Blue Rain suddenly realized this might happen and wanted to make adjustments, but Team Samsara didn’t give them a chance. The first one to arrive was Chaotic Cloudy Mountains. Ignoring everything else, he grabbed Swoksaar and tossed him into the air. Then, bullets flew towards Swoksaar. Zhou Zekai was planning on using a Delivery Gun to send Swoksaar away!

Delivery Gun wasn’t something that couldn’t be broken free from, but…… it required Yu Wenzhou to best Zhou Zekai in hand speed. It was something very very very unlikely to happen. None of Team Blue Rain’s players had any hope for their captain. They hastily searched for Cloud Piercer’s position and headed over to stop him.

But how could Team Samsara just let them do what they wanted? They hurried over to protect him…..

Swoksaar continued to tumble in the air. Cruel Silence being trapped by the Hexagram Prison had been Team Samsara’s trade.

However, the trade for Wu Qi’s Cruel Silence in exchange for Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar was too worth it!

After another series of back and forths, Cruel Silence made a heroic sacrifice and Swoksaar was finally killed by Cloud Piercer.

Chapter 656: At All Costs

Swoksaar being the first to fall in the finals was an unexpected outcome. Yu Wenzhou was both Team Blue Rain’s greatest strength and greatest weakness. Everyone knew this. Team Blue Rain was no exception. Thus, Team Blue Rain never neglected their protection towards Swoksaar.

Yet in the finals, Swoksaar was actually the first to fall. Even though Team Samsara had sacrificed one of their team members, it was an extremely good trade for them.

The fans of Team Blue Rain were very worried over this death. On the field, Team Blue Rain was clearly in a bit of a fluster. The reserve players on both teams were automatically switched in. Even though it was still a five versus five situation, Team Samsara seized the opportunity to launch a wave of attacks. But Team Blue Rain was still the number one team during the regular season and a team that had reached the finals. Even though Yu Wenzhou’s early departure heavily affected them, his loss wouldn’t cause them to completely collapse.

Team Blue Rain’s five players stood firm, and another closely-fought contest between them and Team Samsara unfolded. Although Yu Wenzhou was no longer on the field and unable to lead the team or set up formations, his tactics and knowledge imperceptibly seeped into the team after playing for so long together. Despite him not being there, Team Blue Rain was still a team that coordinated well with each other. This was what a pro team should be like.

Countless fans continued to watch in worry. The health of the characters on both sides continued to fall. Even with healers, they couldn’t keep their teammates at full health. This was PvP, not PvE. The battle was constantly changing. Healing had to closely follow the pace of the battle. Every skill and drop of mana had to be utilized efficiently. In this kind of high-level fight, no one had any opportunities to be wasteful. A single overheal could be a deciding factor in a match.

There were sometimes brilliant plays and sometimes mistakes in the shotcalling by both teams. As the fight went back and forth, everyone’s health and mana fell. The match was nearing the endgame, which required perfect play. Both sides were fully focused. Apart from Huang Shaotian chattering away in the all chat, the tensions were at their peak.

Had Huang Shaotian’s trash talking affected this match?

Although the other players in Team Samsara weren’t as quiet as Zhou Zekai, they still took after their ace player. Thus, their team was generally quiet and rarely talked in all chat. When facing Huang Shaotian’s completely illogical and brainless trash talk, Team Samsara wouldn’t bother inviting trouble onto themselves. But Huang Shaotian would still be constantly chattering in all chat even though no one ever replied back. No one knew what Team Samsara’s players were feeling right know. From the way the match was going, it didn’t seem like they made too many mistakes. Or perhaps these mistakes were a result of his trash talking? If Huang Shaotian wasn’t talking trash non-stop, would their play have been more perfect?

The effects of trash talking was difficult to test.

Headwind, Double Stab, Rising Dragon, Falling Phoenix, Sword Strike Rends the Sky!

Huang Shaotian didn’t lose his distinctive characteristic as an opportunist. He suddenly found an opening amidst the wave of attacks. Before anyone else could interrupt him, he chained a series of attacks onto Team Samsara’s Blade Master, Du Ming. Against his own class, Huang Shaotian seemed to be even more merciless. After completing this combo, he finished it with an Immortal Guides the Way. By the time Du Ming’s Blade Master flew backwards, he had already died.

Before Huang Shaotian could feel happy about his kill, he quickly turned around…….

Bang bang bang bang bang bang…..

To Huang Shaotian, the majority of a Sharpshooter’s attacks could be described with a single word. “Bang!”

Repeated gun sounds along with punching and kicking could be heard. The same time Huang Shaotian killed an opponent, Zhou Zekai also killed one.

“F*ck! 1v1 me!!” Huang Shaotian shouted in all chat. Troubling Rain rushed towards Cloud Piercer with a Triple Slash. But Zhou Zekai wasn’t done yet! He continued to shoot. If no one stopped him, he would kill off a second player soon.

With Troubling Rain closing in, Zhou Zekai didn’t dare ignore him. He temporarily switched targets. He retreated, while pointing his gun at Troubling Rain, running while attacking.

“F*ck, stand still! Stop running!!” Huang Shaotian shouted. It looked as if Zhou Zekai was a coward, but anyone who played Glory knew that even though Sharpshooters had close combat skills, it was better to keep a distance away and take advantage of their long-ranged skills. If you didn’t have the ability to close in on your opponent, you would be kited to death.

Zhou Zekai’s actions were very normal. Huang Shaotian’s taunting was being deliberately provocative, but then again, talking back to Huang Shaotian was just inviting trouble without reason anyways.

The ace players on both teams clashed. Everyone hoped for more sparks to fly. But despite Huang Shaotian constantly cursing at Zhou Zekai, Troubling Rain didn’t complete his Triple Slash and turned around. His target wasn’t Cloud Piercer.

Huang Shaotian had switched targets, but his trash talking was still towards Zhou Zekai. It was very obvious too. Most people would have been confused and disoriented by the switch-up. They might even think Huang Shaotian had messed up and gotten the wrong person.

But pro players wouldn’t be so easily affected. When Troubling Rain closed in on Fang Minghua, Fang Minghua didn’t panic. He had Laughing Song retreat calmly to the protection of his other teammates.

Team Blue Rain seemed to have all gotten the same order. All of them pounced in one direction. It seemed like they were determined to kill Laughing Song once and for all.

Zhou Zekai!

The person to stand out again was Zhou Zekai!

The wide-coverage that long-ranged classes possessed was fully utilized by Zhou Zekai. Cloud Piercer shot with his two guns to delay the movements of the other three Team Blue Rain players.

In the end, it turned into a situation, where Team Samsara had Troubling Rain surrounded.

Both teams had a 1v3 situation on side and a 3v1 situation on the other side. But for Team Blue rain, their 3v1 put them on a disadvantage. Even if they switched targets to Cloud Piercer, he was still far away! By the time the three of them arrived, Troubling Rain might already be dead by then.

Huang Shaotian was without a doubt a top God, but fighting 1v3 was a stretch. It was the endgame too. None of them had much health left. Even running away in a 1v3 situation might be difficult for him.

“F*ck f*ck f*ck f*ck f*ck f*ck f*ck f*ck f*ck!!!!”

When he typed out a bunch of curse words, a yellow light on his computer lit up, giving Huang Shaotian a warning. Huang Shaotian’s “f*ck” wasn’t an appropriate words to use. If he just used it once or twice, everyone would turn a blind eye to it, but they had to give a warning for a bunch of them in a row.

“Sword sword sword sword sword sword sword sword!!!!”

Huang Shaotian immediately switched words. He didn’t dare go against the rules and continue swearing. If he got enough warnings, he would be kicked out from the match. As for whether his “sword” meant “look at my sword” or “dirty dirty dirty dirty dirty” (TLN: the word for dirty and sword sound the same in Chinese) No one knew. After all, using the word “sword” alone wasn’t commonly done.

Huang Shaotian made his decision. His hand speed erupted. Troubling Rain didn’t try and retreat. He swung his sword to fight the three enemies. The match was at the end game. Without much health left, retreating would be worse, so Huang Shaotian was planning on doing his utmost to deal as much damage as possible before he died.

Blood splattered everywhere!

Some of the blood flew out from the other three characters, but there were some that flew out from him. Huang Shaotian tried to make a trade.

Not a one for one, but a one for three!

He didn’t think he could kill the three enemy players or even kill him along with himself. Instead, he wanted to lower their health enough for the others to be able to finish them off.

“The rest is up to you guys!!!”

Huang Shaotian’s final words weren’t trash talk. Troubling Rain fell, but his three opponents had lost a lot of health in exchange. It was very possible that Team Blue Rain would be able to abandon all else and directly wipe them out in one go. Afterwards, it would turn into a 3v1.

The match would end soon. Team Samsara didn’t cower. The three players faced the attacks of the remaining Team Blue Rain players.

In the end, Team Samsara’s three players fell, but they were able to bring down Team Blue Rain’s Paladin with them.

Without giving them any pause, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer arrived. It was a 2v1, but the remaining Team Samsara player was Zhou Zekai. Apart from healing, there was nothing Zhou Zekai couldn’t do.

Everyone knew the match would conclude soon. Even though Zhou Zekai was skilled, he would still be going up against two enemies. Cloud Piercer may be in a better condition than his two opponent characters, but he still didn’t have much health or mana left at this point.

Bang!

A single bang resounded throughout the field.

Brilliant Edge fell. After Cloud Piercer stood up, he only had a sliver of health remaining, but he still seemed as calm as ever.

When the camera pointed at Zhou Zekai, his calmness couldn’t be seen. From the camera, only his nervousness could be seen. Even so, the thrill after winning couldn’t be hidden. The audience exploded with cheers. This was Team Samsara’s home stadium. Their victory was a victory in the finals.

In the first round, Team Samsara won over Team Blue Rain: 7.5 to 2.

Chapter 657: The People’s War

Hu….. when the match ended, everyone heaved a sigh of relief, even Team Blue Rain’s fans.

This match had been as brilliant as it had been intense. From the first clash between the two teams, the fighting never stopped until there was only one player remaining. This sort of match weren’t commonly seen. The fierceness of this season’s finals made the entire crowd feel like it was worth their money to watch it live.

7.5 to 2. Team Samsara’s lead seemed quite large. However, players familiar with the Glory scene knew that these points didn’t have the same amount of weight as a sport like football. One side leading by five points after a single round wasn’t a dealbreaker in Glory. After all, following the competitive scoring rules, the team competition was worth 4 points. Along with a few points obtained in the individual competition and group arena, this difference in points was actually quite common. The finals would be decided by the total points obtained in the home and away matches, so this difference didn’t mean the competition was over.

The post-match interviews after the first round of finals were like fire. Team Blue Rain’s captain Yu Wenzhou was as calm as ever. He praised his opponents as well as the performance of his players. He expressed his regret for being the first one to die in the team competition: “Because of a few reasons that everyone knows about, I’m often the enemy team’s priority. Maybe I should have considered being the team’s reserve player and substituting in occasionally to prevent our opponents from finding any opportunities to focus me.”

Whether his words were true or not, Yu Wenzhou’s relaxed attitude could still be seen. He was an experienced player who had passed through many storms. A 2 to 7.5 point disparity didn’t make him feel too much pressure.

As for Huang Shaotian’s interview, he once again tested the writing speed of the reporters and their recording device’s battery life. They would need to search through a lengthy speech later to dig up valuable information. It would put their skill as a reporter to the test.

But the most important interview was the one that gave them the greatest headache.

Zhou Zekai was without a doubt the MVP of today’s match. Even though Team Samsara’s Lu Boyuan had been the first to open up the match in the team competition, Zhou Zekai was still the deciding player in the end.

After a bunch of “mm, ah, oh”, The reporters finally obtained a few relatively long responses. One of the questions that they obviously needed to ask was how he felt towards their victory, to which Zhou Zekai replied “Very happy.”

Another lengthier response was Zhou Zekai’s comment towards Huang Shaotian’s performance, which he expressed was “Very outstanding”.

Someone asked Zhou Zekai for more details and his feelings towards Huang Shaotian’s trash talking.

Zhou Zekai fell silent for quite awhile before responding: “No time to read!”

That was about all they managed to unearth from Zhou Zekai. They would be able to get more information out of the other members of Team Samsara, but most of their answers were just decorous remarks, praising their opponents or their team. When the reporters asked about Team Samsara’s skill points, the players would simply smile, but wouldn’t say anything.

After the post-match interviews ended, the stream showed a few highlights from the match. Then, the commentator and guest conducted a detailed analysis of the match. Ye Xiu obviously didn’t need to listen to the content of this analysis. The analysis of the commentator and guest couldn’t compare to their own analysis.

“Tsk tsk tsk tsk……” Wei Chen clicked his tongue. He didn’t say anything. His hands and head seemed to be focused on the game, but his heart clearly wasn’t in it. His character was just running around in circles, not doing anything. His mind still lingered on the match!

Ye Xiu also went back to the game. He soon received a message from Loulan Slash: “A boss spawned!”

“No way. How could it be such a coincidence? A boss spawned right when the match ended?” Ye Xiu replied.

Loulan Slash sent him an ashamed emoji: “The match was too intense. I forgot to pay attention to the game. It was info we received from awhile ago……”

“The boss is still there?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Still there. I just checked.” Loulan Slash replied.

“Then let’s hurry!” Ye Xiu immediately called Tang Rou and Steamed Bun. Those two were still watching the highlights from the match. When they heard his call, they went back to the game.

“Which boss?” Ye Xiu asked Loulan Slash for more details!

“Darkness Palace’s Night Streak” Loulan Slash replied.

“Ah, that guy!” Ye Xiu was excited. Night Streak was a Level 70 wild boss. It was Darkness Palace’s secret protector, an expert in subterfuge and assassination. Among the player classes, he would be categorized as an Assassin.

“I’m on my way. What’s the situation over there?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Currently, none of the guilds have made any movements. However, a few players have grouped up to kill the wild boss, but they’re hovering between life and death. Let’s hurry!” Loulan Slash was quite excited. His guild probably hadn’t gotten a Level 70 boss yet.

“The other guilds might be on their way too. Have your people be on the lookout.” Ye Xiu said.

“Should we start acting now?” Loulan Slash asked.

“Having many bully the few won’t be an issue.” Ye Xiu replied.

Loulan Slash immediately arranged his troops. Ye Xiu asked Wei Chen: “Night Streak has spawned. Did you guys get the information?”

“My side? No……” Wei Chen checked his messages. He looked at the guild chat. It was filled with the guild celebrating their victory. Tonight was, without a doubt, a holiday for Samsara’s fans. It wasn’t just their own guild chat. Samsara had included the global chat with them. They acted like Samsara had already won the championships.

The fans of the other teams couldn’t keep watching.

Especially Tyranny’s, Tiny Herb’s, and Blue Rain’s. These teams had already won the championships before. Their fans were looking down on Samsara’s, regarding them as country bumpkins. Samsara’s fans weren’t looking at the big picture. They had only finished playing the first round of the finals. How could that be considered worth celebrating for?

Excellent Era’s fans also wanted to say a few words, but Excellent Era’s performance in the regular season was too embarrassing. The smarter ones shut their mouths and endured it. A few jumped out and argued about Excellent Era, which attracted a lot of attention. They were immediately met with ridicule.

All sorts of insults were thrown in the global chat. In this virtual world, it was always easy to make sparks fly. It couldn’t be stopped either. Being able to say whatever you wanted was one of the charms of an online game.

Wei Chen finally received a message. He checked it. It was unexpectedly a call for him to PK……. The dispute between the fans of different teams had gone up a level. The friction had been continuously rising. That night, the arrogance of Samsara’s fans had reached the peak.

The guilds couldn’t stop it from happening. This was the people’s war. At this moment, as symbols of their team in the game, the Club guilds could only stand on their fans’ side. Any burden or losses from this large-scale PK was something that they couldn’t ignore. The will of the people was everything.

The fires of war continued to reach new heights. Even Wei Chen, the group leader of Samsara’s second elite group, had been called to battle. The elite groups were the peak powers in the Club guild. They would only set out for important battles.

“I’m…… going……” Wei Chen was solemn as he replied to the call. From the rapid scrolling in the global chat, he could already predict how bitter this war would be. No matter how strong his character was, he would certainly drown within that ocean of people.

The fires of war spread from the fans of the teams, who stood at the top in the game. A guild like Heavenly Justice could only watch as a spectator. Ye Xiu quickly helped Loulan Slash recognize how good of an opportunity this was. Loulan Slash continued to dispatch troops over.

Everywhere they walked was a battlefield.

This was a war among the people. At the same time, it was a paradise for scrap pickers. The fans of these powerful teams were relatively high-end players. When they fought, good equipment would drop everywhere. Even non-professional scrap pickers would join in for this opportunity. However, how could the PKers just let scrap pickers take their equipment? The scrap pickers also got dragged into the war.

An element of equipment soon added into the war between the fans.

Ye Xiu didn’t care about any of this. He picked the shortest route to Darkness palace. Lord Grim’s colorful equipment made others want to vomit at the sight of it. No one was crazy enough to want to fight him. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was a Silver weapon, so many people would covet it, but Ye Xiu wasn’t so stupid as to show it off to everyone. He obviously hid it in his bag. As a result, from the outside, it looked like Lord Grim didn’t have a weapon equipped. His character was also equipped with a set of garbage equipment. It didn’t matter if others had heard of the famous “Lord Grim”. No one caused him trouble.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun’s situation were similar. They weren’t members of any of the top guilds. Their equipment was below-average. They were practically invisible in the current environment. The three quickly met with each other midway and headed over together.

Halfway through, Loulan Slash received a message. A guild had started making movements in Darkness Palace.

“Which guild is it?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Conquering Clouds.” Loulan Slash said.

“Conquering Clouds…..” Ye Xiu repeated.

Even though Conquering Clouds was also a Club guild, in terms of the fight for wild bosses, they were a relatively low presence.

In the Alliance, Team Conquering Clouds had performed quite well in the first half of the season. They had reached eighth place, but after Sun Xiang transferred to Excellent Era, Team Conquering Clouds quickly dropped and ended up in fifteenth place. It was hard to even consider them as middle-tier team in the pro scene. Their guild was certainly more powerful than your average player guild, but they were far from being at Blue Brook Guild’s or Herb Garden’s level. However, arranging a few elite groups to kill a wild boss wasn’t a problem for them. For a lot of player guilds, even if you threw an uncontested wild boss to them, they still wouldn’t be able to take it down.

Thinking about this point, Ye Xiu was a bit worried for Heavenly Justice. Heavenly Justice had started as a player guild. He also didn’t know how good Loulan Slash’s elite groups were. What if they controlled the field, but Heavenly Justice still wasn’t able to take down the boss?

When Ye Xiu asked, Loulan Slash cried: “God, don’t look down on us!!”

“Okay okay. That’s good. I’ll be there soon. Give me a group to lead. I’ll take care of Conquering Cloud. You take the boss.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 658: The Battle at Darkness Palace

Darkness Palace was a place that was filled with countless legends according to the game’s lore. The magnanimity of the palace made the characters look tiny. When you looked up at the ceiling, it looked as distant as the sky.

But to these experienced players, none of this amazed them anymore. Only Tang Rou and Steamed Bun had never been here before. After entering the palace, they looked around everywhere, enjoying the fresh scenery. Ye Xiu and Loulan Slash had contacted each other previously. When they arrived at the palace, they saw Loulan Slash and his group waiting. Loulan Slash immediately invited them to join his team and then directly gave him the position of group leader.

When he saw the equipment worn by the three of them, Loulan Slash felt pity!

“God. I’m feeling sick looking at the equipment on you guys.” Loulan Slash said.

“Then give us some equipment. I don’t mind.” Ye Xiu replied.

“I didn’t bring any with me. I’ll give it to you, when we’re done.” Loulan Slash said.

“Ha ha, then we probably won’t need it.” Ye Xiu laughed.

“Hm? What do you mean?” Loulan Slash didn’t understand.

Ye Xiu didn’t explain and switched topics: “Where are Conquering Cloud’s people?”

“They’re currently inspecting their troops and making arrangements inside. They already saw, so they’re probably on their guard!” Loulan Slash said.

“You haven’t seen any other guilds?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No.”

“Throw some people along the sides of the road to keep a lookout for them. If they discover anything, we’ll be able to prepare a plan in advance.” Ye Xiu said.

“Relax. I’ve already arranged for it.” Loulan Slash wasn’t so green, he needed Ye Xiu to teach him something as simple as this.

“Let’s go in.” Ye Xiu nodded his head and their group set off. Their group was in high-spirits because everyone knew Lord Grim’s name. Even though they couldn’t personally confirm it, most players firmly believed Lord Grim was Ye Qiu. It didn’t matter whether you were a fan of Ye Qiu or not. The weight that the name Ye Qiu held was obvious. Being able to play with a God in the game would always be an amazing experience.

“Is he God Ye Qiu? Is he God Ye Qiu?” Quite a few people were asking around in the group chat. Even though Lord Grim had the Heavenly Justice tag next to his name, he rarely interacted with the other guild members.

“That’s me, that’s me. Everyone, listen to my directions!” Ye Xiu typed.

“Oh oh oh.” All sorts of emojis were typed into chat, making Loulan Slash feel jealous and envious. This sort of respect wasn’t something he could get by throwing money.

“God, I’ll be heading over there.” Loulan Slash called out. He was planning on leading another group.

“Mm, go ahead.” Ye Xiu replied.

Loulan Slash left the group and was preparing to join the other group, but his character couldn’t teleport over. He walked with Lord Grim and the others, guiding them.

It wasn’t very bright in Darkness Palace. After passing through a few rooms, they finally reached a spacious hall. Several hundred players were already inside, but it didn’t feel crowded. Apart from several stone steles and dusky rays of light, it didn’t feel like they were indoors.

“Those are Conquering Cloud’s people.” Loulan Slash pointed out to Ye Xiu.

“I see them.” Ye Xiu replied. He examined his opponent’s members and then said in the group chat: “Come. I’m going to do some rearranging.”

Each group had ten teams. Ye Xiu rearranged it by class. Each team composition had a clear style. The teams were sorted into distinct melee, long-ranged, healers, AoE, control, trap teams to make it easier to lead.

“Our people are over there. When should we start?” Loulan Slash asked Ye Xiu. He wasn’t in Ye Xiu’s group anymore, so he didn’t know that he was rearranging his troops.

“Whenever you want.” Ye Xiu said, while rearranging everyone.

“Ah! They’ve started!” Loulan Slash suddenly shouted. Ye Xiu turned around. Sure enough, Conquering Cloud had started attacking. All sorts of skills suddenly burst out.

“Have some people go up.” Ye Xiu said.

“Attack people or attack the boss?” Loulan Slash asked.

“It doesn’t matter. Right, where’s the boss?” Ye Xiu asked. He hadn’t seen the boss. Night Streak had the same model as the characters. The boss wasn’t some giant monster, so he wasn’t easy to find with so many people here.

Loulan Slash, who was about to go to battle, stumbled. He couldn’t help but turn around and look at Lord Grim. A normal person asking this question would be normal, but God should know everything. They had arrived at the scene, but he couldn’t find the boss. It made Loulan Slash panic a little.

Before he could answer, he heard Ye Xiu say: “Whatever. That’s your problem.”

Loulan Slash absent-mindedly ran to one side and met up with his group. Conquering Cloud’s people fought the boss, while keeping their guard against Heavenly Justice. It was obvious what Heavenly Justice’s intentions were. For Conquering Cloud, having the opportunity to snatch a Level 70 boss wasn’t easy. They didn’t want to lose this chance.

“Go up!” Loulan Slash roared.

“Attack the people or the boss?” The group members asked.

“It doesn’t matter.” Loulan Slash thought about Ye Xiu’s previous words and gave an answer. In the end, he sweeped over the battlefield and then paused: “Right, where’s the boss?”

Loulan Slash understood now……. The battle was such a mess that the boss Night Streak couldn’t seen.

Loulan Slash also couldn’t find the boss, but his group had people paying attention and pointed it out to him. When he saw the boss, Loulan Slash considered how he should go about attacking. At this moment, Ye Xiu sent him another message: “They have quite a lot of people. I might need some more support.”

“Okay.” Loulan Slash replied. He recalculated how he should arrange everything, when he suddenly heard shouts from nearby. Ye Xiu had led his group forward.

Their target was obvious. They didn’t hesitate. Then again, Ye Xiu didn’t even know where the boss was located. He just directed his team to start attacking enemy players.

“Team one and two to the left. Team three and four to the right. Team five in the middle. Team six and seven stand four units from the back and attack. Team eight CC them. Team nine get ready to throw ice. Team ten, get ready to heal!!!”

This division of work had been arranged beforehand. Without anyone disturbing them, their execution went flawlessly. With just one wave of attacks, a huge hole appeared in Conquering Cloud’s troops. They clearly couldn’t hang on. They hadn’t thought Heavenly Justice would be so aggressive and directly charge at them. It didn’t even seem like they knew where the boss was.

“Hold your ground! Hold your ground! Stay in order! Stay in order!!” Conquering Cloud didn’t have any plans on attacking back. They were shouting orders according to the first thing that they thought of.

“Team nine! Ice!!!” Ye Xiu ordered. Team nine was comprised of Spellblades and Ghostblades. They had been ready to attack at any moment. When they heard the order, they immediately cast their spells. The Spellblade’s Ice Wave Formation and the Ghostblade’s Ice Boundary were different, but they both had a chance to inflict freezing. A huge section of Conquering Cloud’s troops had been frozen into blocks of ice.

“AoE team, don’t stop attacking!!” Team three charge! Make sure to interrupt their high-leveled skills!”

In a large-scale battle, Ye Xiu had no way of displaying his individual prowess. He could only lead the group. Even though he hadn’t formed any tacit understanding with this group, with Ye Xiu’s identity, no one would question his orders. They didn’t ask why and just carried it out. Each of the teams had their use in the battle. There would sometimes be AoE attacks or crowd control or focused attacks. The battle went smoothly.

If they were doing well, Conquering Cloud was naturally having a bad time. Their troops were in a complete mess, yet their leader was still telling everyone to hold their ground. In comparison to Ye Xiu’s quick and precise leading, Conquering Cloud’s troops were like scattered sand. Without any strategy or tactics, they suffered heavy losses with very little advantages to show for it. This was Conquering Cloud’s current state.

If Conquering Clouds continued on in this way, they would be forced out. It wasn’t that the leader was stupid, but rather he didn’t know what do in this situation. The enemy attacks blotted out the sky and covered the ground. It made him feel like if he did this, it wouldn’t be right, but if he did that, it wouldn’t be right either.

“Hold your ground. Hold your ground.” As he shouted these words, the leader was actively surveying the situation and thinking of a solution. However, his thinking couldn’t keep up with the constantly changing situation. As soon as he thought up of something, the battle suddenly shifted. It was as if a spy had ruined his plans. How could he dare to send out any orders?

Once Ye Xiu’s team spread chaos throughout Conquering Clouds, with the rear on fire, how could the ones on the frontlines attacking the boss be calm! Quite a few of them went to help in the PvP in panic, when Loulan Slash’s group suddenly charged forward. Conquering Clouds immediately resisted, thinking Loulan Slash’s group was planning on attacking them like Ye Xiu’s group, so they decided to strike first.

Even though the boss was their target, Loulan Slash obviously couldn’t ignore this attack. His leading couldn’t compare to Ye Xiu’s, but his group had a team of elites too!

Loulan Slash, Ocean Ahead, Little Bei, Night Tide, Thousand Falling Leaves.

These five were planning on entering the Pro Alliance next season. Whether it was their character or their skill, they far surpassed normal players. It could be said that unless a pro team was here, for a five-player team, Loulan Slash’s team were unrivaled in the game.

This point could directly be seen in this battle. These five were unstoppable. They had tacit understanding with one another and their coordination linked together naturally. They already had an aura of pros.

With such a team, Conquering Cloud’s troops were suppressed. Heavenly Justice’s other players weren’t just cheerleaders either. Both sides of Conquering Clouds had to retreat in defeat. They couldn’t control the boss Night Streak either. Attacked on all three sides, their troops fell layer after layer.

“Attack the boss!” Loulan Slash was still clear-headed. He hadn’t forgotten his goal. As he killed players, he directed several of his troops to begin attacking the boss. Conquering Cloud’s defeat had already been determined, but who knows if another guild might show up?

Just as he was thinking about this, he received a message: “Players from Seaside are heading over!”

Chapter 659: Who is robbing whom?

“I knew it wouldn't be this easy.” Ye Xiu sighed after reading Loulan Slash’s message. Compared to Conquering Clouds, both the guild and team Seaside were troublesome opponents. Their team’s Zhao Yang was an All Star level pro who used the Qi Master, Boundless Sea, a powerful character even amongst the pro players.

Although they were strong, there was still a limit to just how powerful they were. The truly powerful Clubs were too occupied with the drama happening during the playoffs. The only ones who still had time to fight for field bosses were the small fries who still hung around on both sides.

“Where are they now?” Ye Xiu asked Loulan Slash.

“They’re on the way. There are two groups.” Loulan Slash answered.

Guild Seaside didn’t have much success with wild bosses in the past, so they had learned to be more vigilant every time they found a new opportunity; they would gather their troops together before they embarked on the conquest. Because of this, they were a lot slower than Heavenly Justice and Conquering Clouds.

“Two groups are fine. Let’s hurry up and finish it up here. You guys continue dealing with the boss. I will lead another group to deal with Seaside.” Ye Xiu decided.

Loulan Slash wasn’t dealing with the boss at the moment. He and his five people team were enjoying their massacre against Conquering Clouds along with the assistance of Ye Xiu’s group. Loulan Slash had only sent a portion of his people to deal with the boss Night Streak. Seeing that that portion was enough, everyone else continued to enjoy the slaughtering.

With sharp strategies on one side and overwhelming combat prowess on the other, Heavenly Justice beat Conquering Clouds swiftly. Although Heavenly Justice didn’t win without any casualties, all of the losses they sustained were rather negligible. The brilliant strategies minimized the damage they had taken.

Conquering Clouds quickly realized that their defeat was set in stone and struggling longer would only lead to more losses. The guild leader ordered the retreat with a long sigh. Under normal circumstances, Heavenly Justice would have just let them go, but considering that Seaside was arriving soon, they chased after Conquering Clouds, trying to kill off as many players as possible. Heavenly Justice wanted to eliminate the possibility that Conquering Clouds would come back to take an advantage of both sides once Heavenly Justice clashed with Seaside.

Conquering Clouds had the worst luck today as they were slaughtered all the way out of the Darkness Palace. Even the guild leader died in the chaos.

Without a leader, Conquering Clouds fell apart immediately. Ye Xiu stopped the bloodshed right away, and started reorganizing the troops because Seaside’s troops were now within sight.

Heavenly Justice had grasped total victory against Conquering Clouds, so everyone’s moral was through the roof right now. Loulan Slash spent no time on the boss. Instead, he followed Ye Xiu’s group all the way to the entrance. Using this small break, he delivered a rallying speech to his own guild, outlining the glorious victory they would have over Seaside.

“Stop listening to his bragging. Hurry up and get into positions!” Ye Xiu yelled out, and the crowd scattered instantaneously.

“What are we doing?” Loulan Slash was confused.

“Ambush!” Ye Xiu replied.

“Ambush?”

“Do you actually want to go head to head with them? Don’t you know how to use your information properly?” Ye Xiu questioned.

“But didn’t they already see us?” Loulan Slash was even more puzzled.

“Then they can chose to not enter. There’s only one entrance to the palace anyways.” Ye Xiu refuted. He had already regrouped all the players and sent everyone in hiding. He never planned on having a direct confrontation with Seaside, so instead, he had the ambush in mind from the start.

“Oh. I get it. I should get my guys to hide too.” Loulan Slash turned around to deliver the new command to his group.

“Tell me,” Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim stepped in front of Loulan Slash, “If you come over here, then once the boss dies over there, who will pick up the loot?”

“F***!!” Loulan Slash jumped up in shock.

The right to pick the boss’ loot wasn’t free for all. It’s usually determined within the group, so only the guild leader or the person designated as the guild leader had this right. Loulan Slash hadn’t given this authority to anyone, so by default, he had to be the one to pick up the loot. However, he was so far away from the boss that the system had switch the right to pick loot to free for all, which definitely didn’t work for Loulan Slash.

After realizing this, Loulan Slash ran back like a shooting rocket. On the other hand, Ocean Ahead and the others stayed behind to join the upcoming battle.

But then again, just now was pretty exciting, but this time… seemed a little shameless?

Although something felt wrong, everyone hid themselves well. As they approached, Seaside noticed that there was a crowd at the entrance, but the mob quickly dispersed. Knowing that there was a wild boss, Seaside assumed that the scene they witness was probably the result of the clash between two guilds: What a wonderful opportunity for us!

No matter who the winner of that conflict was, both sides must have suffered severe losses. If this isn't the most perfect time to attack, what is?

Guild Seaside moved swiftly and was soon upon the entrance at the middle of mountain. Nonetheless, they maintained a cautious position and did not break their formation nor did they attack randomly, preparing against a potential assault.

Unfortunately, they had miscalculated the results of the conflict between Conquering Clouds and Heavenly Justice. They never imagined that Heavenly Justice had decimated Conquering Clouds by such a large margin. There were some minor casualties, but the moral of Heavenly Justice was incredibly high after that one-sided victory.

While guild Seaside was still thinking about how to torture a group of wounded after a battle, they stepped into the gateway of Dark Palace. A flood of skills exploded out without any warning.

“AMBUSH!!!” The guild leader of Seaside screamed, but he was not too worried. This was, in the end, a game. All that an ambush could usually accomplish was to provide some initial advantages since instant-kill between same level players was not a possibility. Unlike a real battlefield, where a successful ambush could take out a field of enemies. In a game, all it could do was lowering the enemy's’ HP somewhat, unless you focused firepower on a single target. Believing his opponents were just a group of wounded players, the leader of Seaside’s troops did not panic at all.

He told his troops to not panic, and then started observing the situation calmly. Within moments, this guild leader found himself in a total confusion.

Wasn’t this offense…. A little too violent?

The guild leader of Seaside noticed this whiling watching his own HP gauge slipping at a visible speed. The attacks were simply too fierce to be coming from the pitiful victims that he was imagining. On top of that, there were attacks coming from all directions, so he had no idea which way he should be retreating to.

“First team…”

“Fourth team…”

“Sixth team…”

Ye Xiu, on the other hand, was giving out a constant flow of commands and directing this surprise attack with patience. He had no intention of turning this into a frontal battle after gaining even the tiniest advantage at the beginning. However, Ocean Ahead and his friends had a different idea. After being contemptible for awhile, they decided to charge in and soon wrestled among Seaside’s players.

This gave the ambushed Seaside a sense of direction and focused their attacks on them.

In terms of numbers, guild Seaside had the upper hand. Still, Heavenly Justice had just won a perfect victory. Their high moral boosted their performance level way above the usual. Coupled with Ye Xiu’s ingenious strategies and the fact that only Loulan Slash was missing from the elite force, Heavenly Justice dominated the battlefield with ease. Guild Seaside’s confidence quickly deteriorated: Aren’t our people dying a bit too quickly?

Advantage? Where is our advantage?

Seaside’s guild leader finally began to panic. The current situation was not what he had expected in the slightest. He had dreamt of an easy victory. He had prepared to accept the struggle if the opponent was not that much weaker, but he couldn’t understand why the balance of winning was tilting in favor of the other side as it continued to progress.

“Third team, 4 o’clock direction, charge.”

“Ninth team, 8 o’clock, traps.”

“Sixth team, AoE attack, provide cover for the charging team…”

“First team, ignore them. Come back and regroup with the second….”

The attacking teams were also being put on track as well under Ye Xiu’s command. They maintained the violent attacks without sacrificing organization. Seaside’s ease and calmness had already been crushed. The guild leader was starting to give out directions like “stand your ground!”. If the people from Conquering Clouds were here, they would definitely feel a sense of deja vu. If someone could give them another chance to start over, they would retreat right at that moment without any hesitation.

Unfortunately for Seaside, since they had no idea what had happened before they had arrived, they still believed that there was still a chance for them to turn it around. The guild leader was still looking for an opening to turn the tide. As he looked around, he noticed that his people were disappearing at a frightening pace. Soon it seemed like the entire screen was filled with Heavenly Justice’s people, waving their blades around to reap the life of another one of his comrade. All the characters with guild Seaside’s tag above their head were either struggling or on the ground.

It was only then did Seaside’s guild leader realize that he had lost this fight completely. He had lost this boss fight without even seeing the boss once.

No matter how unsatisfied they were, they could not revive dead characters with their emotions, so Seaside had no choice but to retreat, which is the best thing they could do right now.

Seaside had a smooth retreat. Loulan Slash did not receive any more additional news of any newcomers, so they did not treat Seaside the way that they treated Conquering Clouds. Upon seeing them retreating, Ye Xiu let them off by easing the attacks before sending Loulan Slash a message. Loulan Slash did not have the spare time to reply. When the players rushed back to where the boss was, the announcement that Heavenly Justice had killed Night Streak showed up in the world channel.

Cheers erupted from the troops. All of that killing was for this moment.

Noticing that everything went without problems, Ye Xiu finally let his heart drop back down and started hoping for the right loot.

When the new message from Loulan Slash arrived, Ye Xiu was fully expecting a report of the loot, but the message had only one word, “F***!”

“What?” Ye Xiu was confused. This was a level 70 field boss’ drop, so no matter how unsatisfactory it was, one could always use it to trade for something he or she needed.

“I got killed by someone!” Loulan Slash messaged again.

“WHAT?”

“Deception! Wasn’t he your friend?” Loulan Slash asked.

“That guy…” Ye Xiu paused in surprise. He could guess most of the things that happened without asking and cried out hurriedly, “Steam Bun! Hurry up and guard the door!”

“Humph?” Steamed Bun looked up. After a second of confusion, he took off his headphones and walked towards the entrance of the room.

All three people in the room stared at him for a second, then Ye Xiu snapped exasperatedly, “I’m asking you to guard the door in the game!”

While Tang Rou was laughing hysterically, Wei Chen was full of seriousness, “This was a grave mistake on our part!”

Chapter 660: Be Wary of Leaving Combat

When Steamed Bun finally figured out what was happening and rushed to the entrance of Dark Palace, Tang Rou had moved ahead of him. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim followed Soft Mist to figure out the situation.

The cleric present revived Loulan Slash right away, so he was present as well. Right now, he was ordering everyone to start a hunt, “That guy was pretty strong. Make sure you stay with your party. Don’t confront him by yourself.”

When Ye Xiu heard his command, he hastily spoke up to stop Loulan Slash, “Scatter! Scatter around!”

“But that guy was pretty strong!” Loulan Slash stated his point again.

“Being alone can drag him out, so it’s a good thing. If this drags on for too long, then he’ll leave combat be able to log out. It’ll be too late by then.” Ye Xiu explained.

Upon hearing this, Loulan Slash changed his orders immediately while lamenting over the shrewdness of the experienced experts.

“Isn’t he your friend? What’s going on?” Loulan Slash was nowhere near as composed as he appeared to be. He rushed forward to pick up the loot the moment the boss died. While he was still counting the rewards excitedly, someone else suddenly labeled him as a boss and killed him when he least expected it. When one got killed in the game, a few items from the inventory would also drop. Therefore, most players wouldn’t carry anything important on themselves. Just now, when he picked up the loot, Loulan Slash had turned himself into a mobile treasure vault. When he died, he lost more items from his inventory than equipment on his body. Three items from his inventory dropped, while only one equipment on his body had dropped.

While his equipments were flashy, the items in his inventory were much more rare. After all, they had came from a level 70 wild boss, which was usually hoarded away by the big guilds. The items he lost, especially the materials, couldn’t even be bought with money. Their value far surpassed the equipments he had. Right now, he lost all of that to a scrap picker. There were no words to describe the bitterness he felt.

“We just know each other. Don’t worry. He hasn't run too far yet. I’ll take full responsibility if I can’t get the stuff back.” Ye Xiu replied.

Loulan Slash had some doubts. Apart from Deception’s reputation, Loulan Slash had seen Lord Grim working with him last time. The thought “did he act on Lord Grim’s order?” surfaced the moment he got killed. Still, he quickly realized that this kind of betrayal was meaningless. They had originally agreed to divide the loot by half. This assassination would earn him less than half, so what would be the point?

Loulan Slash didn't think too much about it, but the thought was still there. He simply pushed it to the back of his mind. Ye Xiu’s words not only crushed his doubts, it also embraced him a little, “No, I didn’t mean it that way. I was just wondering. Aren't the two of you friends? Is there some misunderstanding?”

“No. That is just what he does.” Ye Xiu answered.

“Oh, he…” Loulan Slash was going to follow up with an explanation of how Deception had killed him, but Ye Xiu interrupted, “Just tell me where he ran off to. That’s much more important than how you died. This way?”

Lord Grim pointed with Myriad Manifestations Umbrella towards the direction where players were gathering.

“Yeah…” Loulan Slash agreed.

“Start attacking with AoE attacks!!!” Ye Xiu called out, while going over, “Attack with your group! Those who aren’t in the same group, don’t crowd together!”

“Don’t stand around too loosely! Try to cover more area with your attacks! Start attacking!” Ye Xiu was too busy giving out commands to chat with Loulan Slash.

Loulan Slash thought about it. There really was no time to chat. Once Deception leaves a combat state and logs off, he can’t have everyone here wait until he comes back. It didn’t take long to leave combat: only 3 minutes. This was determined by the system. If no skill hit Deception within 3 min, he would be considered out of combat. Then, he could simply log off and escape this hunt with ease.

Ye Xiu’s plan right now wasn’t focused on killing or even finding the opponent. All he wanted to do was ensure that Deception couldn’t log off.

“Open your eyes! That guy’s a ninja. The ID is Deception! He’s a professional scrap picker! His greatest strength is being shameless! Very shameless!” When Ye Xiu’s voice echoed across the hall, Loulan Slash, as the guild leader, decided to stay silent to let Ye Xiu take full control.

The players from Heavenly Justice responded in kind. They were quite enraged by the fact that their guild leader got killed out of the blue. They simply couldn’t allow the fruits of their hard work to be stolen so easily. They couldn't accept that they had beaten two large guilds with Clubs behind them, but lost to a lowly scrap picker.

The peace and quiet that had settled down in the Darkness Palace with the end of the boss fight was quickly shattered. Players of all classes took out their AoE skill. No one knew if the skills had hit Deception, but they had aggroed quite a number of monsters.

Dark Palance was nonetheless still a leveling area and all leveling areas had regular monsters. It was just that those regular monsters posed no real threat to the elite teams, so no one really cared much about them. While dealing with the monsters casually, everyone was still looking around, hoping to see Deception.

“There!”

A cry rang from somewhere. When most were still looking around to locate the source of it, Lord Grim had already run off.

“Is he there?” Loulan Slash hastily followed but he wasn’t sure about it at all. This only made him realize the gap he had in comparison to pro even more.

Ye Xiu had Lord Grim charging straight over. Purple smoke exploded, engulfing a number of people in a flash.

Ninjutsu- Smoke Bomb.

Spitfires have a similar thing called Smoke Bullet.

Smoke bombs worked faster than smoke bullets. They filled the entire area in a split second. Using this skill in that moment was obviously for escaping. Ye Xiu immediately gave up trying to find Deception in the smoke cloud. Instead, he started predicting where he would jump out from.

As expected. Deception's figure quickly shot out of the smoke cloud. Surely, there were people other than Ye Xiu who noticed this and gave chase right away. Ye Xiu, on the other hand, noticed that Deception's hand moved back as he was escaping and shouted out a warning, “Beware of the nails!”

“Nails” was the name given to the skill by the players. The actual skill name would be caltrops. These tiny spikes are thrown onto the ground. Those who stepped on them wouldn’t take a lot of damage, but it severely decreased a character’s mobility.

Deception hid his action well, so most people wouldn’t have noticed that he threw out the nails. Unsurprisingly, among the many that gave chase, quite a few slowed down suddenly. Clearly, they had stepped on the nails by accident. With another handful of caltrops, he successfully delayed his pursuers to buy himself sometime to jump onto the stone pillar nearby and started climbing upward.

The guns roared away.

Just because the melee players were stopped didn’t mean that the long-range players had to take a back seat. The gunner class players focused their gunfire on him right away. However, Deception performed superbly. He was clearly well-practiced with the climbing skill known to ninjas. In that moment, there was no one to stop him. Ye Xiu knew from his agile movements that he probably hadn’t brought out his trash equipments for this scrap picking. This kind of speed could only be achieved with movement speed buffs from relatively good equipments.

In a few breath, Deception was pretty high up. With a backward jump, he stepped onto a beam and started sprinting straight ahead.

The beam was rather narrow, so it had no space for horizontal movement. Running up there spared him from dealing with the troubles from melee class players, but it made him the perfect target for long-range class players.

Amidst the gun fires, Deception ran straight ahead, swaying left and right to dodge the attacks. These actions demonstrated his incredible mastery over his character’s movements.

“Not bad!” Ye Xiu praised. At the same time , Deception had finally entered Lord Grim’s effective attacking range. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shook and Anti-Tank Missile shot straight at Deception.

Boom!

The missile landed on the bean squarely and the shock wave spread out. Deception dodged both with an agile leap, successfully avoiding this calculated move of Ye Xiu’s.

Amidst the regretful sighs of the players around, Deception could feel cold sweat dripping down his back. If he had reacted half a second later, the missile would have hit him.

Deception had been ignoring his attackers up until now. That well-planned attack finally tempted him a glance at the crowd. Immediately, a familiar name stood out painfully to him.

Why is he here?!

Deception buried his surprise in his heart and noticed the guild ID before Lord Grim’s name. It was same as all the other players: Heavenly Justice.

Had he been recruited?

While Deception was still contemplating about it, Lord Grim fired again.

Deception started to worry. If if was a one on one, he was confident that he could dodge the attacks pretty easily. The problem at hand right now was that he was running around in a rain of bullets. If an expert at such a high skill level joined the fray, there was no way his escape would be easy. That jump had indeed been splendid, but that was because he had made a mistake previously and moved one step too slow. How many players could make that sort of prediction?

I can’t drag this on any longer!

Deception made up his mind. Eyeing the stone pillar nearby, he suddenly jumped over.

Just when he seemed to have missed it, he threw out a ninjato, which buried itself into the pillar. Then he swung his character over using the rope attached to the small knife. After some swinging in midair, he successfully hid himself behind the pillar.

“Surround him!!” Loulan Slash ordered loudly, and the players of Heavenly Justice rushed from every direction.

Behind the pillar, Deception used a Ninjutsu · Disappearing Body Technique right away and was planning on taking his time to assess the situation when a roll of racing bullets nicked him

Among the flying debris, Lord Grim’s gun pointed straight at him from below the pillar, “Still hiding?”

Deception was gloomy. Wasn’t that a bit too fast?

Chapter 661: Hasty Escape

The Disappearing Body Technique was a skill that enabled Ninjas to have Spiderman-like abilities. However, this skill had a limited activation time. Deception was able to maintain this skill for 20 seconds. He planned on making good use of this time by planning his escape route, but he didn’t expect Lord Grim to find him so quick.

This guy was very troublesome. From their previous fight together, he had experienced how bothersome Lord Grim was. Right when he thought he had gotten a good haul, he just had to bump into him.

He had used the Disappearing Body Technique and Darkness Palace itself was dimly lit. The higher you went, the darker it was too. How was this guy able to find me? Deception thought perplexedly. As he pondered over this, he didn’t hesitate to move to a higher place. The long-ranged classes could still hit him at this height.

However, when he moved from his hiding place, he heard Lord Grim say, “There! Did you see him?! He moved just now!”

“I see him!” Numerous people responded and immediately began attacking him.

Deception felt helpless. He dared to make a bet with anyone that Lord Grim hadn’t actually known where he was hiding, but rather guessed that he would be around this area. Did the random firing force me to move and trick me into revealing my location?

If I had just stayed still and took the sudden attack, would he have passed by me?

Deception’s current analysis of the situation was actually incorrect. He had underestimated Ye Xiu.

It was true that Ye Xiu wasn’t completely sure about his hiding position, but he could still roughly guess it. Deception’s hiding position could be determined from his previous position and movement speed. In such a short period of time, when Deception went behind the pillar, he couldn’t have moved much farther past it. Ye Xiu was sure about this. The previous blind firing hadn’t been completely random. Even if it hadn’t hit him, it wouldn’t be too far off.

Deception was unable to hold off from the heavy attacks from so many players. The Disappearing Body Technique wasn’t invincible. Escaping while being targeted by so many players on the stone pillar was no easy feat. Deception attempted to move to another pillar but immediately dismissed the notion, when he remembered that there was that troublesome guy below. He slid down the pillar and mid-way through, he suddenly kicked the stone pillar and jumped, ready to forcefully charge through the crowd.

He moved like a bullet, while taking note of Lord Grim’s position. He had to avoid that guy at all costs.

However, right when he glanced over to check Lord Grim’s position, Lord Grim’s umbrella locked into him. He realized that of all the players, Lord Grim's reaction speed was the fastest. The other players were still shooting at the stone pillar.

“Bang bang!”

Two muffled sounds could be heard and the two shots had actually hit him, causing Deception to tumble in the air.

To be able to hit him, while he was moving at such fast speeds. This guy’s aim was too terrifying!

Deception, who had been shot down from the air, was about to fall into a group of players. If he were surrounded by these players, there was no way he could escape. In that instant, he used the ‘Shadow Clone Technique’ and then used his main body to force his way through.

He waved his hands and threw a smoke bomb towards the ground, instantly creating a thick purple smoke screen around him. The purple smoke was so dense that no one could see anything despite being right next to each other. It would be considered quite good if they didn’t crash into each other. Even though Heavenly Justice’s players could blindly attack because they wouldn’t be able to hurt each other, these aimless attacks would only deal a tiny bit of damage to Deception if they hit. They had no way of keeping him there. In the blink of an eye, Deception snuck his way out of the smoke and stealthily tossed a few caltrops behind.

The two ninja tools were used flawlessly. Deception, who had been in this kind of situation countless times before, knew how to get out of this predicament.

Deception had forced his way out of the encirclement. Normally, he would have ran away without looking back. However, today there was a troublesome guy who wouldn’t let him off so easily. As a result, he couldn’t help but look back. He noticed that while everyone else had lost their sense of direction and moving sluggishly, only Lord Grim quickly dashed out of the smoke and pursued him.

As expected, it’s not going to be easy shaking him off!

Deception turned around and sped up. His equipment could be considered as top quality in the eyes of the Glory community. Ninjas were also a class that emphasized speed. As a result, equipment that increased his movement speed were highly valued. In terms of running, Lord Grim’s shabby equipment would definitely lose to Deception’s.

But how could Ye Xiu only rely on just running? Lord Grim fired his gun while chasing after him.

With all of the bullets coming from behind, Deception could only zig zag left and right to prevent Lord Grim from accurately hitting him. But how could he dodge all of Lord Grim’s attacks? Not all of the bullets hit, but the accuracy was higher than what Deception had predicted. Deception felt like his zig zagging was pointless, but he also knew that if he didn’t move in this way, he would have been turned into a honeycomb.

The bullets induced a small stun effect, making it very annoying. Lord Grim purposefully aimed at Deception’s legs too, so he moved like a crippled duck.

In this situation, even though Deception's speed was still very fast, Lord Grim, who was able to slow down Deception’s speed, was able to control him quite well.

The exit is right there!

Deception could already see the light coming out of the exit to Darkness Palace. With his current speed, he could shake off the other pursuers, but what about Lord Grim?

Deception wasn’t confident that he could escape. Suddenly, the sounds of gunshots stopped. Surprised, Deception glanced over and realized that the distance between him and Lord Grim had widened enough that he was out of Lord Grim’s attack range.

Ye Xiu couldn’t do much about it.

He had tried his best to hold off Deception. If only his equipment was a bit better, he could definitely catch up to Deception. Unfortunately, his shabby equipment didn’t increase his movement speed much, while his opponent’s equipment increased his movement speed by a lot. And even though his bullets could slow him down, Deception was still able to slowly increase the distance. Currently, a lot of Heavenly Justice member had run past Lord Grim, but they were only running after Deception, without using any skills to impede Deception's progress. Without slowing him down like Ye Xiu did, they would never be able to catch up. Now that Deception have escaped Ye Xiu’s range, his movement speed increased even more.

Deception felt more confident now, after shrugging off Lord Grim. Deception ignored all of the other pursuers.

“Steamed Bun, Little Tang!” Ye Xiu raised his head and called out.

“Hm?”

“Come over. You need to stop Deception.” Ye Xiu spoke.

“No problem.” Both of them replied.

Darkness Palace’s exit was quite wide. Even with 2 players blocking, the exit couldn’t be blocked completely. However, these two players didn’t consider themselves as mere blockers. The murderous aura they released clearly stated their intention that they were ready to kill anyone who came near the exit.

In the blink of an eye, Deception reached the exit. After escaping from Lord Grim, he paid no heed to the other pursuers. Deception only glanced at the 2 players at the exit. Without even caring to avoid or evade them, he dashed forward.

When Tang Rou saw this person dash forward without any hesitation, she immediately felt admiration for him. Soft Mist moved forward and welcomed him with her spear.

As Deception ran closer, he saw their mismatched equipment and regarded them as worthless. The moment he reached Soft Mist, he suddenly jumped, and threw three shurikens.

Tang Rou didn’t know everything about every class, but she had seen the majority of their skills before. In the Arena part of the Heavenly Domain challenge, she had encountered skills from various classes before.

Tang Rou is still not knowledgeable about other profession but have seen the majority of the skills. When she faced the Heavenly Domain challenge, she had witnessed quite a number of these skills, even more so when she completed the Heavenly Domain challenges.

Shuriken was a low level Ninja skill which Tang Rou had seen many times before. The moment the shurikens were thrown towards her, she had Soft Mist move sideways and swing her spear.

“Ding!” The sound of the spear colliding with those shurikens echoed throughout the area. This type of attack wouldn’t have priority over her spear because projectile attacks were usually weak attacks.

Tang Rou moved sideways, causing the shurikens to pass by her without harming her.

Against such a weak skill, Tang Rou had used such a domineering method to counter it. Of course, with such a domineering method, she also showed that she wasn't just any ordinary player. Deception didn't expect a character with such a mismatched equipment to be so skilled.

Are we of the same profession?

At this moment, Deception thought about this question. Although the equipment worn by experts weren’t usually bad, experts who came out for scrap picking would usually wear poor equipment. Didn’t Deception also use low grade equipment during scrap picking?

After deflecting the shurikens, the spear didn’t slow down and continued to arc towards Deception. As for Deception, he lived up to being a Ninja. He crouched down in mid-air and dodged the spear. He straightened his legs and stepped on the spear. Using it as leverage, he kicked at Soft Mist.

Seeing Deception and Soft Mist fighting, Heavenly Justice was completely petrified by the scene before them. Before their eyes was a pro-level fight. With those mechanics, were these guys really normal players?

Deception rapidly descended as if he were planning on tackling Soft Mist, but halfway, he was met with a flying brick, stopping him. Soft Mist’s spear swung at him and threw him towards the ground.

Deception immediately had his character quick recover, when he was suddenly met with a handful of sand.

Sand Toss!

Deception obviously recognized this skill and immediately turned away, so he wouldn’t be blinded. The Brawler was faster than the sand though. Right when Deception was about to turn his body away, his butt was kicked and he was sent stumbling face-down into the floor.

Deception hastily stabilised himself, but was immediately knocked over by Tang Rou’s Circle Swing.

The Heavenly Justice players felt numb inside. They had so many players, yet they couldn’t compare to these two players with trash equipment, who could stop Deception from escaping. Seeing Deception being tossed around on the ground by them made them sweat.

Chapter 662: The Heart of Shadow Dance

Deception had been careless. Facing two players with such garbage equipment, he hadn’t given them a second thought. If not, with his level of skill and superior equipment, even against both Tang Rou and Steamed Bun, he wouldn’t be in such a sorry state.

Circle Swing was categorized as a forced “grab” and couldn’t be Quick Recovered, but Deception was quite quick. As soon as he crashed into the ground, he immediately followed up with a roll. In the blink of an eye, he was back on his feet as if he really had used a Quick Recover.

Deception no longer underestimated his opponents. He only hated how he had used his ninja tools.

A Ninja’s ninja tools were a part of the skill tree. However, ninja tools differed from ninjutsu, which could be immediately cast after forming the hand seals. On the other hand, ninja tools required the Ninja to craft the tools in order to use them. There was a limit to how many ninja tools a Ninja could carry. Normally, Ninjas would prepare enough before setting out, but he had been using his smoke bombs and caltrops the moment the skills had refreshed from cooldown, so he had run out awhile ago.

He had been using pre-made ninja tools. How would he have any time to craft any, while running?

Seeing how these two fearsome individuals were blocking his path, Deception regretted using up all of his tools. In this sort of situation, they clearly weren’t going to give him any time to craft his tools.

When he got back onto his feet, Soft Mist’s spear immediately stabbed towards him. Deception hastily dodged when he saw something else flying towards him. It wasn’t a skill or a tool, but a person! Steamed Bun Invasion had directly pounced on him, pinned him to the ground, and started attacking him in a flurry.

Deception wanted to cry. Even though he was a lone wolf, he still had plenty experience with the game. Steamed Bun Invasion had used the Brawler skill, Tyrannical Chain Punch, which pinned the target to the ground and followed up with a flurry of punches. A skill was just a skill though. Every person would use it differently. Facing this wild monkey, Deception wanted to go crazy. The skill wasn’t being used with any strategy to it. It was just a bunch of random attacks.

How could he bear being pinned by such a person? Not longer after Tyrannical Chain Punch ended, without the effects of the skill forcefully pressuring him, Deception immediately dug into the ground.

“What!?” Steamed Bun cried out in astonishment.

“You’ve never seen it before?” Tang Rou said. Soft Mist had already started acting. It wasn’t impossible to find someone who was using the Underground Tunneling Technique. There was a small hole used for breathing from the ninjato’s sheath. It was very small though, so the terrain easily hid it. However, Deception had used the skill right in front of them. How could they not know where he was? Soft Mist stabbed the ground, but something didn’t feel right.

The Underground Tunneling Technique wasn’t a rigid skill that only allowed the user to go up and down. The user could tunnel around a small area. Deception was a skilled Ninja. Since he dared to use the technique in front of them, he obviously had some confidence in using it. When Soft Mist stabbed the ground, Deception popped out of the ground behind her. His ninjato didn’t gleam with cold light. It silently stabbed Soft Mist. Deception didn’t follow up though. He had already started running. No matter how confident he was, he didn’t dare to continue fighting the two of them. There were more chasing after him. He had to be especially aware of Lord Grim in particular.

Deception glanced back, when he saw a brick flying towards him. He hastily tilted his head and dodged it. Suddenly, he was struck by Soft Mist’s spear.

These two reacted too quickly!!

Deception was astonished. His Underground Tunneling Technique had hit Soft Mist. Whenever an attack hit a character, there would be some sort of effect. Deception thought Soft Mist would be startled by it. He didn’t know how much Soft Mist had been slowed down, but she had been able to react in time and chase him down with her spear. No matter how fast he moved, he couldn’t be faster than the enemy extending her arms. The superior range of a spear finally displayed itself here.

Soft Mist had used Dragon Tooth. It didn’t deal much damage, but it still had a stun effect. This stun duration was enough for Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion to trap Deception again.

Helpless, Deception could only start fighting the two of them again and see if he could find an opportunity to escape. After a few back and forths, he couldn’t find any openings. In trouble, he heard someone say: “You little punk! You scrap pick very bravely now!”

Deception knew who was talking, but he didn’t have time to look. He relied on Tang Rou’s and Steamed Bun’s lack of real battle experience to grasp an opening. He was about to take advantage of it, so how would he have the time to glance at Lord Grim?

Deception’s two hands moved in a blur as they formed a complex seal. It was clearly a high-leveled move. If not, he wouldn’t need so much time to complete the seal.

Ninjutsu - Shadow Dance!

Numerous clones instantly appeared all around Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun hadn’t experienced this skill too many times. High-leveled skills required more time to activate. Even Deception required a good opening in order to successfully execute the skill. Normal players would have needed even more time than him, but Tang Rou and Steamed Bun completely dominated their opponents. Very few of their opponents had the opportunity to activate the skill.

Thus, even though the two of them knew what this skill did, they didn’t have much experience dealing with it. Deception was an expert as well. Several clones jumped and attack them all at once. The two didn’t know what to do. The attacks from the shadows wouldn’t bother them too much, but they had no way of grabbing onto all of the clones

The Blade Master’s Shadow Steps hid the real body amongst the fakes, but that wasn’t the case for Shadow Dance. They wouldn’t be able to catch Deception unless they killed all of the clones.

But Deception obviously wasn’t using this skill to continue fighting them. He was just using it as a distraction so he could escape. He just had a few of his clones randomly jump at Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion before sprinting towards outside of Darkness Palace.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun tried hard, but they could only keep on killing the clones one after the other, but Deception would never jump to a clone that was attacking them.

As for the other clones, he had them run as well. Shadow Steps only had a limited range, so the clones couldn’t be too far from the real character. This made it easier to control though. Deception had two clones stop Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion from advancing.

At this moment, Deception finally had time to check the situation. Sure enough, Lord Grim had caught up to him along with a bunch of Heavenly Justice players. There were even a few players that were faster than him, but in any case, none of them were closer to him than Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion. After stopping them from chasing him, Deception felt like escaping wouldn’t be too difficult now. He still needed to pay close attention to Lord Grim though. What trap had that guy set for him? Should he have some of his clones harass him?

Deception was still deciding when one of the clones moved askew. Soft Mist clearly hadn’t attacked it. In that moment of absent-mindedness, the clone had been whisked away.

“Not good!!”

Deception suddenly understood what had happened. He hastily moved his character when he saw the clones running out of Darkness Palace suddenly poof into smoke as he was grabbed by a Qi Master.

Qi Mister skill: Cloud Grasping Fist.

Deception obviously knew this skill. He just hadn’t thought his enemies would use this sort of skill to break his Shadow Dance.

He only had two clones remaining. One of them had been grabbed by the Qi Master and the other was instantly killed by Steamed Bun Invasion. By default, the system forced Deception back into his original state.

“Ha ha, why are you only paying attention to me? Aren’t you looking down on everyone else here?” Lord Grim’s laugh floated over.

Deception was sad!

Indeed, he had ended up paying too much attention to Lord Grim. He had thought that Lord Grim was the only top expert among the group. Even though the two with trash equipment had surprised him, he hadn’t put Heavenly Justice’s players in his eyes. However, the one who had used Cloud Grabbing Fist on him had just been a normal member of Heavenly Justice. The only reason he was able to pull it off was because he was a Qi Master that could use Cloud Grabbing Fist.

Deception was certain that the reason the Cloud Grabbing Fist had worked on his Shadow Steps wasn’t because of the Qi Master’s skill, but either on accident or…...

“Not bad……” Deception heard a voice. Lord Grim had walked over, talking to the Qi Master.

Sure enough!

Deception knew that he had fallen into Lord Grim’s hands.

In theory, none of the clones were his real body for Shadow Steps. However, because the clones could only move around in a limited area, in order to satisfy this condition, there had to be a marker of some sort. This marker was the clone being used by the user.

If this clone were killed, it just meant there was one less clone. Even if the player didn’t choose to, the system would automatically throw the player into another clon, and this clone would become the new marker.

This marker clone was called the Heart of the Shadow Steps. It wasn’t the real body. The player could still freely switch.

What Ye Xiu had done was determine that Deception had used the clone Soft Mist was fighting as the Heart of Shadow Steps, and so he quietly ordered a Qi Master to suddenly use Cloud Grasping Fist to bring him over. By the time Deception noticed, it was too late to move. All of the clones that had rushed out of Darkness Palace were immediately recalled because they were now out of range of the heart.

Chapter 663: Don’t Let Him Escape

Translator: Editor:

Deception’s path ahead was completely blocked off. Loulan Slash had even set up a net comprised of several players linked together in the air to defend. Deception was simply too slippery to catch. It was no wonder that he was infamous. He had successfully pulled off his scrap picking operations time after time. Loulan Slash had fought alongside Deception before, so he had a good understanding of his skill level. This time, after becoming the target, he deeply felt how talented this person was. If the five players on his team were qualified to be pro players, Deception was definitely qualified as well.

Loulan Slash had already started thinking of how he would recruit him. For a moment, he wasn’t sure what to say, but the Heavenly Justice players surrounding Deception had begun shouting: “Run! Why’d you stop running? Why don’t you give it another try!”

There were a hundred of them, yet they couldn’t even catch a single person. Fortunately, two players had been blocking the exit. These two players wore such garbage equipment that everyone wanted to cry just looking at them. Heavenly Justice’s players were ashamed and resentful.

Deception didn’t say anything. When he killed Loulan Slash, three items from the Level 70 wild boss had dropped. Even if he died, he would still profit, unless he were unlucky enough to lose all three of those items. However, the probability of this happening was too low. Maybe none of these item would drop and he lost one or two pieces of equipment. He would have made a killing if that were the case.

If you dropped an item after being killed, getting it back wasn’t an easy task. A single fight was rarely enough. However, even if you couldn’t get your dropped item back, getting another item of equal value wouldn’t be bad either! However, this wasn’t even close to the case right now. Nothing on Deception was equal in value to any of the three items that were dropped by a Level 70 wild boss.

Deception clearly knew this point, so he knew that when he died, he was very calm. So what if he died?! He would still make a huge profit.

The Heavenly Justice players could only curse at him. No one moved though. They understood this point. They wouldn’t be able to get the items back if they killed him once. Perhaps there was a better way.

However, their guild leader wasn’t saying anything. Lord Grim stood out though.

“You can’t run anymore. Hand over the items.” Ye Xiu said.

Deception didn’t even look at him. Quite a few Heavenly Justice players turned to look at him. They felt like his words were a bit naive. Even if Deception died, he would still profit. Why would he just hand over the items like that?

“This brother is very talented!” Loulan Slash finally spoke. His opening words were meaningless. Afterwards, he played by the book: “If you don’t mind, why don’t we add each other as friends. You won’t need to return the items. Just consider them a gift from me.”

It was very obvious what his intentions were. Loulan Slash’s boldness manifested itself. He was willing to gift three Level 70 wild boss drops. His character as a money warrior showed.

Even though the players from Heavenly Justice weren’t too happy, Deception was truly very skilled. They could understand why Loulan Slash made this type of decision. Let alone the fact that none of the players that had come to kill the wild boss were outsiders, everyone in the game near Loulan Slash was planning on entering the pro scene. If he found someone talented, of course he would try and recruit him!

Deception ignored him though, leaving Loulan Slash hanging.

Loulan Slash felt a bit embarrassed, but he didn’t back down. He played his big card: “Brother, scrap picking is a waste with your talent. I’m currently forming a pro team and I’m looking for players to join. Brother, would you be interested? If you are, I’m open to whatever conditions you have.”

The Heavenly Justice players were jealous!

Being offered to join a pro team and even being allowed to state your own terms? How could a Glory player not feel jealous about such treatment?

But when the person in front of them heard such incredible terms, he remained indifferent. He didn’t even glance at Loulan Slash.

“Brother……”

“What brother!”

Right when Loulan Slash was about to say something, Ye Xiu interrupted him. He saw Lord Grim transform his umbrella into a spear and stab towards Deception.

Deception didn’t even dodge. After getting stabbed, Deception stumbled. Lord Grim stabbed again and Deception fell to the ground. He didn’t seem to have any plans to get up.

“He logged off.” Ye Xiu said to Loulan Slash.

Loulan Slash was a pro-level player. Just from the reactions made by Deception after being attacked, it was clear that no one was controlling the character.

Deception was still in a combat state, so he couldn’t directly log off. He could only force quit the game. If that were the case, his character would remain in the game until he left combat. Another possibility was that he had left his character in the game and was just not controlling it anymore.

“Maybe he’s still there?” Loulan Slash thought of this possibility.

“Then you want to keep on chatting?” Ye Xiu asked.

Loulan Slash felt a bit embarrassed. Whether the person was there or not, his attitude was clear. He wouldn’t pay any attention to them. Talking to a piece of wood with so many people watching was too embarrassing! If he had confidence in persuading the other side, he might give it a try, but Loulan Slash’s previous statements had been very clear. If even these statements couldn’t move him, then nothing would work. After thinking about it, Loulan Slash felt like it would be better to show off his strength. In the end, he pointed his sword at Deception and said: “Kill him.”

As soon as he gave the order, the players attacked and Deception instantly became a corpse. He didn’t revive for a long time. It seemed as if he had truly logged off. Deception must be celebrating his success! It was a good thing Loulan Slash didn’t continue speaking. If not, Deception might have gotten out of combat and actually logged off. That would have been even worse!

When Loulan Slash looked at the ground, it didn’t make him feel happy though.

Not a single one of the three Level 70 drops that Deception had stolen had dropped. Two pieces of Ninja equipment had dropped, but Loulan Slash wouldn’t put any equipment from the game in his eyes! He looked at them and didn’t even want to pick them up. He was clear-headed enough to know that he wasn’t the only one unhappy. He said loudly: “Killing him can be considered our revenge! You can blame me for being too careless and getting killed by him. Don’t worry everyone. I’m not going to reduce any of the rewards for this run just because of something like this.”

The Heavenly Justice players felt much better after hearing his comforting words.

They clearly knew that these Level 70 wild boss drops would have been used by Loulan Slash for his pro team, so he couldn’t directly distribute them to the guild. He could only give them other rewards. It was the same for any other Club guild. Equipment from Level 70 wild bosses could sometimes be found in the guild storage, but materials were a dream.

None of them expected to get any of the boss drops anyways, so they didn’t care too much if Loulan Slash didn’t end up getting the drops. After all, Heavenly Justice had been founded through Loulan Slash’s money and his team had just been created. The fans created through hype didn’t have as much loyalty as the other Club guilds. For the Club guild players, if they were fans of the team, they would share the team spirit and cohesiveness. If something like this happened and not getting the materials affected the team’s development, they would definitely feel worried too.

As for Heavenly Justice, when Loulan Slash expressed his attitude on this matter, the majority of the players were happy. Of course, they wouldn’t display it. They remained gloomy in the game. However, Loulan Slash understood their feelings. If not, he wouldn’t have said any of these words to comfort them. In order to gain more fans, he had to be willing to say anything.

After placating his guild members, Loulan Slash had to say something to Ye Xiu too.

Even though Ye Xiu had said that he would treat the ones that had been stolen away as his part of his share, but how could Loulan Slash let him do that? Having those items stolen away was definitely his fault. Even though he could come up with many excuses, none of it could be blamed on Ye Xiu. He had been responsible for attacking the other competing guilds and had completed his task beautifully. Being able to crush two Club guilds was something that they couldn’t usually do.

Loulan Slash messaged Lord Grim. He gave him the list of items that had dropped from Night Streak and then said: “The three drops stolen away by that guy should be considered as part of my share, but I really wasn’t able to see which items were stolen. How about we first split it evenly and then you can pick any three from my share.”

“What? You’re planning on letting him go so easily?” Ye Xiu said.

“Him?” Loulan Slash asked. He obviously didn’t feel happy about letting him go, but that was how it had turned out. Loulan Slash was very angry, but what could he do? Deception had already died and they didn’t know which city he revived at. Chasing and hunting him down wasn’t worth it either. Plus, they probably wouldn’t be able to get the items back by hunting him down. Once he revived, he could just transfer the materials to his storage. The items in storage couldn’t be dropped.

“Just provide me with info. I’ll be responsible for hunting him!” Ye Xiu patted his chest.

“God, look! There are still a few wild bosses left to kill. Shouldn’t we put in our efforts towards those bosses? If we can get another boss, isn’t that more valuable than getting those three drops back from that punk? Wasting your time and our resources on him just isn’t worth it!” Loulan Slash refuted.

“Of course we have to get the bosses, but we can’t let that guy go either. In any case, all you have to do is tell me his coordinates. Announce it to your guild and just have them report his location if they ever see him.” Ye Xiu said.

“But if you go and take care of that punk, how am I supposed to steal bosses?”

“You don’t need to use a spear to kill a fly.” Ye Xiu said.

Loulan Slash hesitated: “Are you saying that punk is the fly or the boss is the fly?”

Chapter 664: A Bit of an Ass-Kisser

Translator: Editor:

Deception hadn’t actually logged off. He was still in the game! After knowing he would certainly die, he was too lazy to try anything else, so he got up and went to take a bathroom break. When he returned, as expected, his character had died. The surrounding players hadn’t left yet though. That eye-sore Lord Grim was still walking about.

Deception didn’t care. It wasn’t like he would revive on the spot. After choosing to revive, he clicked on the choice to revive at the closest city. He checked his inventory and found that all three of the boss drops were still there. He knew that he would still be profiting today no matter what he had lost. When he saw which equipment had been dropped, he felt his heart hurt a bit, but the profit he had earned was far greater than his losses. It was the first time in his scrap-picking career that he had managed to obtain Level 70 wild boss drops. His luck today had been very good.

Deception coming to this area had been a complete coincidence too. If he had planned on going scrap picking, he usually wouldn’t wear his best equipment. Today, he had just wanted to get a few items from Darkness Palace and just happened to run into the wild boss.

While the guilds fought, Deception hid on the sidelines. He didn’t act blindly without thinking because the equipment he had on him was quite expensive. Scrap pickers always had to consider whether the equipment obtained would make up for the equipment they lost. Since he had worn a good set of equipment this time, he obviously couldn’t press forward rashly like he usually could.

Deception had waited patiently for a long time. Today’s wild boss fight wasn’t as chaotic as usual. There were fewer participating guilds and Heavenly Justice had the clear advantage, not giving the other competing guilds any opportunities. This sort of situation wasn’t suitable for scrap picking, so the experienced Deception continued to wait patiently.

In the end, the opposing guilds had been defeated and Heavenly Justice began focusing the wild boss. This conclusion made Deception quite disappointed. However, he still waited, hoping Heavenly Justice would make a huge mistake and get wiped by the boss. If that happened, he could happily pick away.

Heavenly Justice didn’t get wiped as he had hoped. The one to fall was the wild boss, but at this moment, Heavenly Justice became careless. They made a common mistake committed by victors. The moment the winners celebrated, he acted.

Afterwards, Deception obviously needed to try and escape. Even though he failed, his gains had been quite considerable. How much would he able to sell these three wild boss drops for? Deception wasn’t really sure because these sort of items rarely showed up on the market! Deception felt like if he sold it correctly, he would be able to live lavishly for years to come.

“Hm? Did that guy revive??”

The instant Deception revived, the surrounding players reacted. After a character revived, the corpse would disappear and turn into a tombstone. If he had really logged off, this wouldn’t have happened.

“That guy was still on!!” Loulan Slash shouted.

“Have your players in Darkness City be on the lookout.” Ye Xiu instructed and then called out to Tang Rou and Steamed Bun: “We’re leaving.”

“Everyone, let’s go.” Loulan Slash ordered, “Grab the equipment on your way out.”

Loulan Slash was pointing at the equipment dropped from the battle. Quite a few players from Conquering Clouds and Seaside had died. Players who died would naturally drop equipment. No matter how hard they tried to get them back, there would still be many pieces of equipment that would land in the hands of Heavenly Justice’s players. The guilds all had their own ways of resolving this situation. In general, it was a difficult issue to deal with because in this type of chaotic battle, it was difficult to pinpoint who exactly took your equipment.

Ye Xiu had talked about these equipment drops with Loulan Slash earlier. Loulan Slash now understood why Ye Xiu said he didn’t need equipment, if it were after the battle. It turns out he had complete confidence in their dominating victory and knew that he could just pick which of the plundered equipment he liked after the battle.

But choosing out of all of these was quite troublesome. Everything had to be organized first, so Loulan Slash made the decision: instead of going through all that trouble, he would directly buy them the equipment that they wanted when they got back to the city.

Right when he said this, they realized Deception had revived. Ye Xiu said a few words and started rushing back to the city with Lord Grim.

“How do you know he’s in Darkness City?” Loulan Slash chased after him and asked. Darkness City was the city closest to Darkness Palace.

“From his equipment, it didn’t look like he had planned on scrap picking today. If he had something else to do, isn’t it common sense that he would pick the closest city as his revival point?” Ye Xiu said.

“Right!” Loulan Slash suddenly understood. He hadn’t thought about this point because he had no knowledge of how scrap picking worked.

Loulan Slash gave an order in the guild chat. Ye Xiu and his team naturally saw it too. Right now, they were under Heavenly Justice, so they belonged to the guild.

“I have players in Darkness City who are heading over to search.” Loulan Slash said to Ye Xiu.

“Mm, that’s good.” Ye Xiu replied. Lord Grim turned his head to glance back. Loulan Slash also looked back and was a bit speechless. As his and Ye Xiu’s groups rushed back, they had left the other Heavenly Justice players behind. The players with equipment that increased their movement speed were still able to keep up for awhile because they ran faster, but gradually, without properly utilizing their stamina, they would run out. If they could no longer sprint, their equipment’s added movement speed wouldn’t do anything.

In comparison, Loulan Slash and his team kept up. Thinking of this point, Loulan Slash felt a bit happy. They deserved to be pros! Look, they could keep up with a God!

Just as he was thinking in this way, he noticed that Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion were easily keeping up as well. When he looked, he immediately realized how disgusting their equipment looked. He was wearing good equipment and had some increase in movement speed, yet he was running at the same speed as them. How could he feel happy?

Loulan Slash felt quite defeated.

“Have the brothers who are investigating in the city hide their guild tags.” Ye Xiu suddenly said. He was still being careful.

“Okay!” Loulan Slash received the message and immediately passed it down.

“Have players in other cities pay attention too. Darkness City is just an estimation. He isn’t guaranteed to be there.” Ye Xiu added.

“Makes sense!” Loulan Slash nodded his head and ordered again.

When Ocean Ahead, Homeward Bound, Thousand Falling Leaves, and Night Tide heard their conversation, they tried hard not to interrupt. They couldn’t compare to Steamed Bun in this area. Student Steamed Bun would say anything that he thought of. When he heard the two talk, Steamed Bun opened up the guild interface. After studying it carefully, he suddenly asked: “When you said ‘Makes sense!’, who said that?”

“Me!” Loulan Slash said.

‘Who is this ‘me’?” Steamed Bun asked again.

“What do you mean?” Loulan Slash was puzzled.

“Loulan Slash?” Steamed Bun seemed to have determined something, but he still seemed unsure.

“That’s me!” Loulan Slash said.

“Senior, how mighty!” Steamed Bun excitedly said, “You can even order around a guild leader. What a god!”

Sweat!

Ye Xiu typed an emoji sweating. Loulan Slash typed a depressed face. The others had wanted to say something about this. Loulan Slash and them weren’t just any players in the game. They had been good friends even before they started playing and understood each other well. With their friendship, the other four wouldn’t object to any one of them being the guild leader. In the end, Loulan Slash became the guild leader because they felt like he had the most potential as a leader.

If this hadn’t happened in front of them, they would never have though Loulan Slash could ever be regarded as a little kid and he didn’t even look like he had any objections.

How embarrassing!

At this moment, all of them felt a bit embarrassed. Loulan Slash wanted to explain, but he also felt like he had been acting like a b*tch! How would he explain himself? Wouldn’t it just make matters worse?

In the end, Ye Xiu was the calmest. He immediately said: “Steamed Bun, what do you know? We’re discussing strategy.”

“Oh, so that’s the case!” Steamed Bun said.

This sort of explanation was enough for Steamed Bun, but for everyone else, it didn’t explain anything. Loulan Slash knew his friends were probably laughing at him. They just didn’t express it.

How depressing! However, a message suddenly arrived, averting everyone’s attention from the issue.

“Someone’s found him! He really is in Darkness City!” Loulan Slash said.

“Good!” Ye Xiu replied.

“What do we do now?’ Loulan Slash asked.

Ocean Ahead and the others were crying. Brother, do you have short term memory? How can you keep acting like this?

But this time, Ye Xiu was generous. Instead of directly saying it, he sent Loulan Slash a private message: “Watch him and figure out where he’s headed.”

The instant Loulan Slash received the message, Loulan Slash immediately realized….. He had acted like Ye Xiu’s b*tch again.

Fortunately, he had been reminded by Ye Xiu. It was a you say it instead of me message! Loulan Slash immediately gave the order and told Ye Xiu: “We’re not sure right now. Let’s just head over according to his coordinates!”

“That’s fine too. Can you get us some better equipment? Especially any that add movement speed. If not, dealing with that guy might be a bit difficult.” Ye Xiu replied.

“I’ll see if anyone can do it for us.” Loulan Slash busied about.

Following afterwards, they quietly entered Darkness City. Ye Xiu and Loulan Slash talked to each other privately, so the others obviously wouldn’t know.

“It seems like he’s planning on teleporting away!” Loulan Slash received some new information.

“Have your players in the other cities hurry and pay attention to the teleport formations! The more cities the better.” Ye Xiu hastily said.

“Already done.” After being embarrassed, Loulan Slash checked himself. Did he really need Ye Xiu to teach him this type of stuff? Not at all. With his experience, he could have done it completely on his own.

Chapter 665: Insufficient Equipment

Translator: Editor:

They finally arrived in Darkness City. The news that they had received on the way there had made them feel gratified. Deception hadn’t gone directly to the teleport formation. Instead, he headed towards the marketplace in Darkness City. If he had ran straight for the teleport formation, Loulan Slash and the others would have been in big trouble. The Heavenly Domain had numerous cities. Having people stationed in every city just wasn’t possible.

The good news didn’t last long. The strong teams had an astonishing amount of fans and support. It was a world war right now. The marketplace was cold and empty. Deception walked around for only a short while before he quickly departed.

Fortunately, when they received this information, they had just arrived at Darkness City. Along the way there, they saw battles taking place everywhere, so their group hid their guild tags. Ever since Heavenly Justice made the announcement that they were forming a pro team, they had been looked down upon by the other teams. Now that everyone was in a state of aggression, who knew if their violence would fall upon Heavenly Justice. Loulan Slash didn’t want Heavenly Justice to be dragged into the war. Even though this war was a result of a dispute between who was the best team, Loulan Slash didn’t want to look for trouble.

Without a guild tag next to them, they appeared inconspicuous. Since everyone was busy fighting, they didn’t have time to pay close attention to whether or not that passerby really was Lord Grim.

When they arrived at Darkness City’s entrance, there were people waiting there to bring them the equipment that Loulan Slash had asked them to find for him.

Ye Xiu picked which pieces of equipment he wanted. If Loulan Slash had any, he would give it to them. Otherwise, he would spend money to buy it. Just a few sets of in-game equipment for a few characters wasn’t worth much in Loulan Slash’s eyes. Ye Xiu’s group had helped him a lot. He was perfectly happy with spending this bit of money for them.

Ye Xiu’s group wasn’t polite. After taking their new equipment, the three characters switched them out. Their models and stats immediately transformed. Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion finally had a full set of class-specific gear. Their equipment only fell short of equipment that could only be dropped from the seven hundred-player dungeons. In the game, their equipment would already be considered outstanding.

As for Lord Grim….. His stats had changed, but his model…. His new and improved equipment still looked like garbage on him. He still looked like a rainbow. Mixing and matching equipment from different classes almost never looked good together. Each class had equipment that they were proficient in. If you mixed and matched equipment, you would lose stats from your class’ proficiencies. The better the equipment, the greater the losses.

However, Lord Grim’s unspecialized didn’t have any proficiencies, so he didn’t care much about any of that. As a result, he wore a cloth belt, leather boots, a leather cap, heavy armor, and cloth pants. It gave others a disgusting top-heavy feeling.

However, Ye Xiu didn’t care about his appearance. He opened up his character’s profile and appreciated his stats. Because unspecialized characters didn’t change classes, their stat growth was completely balanced. Their strength, vitality, intelligence, and spirit all had a growth of 3. When unspecialized characters reached Level 70, their base stats would each be at 210. The stat point rewards from each quests was also evenly distributed for a total of 90 points per stat. For any class, there were no worthless stats. All of them had their uses, just some less than others. Thus, all players would complete these quests regardless. At Level 70, Lord Grim’s base stats were all at 300.

All characters had a total of 1200 points at Level 70, unless they missed a quest. The only difference between them was how those 1200 points were distributed.

Unspecialized characters had a balanced growth, so their 840 points from leveling up were evenly distributed between each stat. However, every other class was different.

For example, Battle Mages had a 3.5 growth in strength and intelligence and a 2.5 growth in vitality and spirit.

Thus, when they reached level 70. Their total base stats would add up to 840, but their strength and intelligence would both be at 245, while their vitality and spirit would each be at 175.

These stat growths couldn’t be changed by players. The players needed to match equipment based on their needs. Apart from equipment, players could also freely distribute the 160 points they got from the guild buffs.

As for how these points were distributed, it was up to the players to decide. Especially for classes like Battle Mages, which dealt both physical and magical damage they had to think about whether they should stack strength, intelligence, equal strength and intelligence, or a proportion of each? This was a question that was still debated to this day. In particular, when a player got new equipment, they often had to consider this issue.

The top-tier Battle Mage, One Autumn Leaf, had chosen to lean slightly more towards strength and lean slightly less towards intelligence. As one of the most popular characters in Glory, many players naturally copied this choice. However, reality proved that blindly following a pro player’s choice was not always a smart decision.

Because normal players didn’t have the resources to accomplish proper stat distribution. First of all, their skill level wasn’t as high. Second of all, their equipment was far from pro level. A lot of stat distributions required a certain level of equipment to display their utmost potential. If they didn’t meet those requirements, even if their skills were at the pro level, they still wouldn’t be able to utilize it properly.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun were at the pro level in terms of mechanics, but their game sense wasn’t there yet. Having them choose their own equipment would certainly end poorly. As a result, Ye Xiu helped them choose their equipment.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist went with a strength-oriented stat distribution. After switching equipment, her strength reached 870, while her intelligence was only at 540.

These stats were already quite impressive in game, but it was still far from the pro level.

One Autumn Leaf had 1220 strength and 1140 intelligence. These two main stats were 1.67 times greater than Soft Mist’s. This didn’t even include the disparity in vitality and spirit. In terms of overall stats, these in-game impressive stats were not worth anything in pro gameplay.

Soft Mist’s equipment definitely couldn’t be regarded as bad in the game. All of them were second only to those that could be found from the seven hundred-player dungeons and those from Level 70 wild bosses. Even those higher grade pieces of equipment couldn’t compare to Silver equipment.

In truth, the reason Silver equipment was superior compared to Orange and Purple equipment wasn’t because they had much better stats, but rather because they were customized specifically for the player. It was for this reason that Silver equipment allowed pro characters to have such terrifying stats. This sort of disparity in stats was difficult to make up for with skill alone. It was the reason why Wei Chen was so uneasy about meeting a team like Excellent Era in the Challenger League.

If Soft Mist, with her 870 strength and 540 intelligence, faced off against One Autumn Leaf, with his 1220 strength and 1140 intelligence, wasn’t the difference as obvious as night and day?

This didn’t even factor in the difference in attack power between Soft Mist’s Level 70 Purple weapon, Extreme Light Spear, and One Autumn Leaf’s Silver weapon, Evil Annihilation.

This didn’t even considering the other additional stats apart from the four main stats provided by the other Silver equipment on One Autumn Leaf.

This sort of equipment definitely wasn’t enough.

Ye Xiu might be satisfied with his Lord Grim’s current stats, but he knew that it was still far from reaching the required level to enter the pro scenes. His Lord Grim’s stats actually weren’t even as good as Soft Mist’s. Soft Mist at least had proficiency in her armor. Those extra stats from proficiency wasn’t something that he had. In order to make up for that gap, he would need to rely on self-made equipment. Specializing the stats was an issue that Su Muqiu had been analyzing for the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

A weapon like the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had never appeared before in Glory, but the concept of specializing the stats had been analyzed in the pro scene already.

Lord Grim’s strange appearance made others want to laugh, but they didn’t know that Ye Xiu had done it this way for a specific reason.

However, even though they had switched equipment and were looking over one another’s new appearances, they never stopped moving. After understanding Deception’s current path and Darkness City’s teleport location, Ye Xiu decided: “We can make it.” Then, he immediately gave the order: “Little Tang, Steamed Bun. You two head to the revival spot first. Once you get there, message me.”

“Okay.” The two listened to his order and then left.

They were clearly planning on killing Deception multiple times! Thinking about how Deception had stolen away three pieces of material, Loulan Slash felt very excited about this sort of method. The other four felt the same. There had been so many of them at Darkness Palace, yet they still failed to catch that guy. It was too shameful! They had to win back their face.

The five people were pumping themselves up when they heard Ye Xiu say: “Then I’ll see you guys later. If I need any more information, I’ll contact you Little Lan.”

See you later?

The five went into a daze. They had followed this senior all the way here. Now that they had arrived, he just said see you later?

“Hey!” Loulan Slash suddenly called out. The five continued to chase after him.

“What’s wrong?” Ye Xiu had Lord Grim ask, while running.

“What do you mean ‘see you guys later’? We’re going too!” Loulan Slash said.

“You’re going too.” Ye Xiu was puzzled, “I thought you guys felt like chasing and killing him was a waste of time?”

“I…..” Loulan Slash realized he had truly said just that. How could he suddenly change his mind? How did that happen?

“Relax! With this equipment, he won’t be able to escape. I’ll get revenge for you! If I get those three materials, I’ll definitely return them to you, but I feel like he won’t have them on him. He probably put them in his storage already, or maybe you could find some way to get a buyer to get close to him. I reckon that he’ll bring those materials out, if that happens. As long as he has it, we’ll find a way to get them back for you.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay okay. I can’t talk anymore. I have to hurry or else I won’t be able to intercept him. Remember to update me on his whereabouts whenever you can!” Ye Xiu said and had Lord Grim speed up. He wore leather shoes, cloth legs, heavy armor, yet he easily left the five of them behind.

“This this……” The five were tongue-tied, but they had already slowed down.

“How amazing!” In the end, Homeward Bound sighed at Ye Xiu’s decision.

Chapter 666: Ineffective High Level Skills

Translator: Editor:

Lord Grim disappeared from view after turning the corner of the street. In the end, Loulan Slash’s group didn’t follow him any longer.

“Let’s just provide him with the information he wants!” Loulan Slash said angrily.

“Information is information. You’d better not keep acting like a child.” Seeing that there was no one else around them, the other four immediately warned him mercilessly.

I’ve been tainted!

Loulan Slash looked up at the sky, wanting to cry. Today really had been a disgraceful day. He had been killed in the middle of his allies and acted like someone’s b*tch in front of everyone else. He really wanted to find a hole and bury himself in it!

Ye Xiu had Lord Grim hurry ahead. After chasing Deception for so long, he had a good idea of Deception’s movement speed. He was confident that he would be able to reach the teleport formation and intercept him. Of course, the prerequisite was that he had to take the correct path. There were simply too many factors in this game. Whether it was in the wild, a city, or a dungeon, Ye Xiu couldn’t say he was very familiar with all the terrain.

However, with the help of the in-game map, Ye Xiu wouldn’t make such a low-leveled mistake like making the wrong turn. Soon, Darkness City’s teleport formation entered his range of view. There was still no updates as to where Deception’s current location was.

Deception hadn’t gotten anything from his trip to the marketplace. Afterwards, he made an all out effort to rush to the teleport formation. No one liked wasting time traveling, so the faster they ran the better. As a result, the Heavenly Justice players on the lookout for Deception quickly lost him. They couldn’t keep up!

“I hope he doesn’t go somewhere else……” Ye Xiu muttered. After looking at the map, Lord Grim found a suitable location to camp. Over here, he could see all three possible routes Deception could take and it wasn’t conspicuous either.

Ye Xiu not being familiar with the terrain didn’t hinder him from using the terrain to his advantage. He surveyed the terrain and utilized it accordingly, treating it as if it were an away match.

“He should be here soon.” Ye Xiu looked at the time. If Deception were rushing over, Ye Xiu should be able to see him anytime now. He had Lord Grim look around, but there was no sign of Deception approaching.

Maybe he isn’t coming this way?

Maybe he’s just slow?

Ye Xiu thought, but he didn’t leave the spot. After waiting for awhile longer, a figure could be seen sprinting along one of the three routes.

Ye Xiu readied Lord Grim to act at any moment. Soon, the name on that figure could be seen clearly. It was really was Deception. His running speed even felt a bit slow in Ye Xiu’s eyes.

Deception didn’t seem to be aware that there was danger hidden nearby. He was just like a normal player passing by. He didn’t look around to see if there was anything unusual around him. When he arrived at the end of the street, he ran straight for the teleport formation.

“Bang!”

A gunshot rang out.

During this time of war, a single gunshot was insignificant. They were outside of the city, so there were skills and curses flying around everywhere. The players who were online were pretty much used to this environment. However, this gunshot was loud and clear to Deception.

He deserved to be an infamous scrap picker. Deception had actually noticed the shot was aimed at him. He stepped to the side and the bullet whizzed past him.

“Not bad!”

After hearing this remark, Deception saw a top-heavy bottom-light creature jump in front of his character. This creature’s appearance was too eye-catching. Even Deception couldn’t help but be drawn to it before he noticed the character’s ID: Lord Grim.

Deception had played the game for many years already. He had been in constant danger throughout his career. He wasn’t just any ordinary scrap picker. Most scrap pickers didn’t survive after scrap picking. For them, the longer they lived, the more items they could pick up. Deception valued his life very much. There were a lot of scrap picking opportunities in the fights between the top guilds, and Deception obviously took advantage of these opportunities. Thus, he had seen many in-game experts before. However, he had never met anyone as skilled as Lord Grim before. Deception didn’t have much confidence in a real 1v1 fight with him.

Now that he had been targeted by him, Deception panicked a bit, but the teleport formation was just up ahead. As long as he could get there, he would be able to leave Darkness City. Lord Grim definitely wouldn’t know where he would be heading either. Since he wasn’t planning on fighting a life-or-death match, Deception was just going to charge his way past Lord Grim.

He didn’t say anything and focused on escaping. He started with a Shadow Clone Technique. It would be best to create a gap between them before doing anything else.

His clone was left behind as his real body instantly moved ahead, but instead of seeing a clear path ahead, he saw a poof of smoke in front of him.

“Shadow Clone Technique? I can do that too!” The other side didn’t seem to need to see clearly as he attacked him.

Deception hastily jumped backwards. The other side did a flip and began to fire bullets at him. Deception was quick though. He swung his ninja blade and guarded against the bullets.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was flung open. Deception had just wiped some sweat off his face when he heard another bang. The tip of the umbrella lit up, shooting three missiles at him.

A missile’s attack range…… was far greater than a spear’s. Using a dagger to block it just wasn’t going to happen. Guarding would be a pointless action.

But what other option did Deception have?

He had none. Being able to put the dagger in front of his body to block the missile was already quite impressive. How could he have known that, in that short amount of time, the other side would strike him with a sword, stab with him a spear, and shoot him with missiles?

The explosion from the Anti-Tank Missiles engulfed Deception. The shockwave threw Deception into a wall.

There were two other players fighting below the wall! They weren’t too surprised seeing someone get blasted over here, but when they glanced at him, they noticed he didn’t have a guild tag above his head. He was by himself, so they ignored him.

Deception slid down the wall. When he thought back on what had just happened, not only did his Shadow Clone Technique not get him any closer to the teleport formation, it had actually caused him to end up farther away.

Directly use a high-leveled skill!

Deception immediately began forming the hand seals for Shadow Dance.

He saw that there was still some distance between him and Lord Grim. He felt like even with those long-range attacks, he would be able to complete the seals in time.

One advantage of playing as a ninja was that forming seals didn’t affect their movement speed. Even the Elementalist’s “Mobile Cast” reduced the Elementalist’s movement speed drastically when it was used.

Ninjas didn’t need to worry about such life threatening danger. Deception’s hands and legs moved in a blur. He dodged left and right. He also hoped Lord Grim’s attacks would hit other players.

But how could Ye Xiu make such rookie mistakes? Even so, because of this, his long-ranged attacks weren’t as effective as he wanted them to be. He wasn’t able to interrupt Deception’s hand seals.

Ninjutsu - Shadow Dance!

Deception instantly split into ten clones. All of them moved as if they were real, but when Deception turned around, where had Lord Grim disappeared to? F*ck! Lord Grim had ignored his clones. He ran straight to the teleport formation as if he were planning on guarding the entrance.

Would that work?

Deception didn’t think so. The closer Lord Grim was to the teleport formation, the more advantageous it was for him. With so many clones rushing towards him, he doubted Lord Grim had the ability to block all ten of them. As long as one made it over, wouldn’t he be fine?

Deception thought of this and planned on having all of his clones swarm over, but in that instant, he suddenly realized, how did all of my clones get attacked?

“Tsk tsk tsk, it seems like you’re not experienced enough.” Lord Grim’s voice rang.

Deception was depressed! When his Shadow Dance finished and his clones beautifully spread apart, the surrounding players had misunderstood.

With so many clones around them, how could they not defend against them?

As a result, they attacked them before saying anything. For that one moment, Deception had become everyone’s enemy. The surrounding players just attacked whatever clone was nearby. Deception had wanted Lord Grim to aggro everyone with his long-ranged attacks. Who would have thought that he would be the one to aggro everyone with his Shadow Dance.

Deception wasn’t the type of person who would try to explain the situation. Even if he did, no one would believe him. He immediately had his clones charge towards the teleport formation and ignored the surrounding players.

There were just too many enemies, which made it difficult for Deception to handle. Ye Xiu wasn’t going to play nice either. Just as Deception was having a hard time, Lord Grim attacked. He sent one flying away with a Falling Flower Palm, threw another one with a Fling, Repelled a different one far away. He always attacked whenever Deception had openings. Shortly aftewards, Deception soon discovered something... where did all of my clones go? With this distance…...

Pu pu pu pu pu…….

Half of his clones went poof. Lord Grim had scattered them too far apart. No matter which Heart he chose, they wouldn’t be able to cover the entire situation.

To think his Shadow Dance would be broken just like that. Deception still wanted to try with the remaining half, but he immediately realized that it wouldn’t work!

If the remaining half of shadow clones rushed forward one after the other, Lord Grim would have enough time to send them flying away one at a time again. If they had rushed forward in a swarm, the skill’s duration would run out before the strategy would be a success!

And just like this, Shadow Dance became useless.

Chapter 667: Talking While Fighting

All of Deception’s clones disappeared because the skill duration had ended. The good news was that all the aggroed players had realized those clones hadn’t been targeting them, so they didn’t attack him. If not, they would have kept chasing him forever. His real body would have nowhere to run!

Ninjutsu - Hundred Streams.

Deception still wanted charge through. He cast another skill and a hundred streams of water leaped towards Lord Grim to block his path. Just this attack alone posed no threat to Ye Xiu. He easily sidestepped it. Deception moved in the opposite direction and threw a smoke bomb.

Deception’s ninja sense was quite good. After using all of his ninja tools at Darkness City, he had immediately restocked his ninja tools after reviving.

Purple smoke billowed outwards. This was one area where Smoke Bomb was better than the Spitfire’s Smoke Bullet. The former’s effects took place extremely quickly compared to the latter. In return, Smoke Bomb’s area of effect was much smaller than Smoke Bullet. Deception merely wanted to use the Smoke Bomb to act as a wall, so that Lord Grim wouldn’t know which direction he was heading.

As soon he saw the purple smoke appeared, Deception immediately began moving, when he suddenly heard a loud rumble above him. He tilted his head upwards and he saw Lord Grim with a propellor rotating above his head. He had used Rotor Wings to float over the purple smoke. Deception’s sneaky movements could clearly be seen. At this moment, Deception truly felt like an idiot.

Lord Grim had the Rotor Wings dive down and retract in mid-air. A sword light flashed. Right when Deception dodged, he heard a boom. An explosion from below his feet sent him tumbling away. Deception tilted his head down to look down. Only a few remnant of scattered rocks could be seen. Even so, he recognized it as the Mechanic’s Machine Trace.

Why didn’t I see it?

Deception wanted to cry. It was because it had come out of the purple smoke! When he threw the Smoke Bomb, his own vision had been blocked as well, allowing the opponent to utilize it.

Because of this explosion, Deception had to stabilize himself. He couldn’t dodge Lord Grim’s Falling Light Blade as a result and crashed into the ground. He immediately recovered after landing, but Lord Grim had already rushed over. Lord Grim used a Falling Flower Palm and sent Deception flying away from the teleport formation.

I can’t beat him…...

Deception started to have thoughts of retreating. His own skills had been used against him as a cover for his opponent’s sneak attack. It truly made Deception feel defeated.

If I can’t beat him, then I should run!

Deception had quite the natural gift when it came to preserving his life. Once he made his decision, as he fell to the ground, instead of heading towards the teleport formation, he turned around and ran.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim naturally chased after him. His appearance looked funny, but the stats were no laughing matter. Ye Xiu was confident that his movement speed was enough to deal with Deception.

When he chased after him, he felt like Deception’s speed was a bit slow. Deception wasn’t just running to his next destination. He was running for his life!

Ye Xiu had a hard time understanding, but after looking carefully at Deception, he noticed that his equipment was a bit strange. Only now did he suddenly remember that, when Deception died, he had dropped two pieces of equipment. Loulan Slash had regarded it in disdain, but it was still a rare piece of equipment amongst normal players. Those two pieces of equipment probably gave him some movement speed bonuses. Without them now, of course Deception’s movement speed would be affected.

With his advantage, Ye Xiu wasn’t any under pressure. He wasn’t in a hurry either. He chased after Deception, all the while firing at him.

Deception didn’t really have much of a plan. He just knew that he couldn’t charge through to the teleport formation, so he wanted to rely on his speed to shrug Lord Grim off. He originally had confidence, but as he ran, Lord Grim kept following behind him, neither too far, nor too close. Lord Grim occasionally fired a few shots, annoying him very much. From the looks of it, Lord Grim probably had energy to spare. Was Lord Grim just playing with him?

Deception turned his head in despair. Lord Grim’s funny-looking appearance! It really was eye-catching, but at this moment, Deception finally noticed that he had switched equipment.

It’s over. I probably don’t have the movement speed advantage anymore!

Deception immediately thought of this point. The other side was chasing after him in a very relaxed manner.

If he couldn’t rely on his movement speed to shrug him off, his only choice was to hide. As a result, Deception began climbing over walls and crawling through holes and tunnels. He tried to use whatever he could to block his pursuer’s line of sight.

But none of it worked.

Several minutes passed. Lord Grim was still following after him. Deception couldn’t shrug him off or beat him in a fight. Lord Grim never got too close either.

“Maybe that’s the limit of his movement speed and it happens to be the same as mine, so he can’t actually catch me?” Deception thought.

“If that’s the case, then I just need to be patient!” Deception didn’t give up. He was frequently had to wait for opportunities to come when scrap picking, so he had quite a lot of perseverance and patience.

What Deception didn’t know was that Lord Grim had another reason for not catching up to him.

“Okay. Me and Steamed Bun are here.” Tang Rou messaged Ye Xiu.

“Oh, then let’s begin.” Ye Xiu replied and had Lord Grim suddenly speed up.

Deception had been planning on being patient, when he suddenly heard footsteps getting closer to him.

Is it that guy?

Deception was startled. He couldn’t help but turn his head to look.

It really was him! Lord Grim was suddenly starting to get closer and closer to him.

Deception used every trick he knew, but none of them worked. Lord Grim caught up to him every time and was constantly getting nearer and nearer.

Shuriken, Shadow Clone Technique, Caltrops…...

None of these skills stopped Lord Grim from closing in.

Hand seals!

Deception began forming hand seals. He once again used Shadow Dance!

This time, when his shadow clones appeared. Deception immediately pounced towards Lord Grim. He wanted to take advantage of the chaos to find a character that Lord Grim failed to notice and sneak out, but on his way here, Deception knew that he had to use the terrain effectively.

Shadow Dance.

Deception really liked to use this move. It was no wonder that he was quite good with it, but in front of Ye Xiu, he was still too green.

For Ye Xiu, it was wishful thinking if Deception wanted to use these shadow clones to bother him. He used a few skills and easily sent the few shadow clones around him flying away. When Ye Xiu looked around, he quickly noticed the clone trying to sneak away. At this moment, Deception realized that he had been completely seen through.

With a gunshot, that sneaky clone was hit in the butt and Deception’s heart hit rock bottom. He knew that his move had once again been seen through and dismantled.

The heart of shadow switched. He controlled his clones and looked for a different direction, where Lord Grim wasn’t paying too much attention to. Found it!

Deception saw an opening and immediately switched his heart of shadow over. He hastily tried to run. This time, Lord Grim directly used a Shadow Clone Technique to block his path.

Was this because this opening had been a trap, or because Lord Grim had insanely fast reaction speed? Deception didn’t know, but Lord Grim blocking his path in front of him was a reality. Run!

He immediately switched hearts, but his shadow clones suddenly disappeared. The skill duration had ended again!

Deception had been so busy figuring a way out that he had forgotten something as important as this. Such a low-leveled mistake shouldn’t happen to an expert.

“What’s the point in scrap picking all day? Is this really how you make your living?” Ye Xiu asked. It was a rare opportunity for them to meet face to face.

Deception turned around and wanted to run. This time, Lord Grim closed in on him. Ye Xiu wouldn’t give him an opportunity to escape. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened up and he immediately attacked. Deception wasn’t able to block it and it became a life and death battle. Deception’s health rapidly fell.

He struggled and struggled instead of leaving his computer like he had last time, when he had been surrounded by Heavenly Justice. However, it was futile. The usual moves that worked against other players all seemed like child’s play to Lord Grim, who easily dealt with them.

“You’ve got so much talent! Scrap picking is just a waste! You should be using your talent in the right places!” Ye Xiu beat him up while talking the entire duration of the beating. Deception was about to go crazy.

“The finals are taking place right now. Do you even know what that is?” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim’s spear stabbed through Deception’s body.

“It’s a competition between the best players and characters in all of Glory!” Ye Xiu continued.

“You don’t even know that? You’re like an expert who knows nothing about the outside world!” Lord Grim sent Deception crashing into a wall.

“What does any of that have to do with me?!” Even though Deception’s face was sliding down the wall, it didn’t stop him from talking.

“I’m forming a team right now. Would you like to join? There will be a salary as well as living accommodations included!” As Ye Xiu beat him, he sent him an invite. He was acting like a bandit from the Water Margins.

“What are you talking about?” Deception clearly didn’t appreciate this bandit’s conduct.

“You’re skilled. Picking up trash for a living is too much of a waste of that skill.” Ye Xiu said.

“What I pick up is never trash!” Deception said.

“Tsk.” Ye Xiu looked down at him in disdain, “That’s because you’ve never seen the really good stuff.”

“Such as the weapon in my hands. Have you ever seen one like it before?” Ye Xiu said.

“......” Deception had obviously never seen it before, but then again, Ye Xiu’s umbrella was a bit too much. No one in Glory would have ever seen this weapon before.

“This is what you call top-quality. Pick it up and you’ll see.” Ye Xiu said.

“This is……”

Bang! Deception was once again hit, but this time, he didn’t stand back up.

“Oops……” Ye Xiu was startled, “He died….. I was too focused on talking and didn’t pay attention to his health. He seemed like he wanted to say something?” Ye Xiu muttered.

Chapter 668: Revival Point

Deception died. His ghost floated around. The drop rates from PKing in the Heavenly Domain lived up to its reputation. When he died, another piece of his equipment dropped. The ghost Deception could only quietly watch as Lord Grim take his equipment away.

Deception had been mentally prepared. Even though he was sad about his death, he wasn’t too angry either. Soon afterwards, he chose to revive.

When he revived, Deception checked his inventory. He had lost a leg armor piece and a pendant in the Darkness Palace, which he made up for with some make-do equipment. This time, he had dropped a ring.

Good. It wasn’t too painful of a loss.

Losing equipment would always be painful. Deception could only console himself with the three materials on him.

What do I do now? Is that guy still going to be guarding the teleport formation? Deception thought. He didn’t take any of what Ye Xiu had just said to heart. However, what he didn’t know was that the moment he died, Ye Xiu messaged Tang Rou and Steamed Bun.

“I’m here! I’m here! I’m watching the place closely!!” Steamed Bun immediately began looking around the revival point.

Finding Deception at the revival point wasn’t easy. There was a world war going on, so the revival point was very busy. Not only were there a lot of players reviving. There were also a lot of players fighting around it. These players were similar to Tang Rou and Steamed Bun and had come to the revival point to chase after and kill more players. All of the revival points in the cities had turned into intense battlefields.

Even though the revival point wasn’t a safe area, a revived player would be protected by the system for a brief duration. It was similar to logging on. During this brief duration, the character would be protected from all damage they received, but the character also wouldn’t be able to deal damage.

After Deception revived, he checked his inventory to console himself, while running out of this revival point. If not, when the system’s protection wore off, while the players might not be aiming for him, it was hard to avoid taking splash damage.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun saw the chaos around the revival point and obviously wouldn’t look for trouble. The two characters watched from the edges of the battlefield.

“Over here over here over here!!!” Steamed Bun messaged Tang Rou.

“Which way is over here…..” Tang Rou said helplessly, “Coordinates?”

No response. Tang Rou turned her head to look at Steamed Bun’s screen. Steamed Bun and Deception had already started fighting with each other. Tang Rou checked the coordinates and had Soft Mist rush over.

“You punk! Forfeit your life!” Steamed Bun shouted as he lifted the brick in his hand.

Deception looked and immediately recognized that the other side had set up an ambush here beforehand. He was quite annoyed. When the brick flew at him, he tilted his head to dodge it. The brick whooshed past him and slammed into the back of a Blue Brook Guild player in the midst of a battle.

Steamed Bun hadn’t consider whether a mistake on his part would pull aggro. He only reacted after the injuries had already been made.

“Oops!” Steamed Bun shouted. He crouched down in an attempt to hide from the other side.

In reality, the battlefield at the revival point was so chaotic that if an accidental attack occurred, the player hit by it could only consider himself unlucky. The player didn’t even have time to bicker!

Deception saw this scene and thought about how stupid Steamed Bun must be. He immediately turned around to leave. He had no plans on fighting him. Steamed Bun saw that the person he accidentally hit wasn’t going to look for trouble, so he focused again. He shouted “Don’t run!” Steamed Bun shot forward. His character flew through the air as his two legs headed for Deception.

Brawler skill: Powerful Knee Strike.

Brawlers had a street-style way of fighting. Sand Toss, Brick, and Poison Needle skills were all dirty fighting moves. Skills such as Powerful Knee Strike and Tyrannical Chain Punch showed their violent and unrestrained fighting style.

This Powerful Knee Strike was fast and fierce, but Steamed Bun liked to talk when he attacked. Deception heard his loud shout and turned around to look. When he saw the two legs flying towards him, he immediately dodged it. Steamed Bun missed and landed on the ground. He got up and charged at Deception.

Deception quickly formed a hand seal. His character instantly tunneled into the ground to dodge Steamed Bun’s charge. Then, he drilled out of the earth and stabbed towards Steamed Bun Invasion.

Steamed Bun reacted fast. He had Steamed Bun Invasion swing his arms horizontally to block it. His arms hit Deception’s hands and knocked them aside, successfully defending against the stab.

Brawler skill: Tiger Flips the Mountain.

The skill name sounded very intelligent, but players liked to call it “Protect My Face”. From its nickname, it could be seen that it was just a simple defensive move used in the streets. Of course, the game wasn’t going to call it something as lame as “Protect My Face”. That just wouldn’t be right.

After having his dagger blocked, Deception leapt up and used a Bird Fall from high in the air. His two feet stepped on Steamed Bun Invasion’s shoulder. With a whoosh, he flew past Steamed Bun Invasion.

Even though these guys were quite good, they were much easier to deal with compared to Lord Grim. Right when Deception thought in this way, he heard a “Pow!” His head had been smashed in by a brick.

Being hit by a brick from behind had a 100% chance of inducing a .4 second stun.

This meant that even though Deception was still in midair, he would be stunned. Characters in a stunned state couldn’t use skills or make any movements, so he crashed headfirst into the ground.

F*ck!

Deception was sad! Why did this guy like Bricks so much? He wasn’t using it intelligently either. He just used it as soon as it came off cooldown. Even so, he had been hit from behind. Deception was furious.

Fortunately, he had been in midair previously! Even though he lost his balance from the stun, he had still been able to gain some distance. He took some damage from the fall, but the stun wore off fairly quickly. Deception got up and threw a Shuriken. Only then did he adjust his camera. F*ck! The person moving towards him wasn’t Steamed Bun Invasion.

Battle Mage!

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had finally arrived.

Shurikens could briefly stun a target, so it was good at interrupting spells, but it was worthless in front of Dragon Breaks the Ranks, which gave the user Super Armor. Apart from grabs, no other skill could interrupt it.

The shurikens hit Soft Mist and did negligible damage, but it wouldn’t stop her from activating the skill.

Skills with super armor were equally tyrannical. In the blink of an eye, Soft Mist closed in on him. Her spear ripped through the wind as it penetrated Deception’s body.

Deception was sent flying. Soft Mist was a physical-oriented Battle Mage, so Dragon Breaks the Ranks was utilized to its maximum potential. Tang Rou never let up in a battle though. She followed up with a Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. Her spear transformed into a dragon, which shot towards Deception and devoured him. The magic undulations poured into Deception in a burst of colors.

“I feel like he’s much weaker now.” Steamed Bun said from the sidelines.

“It’s probably because you have better equipment now?” Tang Rou said.

“Oh oh, right!” Steamed Bun realized.

Following afterwards, the two coordinated with each other and Deception’s bitter days had truly come. He didn’t even plan on fighting them anymore. He just wanted to escape, but now that they had switched equipment, their strength had improved significantly. Deception could no longer handle both of them together. He had also lost experience and equipment. He had three mismatched pieces of equipment and his stats had been reduced to that of a Level 69.

“Do we just kill him?” Steamed Bun asked.

“Probably?” Tang Rou wasn’t sure.

“Let me ask!” Steamed Bun stood up and shouted: “Senior, do we kill him?”

“Huh…..” Ye Xiu jumped up in surprise at Steamed Bun’s sudden shout. His Lord Grim was heading towards the revival point, but it seemed like Steamed Bun and Tang Rou were fine on their own?

“I was just talking with him to see if he wanted to join us. How about you keep asking him?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Understood.” Steamed Bun sat down and immediately said: “Punk, what a rare opportunity! Our senior actually recognizes your skill. Have considered his offer?”

Consider my ass! When did I say I would consider it? Deception was being hunted down repeatedly. How could he be in a good mood? He also couldn’t beat his enemies. This type of powerlessness was very frustrating.

“Why aren’t you talking? Are you thinking about it? Is three seconds long enough?” Steamed Bun said.

“......”

“One, two, three…..” Steamed Bun counted.

“......”

“You’re still not talking? Is three seconds not enough? Then how many seconds do you need?” Steamed Bun asked.

“Enough!!” Deception couldn’t help but shout.

“If it’s enough, then where’s your answer!” Steamed Bun said.

“I’m saying I’ve had enough of your chattering!” Deception said.

“Then did you think about it?” Steamed Bun asked.

“......” Deception was speechless. He wasn’t the talkative type, let alone keeping up with Steamed Bun’s thought process.

“He’s about to die.” Tang Rou reminded.

“Hurry hurry. Drink some potions!” Steamed Bun hastily urged Deception.

“.......” Deception wanted to cry. In order to survive, he had chugging potions, but potions had cooldowns. They were on cooldown right now. Did you think I didn’t want to drink more?

Tang Rou felt like Steamed Bun’s way of speaking was completely brainless, so she explained: “We’re planning on forming a team. Are you interested in joining us?”

“Not interested!” Deception ground his teeth.

“Okay!” Tang Rou replied. She attacked and ended Deception’s misery.

“I……” Deception had wanted to say something. His character died though, so his voice didn’t come out. His ghost floated around again. Deception was speechless. This sister was so ruthless!

Afterwards, Deception saw Steamed Bun Invasion run forward and pick up something from his corpse.

Another piece of equipment…. lost…..

Chapter 669: Three Tasks

Deception’s corpse lay on the ground. He chose not to revive. He knew that the other side wouldn’t leave just like that. He couldn’t beat them, nor could he run away from them. If he revived, it would just be a never ending loop.

It seemed like logging off was the most appropriate choice in this situation.

However, Deception wasn’t willing to! He had played this game for so long, and he had aggroed a lot of players during his scrap picking career. It wasn’t his first time dying, but it was certainly his first time being camped at the revival point and being unable to escape from them.

But what could he do?

He couldn’t beat them. He truly didn’t have the ability.

Let alone Lord Grim, fighting even Steamed Bun or Soft Mist was hard enough. With those two fighting him together, Deception couldn’t see any chance of winning.

He had always played alone, so he didn’t have any friends in the game. If he were any other player, most of them would have called their friends to help them escape by now.

Seeing how Soft Mist and Steamed Bun were still standing there, checking that his corpse hadn’t turned into a gravestone, Deception knew that they weren’t planning on leaving.

I guess I should log off…..

Deception didn’t have any other choice. He could only log off.

By the time Lord Grim arrived, his corpse still hadn’t turned into a tombstone, but it had already disappeared, indicating that he was offline.

“He escaped.” Steamed Bun sighed with regret.

“What did he say in the end?” Ye Xiu asked.

“He said ‘I…..’ and then he died.” Steamed Bun described it vividly. He even had his Steamed Bun Invasion lay on the ground as if he had truly died.

Ye Xiu couldn’t do anything about it. Lord Grim turned around and faced Soft Mist.

“I asked if he was interested in joining us. He said no.” Tang Rou said.

“Tsk……” Ye Xiu sighed. It seemed like getting Deception to join wasn’t going to be an easy task. The key point was that he wasn’t an ordinary player either. If a normal player got an invite to join a pro team, the player would be extraordinarily happy. Even if the player couldn’t accept it because of his family or some other reason, every player desired to be a pro player, but this Deception only scap picked and didn’t seem to care about anything else in the world. Ye Xiu wasn’t sure how to persuade someone like him. There weren’t any players in the pro scene who liked to scrap pick…..

“Hu…… how tiring…..” Just as he was sighing, the door to the practice room opened and Chen Guo came in out of breath. The finals were the finals after all. Even though Excellent Era wasn’t playing, Happy Internet Cafe was still packed. Any team that entered the finals would have plenty of fans.

When the first round of the finals ended, Samsara celebrated, while Blue Rain cried. The fans of the two teams taunting each other was hard to avoid. Fortunately, the fans were reasonable enough and nothing escalated too chaotically. However, keeping everything under control was still exhausting work. It hadn’t been easy getting everyone to leave. During that time, they had defeated two guilds, killed a boss, and killed Deception twice.

“Today’s match was pretty good.” Chen Guo was obviously here to discuss the match with them. Chen Guo didn’t care too much about either team, but it was still an intense and entertaining match.

“Yeah.” Ye Xiu answered.

Chen Guo looked at the practice room. Something wasn’t right! None of them had the excitement that they should have had after watching such a brilliant match. Even though she had come late and they had already finished discussing it, shouldn’t they still have a happy expression on them?

“What’s wrong?” Chen Guo walked around in a circle questioningly. Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, and Steamed Bun weren’t doing anything right now. Only Wei Chen was busy. Truthfully, when Ye Xiu and the others had defeated the two guilds and killed Deception, Wei Chen’s shouting was louder than their own.

Wei Chen was participating in the world war! And as Samsara’s second elite group leader, wherever the battle was cruel and intense, he would have to appear there. When Chen Guo turned to look at Wei Chen’s screen, she saw all sorts of skills flying around everywhere. Wei Chen’s Warlock was running around amidst the chaos. All of the players around him had guild tags of the top guilds.

Chen Guo had been monitoring the situation downstairs. There was no way she would know about what was happening in the game.

“What’s going on? Are they fighting for a wild boss?” Chen Guo asked.

“They’re fighting.” Ye Xiu said.

“What do you mean?”

“The fires from the finals have reached the game.” Ye Xiu said.

“How exciting!” Chen Guo immediately turned on a computer and logged into the game.

Ye Xiu had just got in contact with Loulan Slash. Deception had logged off. Ye Xiu and the others couldn’t stay there guarding the entire time, so they asked Loulan Slash for help to pay special attention to his whereabouts.

“Okay. I got it.” When Loulan Slash heard Deception had already died twice, had been forced to log off, and Ye Xiu still wasn’t done, he deeply felt that offending this God was a very scary matter. When this God pursued and killed players, he did so with everything he had.

Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze entered the game. She walked around and naturally saw the battles going on everywhere. These battles had started since the end of the first round of the finals. Now, they had reached their peak. Walking around on the street wasn’t so bad though. The players feeling it the most were the elites of the Club guilds, such as Wei Chen. They were fighting nonstop without rest.

As for Ye Xiu and the others? Loulan Slash had gotten them new equipment. They were max leveled and max skilled. Getting better equipment from the game than what they had now was pointless. No equipment in the game could compare to those in the pro scene. In order to get to a pro level, they would have to create their own equipment, which required wild bosses. Ye Xiu hoped for Loulan Slash to message him about bosses, but there just weren’t any more spawning right now. Without anything to do, Ye Xiu led Tang Rou and Steamed Bun around to form a three-player scrap picking team…….

Correct. Right after killing the infamous scrap picker Deception, Ye Xiu and the others went to go scrap picking.

With a huge war going on, there were plenty of opportunities to pick up scraps. However, even a master scrap picker like Deception didn’t dare to rashly move and instead went to Darkness Palace to do something. This only showed how difficult scrap picking would be right now.

However, there would always be players who welcomed challenges. With the fires of war spreading everywhere, it was sometimes hard to tell who was there to fight and who was there to pick up scraps. These fights were because of the competition between the pro teams. Players with the Club guild tags on them were only a very small portion of the fans. Those with guilds and those without guilds participated in this war regardless.

Ye Xiu and the others really had nothing to do without any wild bosses out there. From a training perspective, letting Tang Rou and Steamed Bun participate in these chaotic battles would be good practice.

Facing Ye Xiu’s logical and confident words, Chen Guo had no way of arguing against him.

Because they would be regarding this as training, they would obviously go to the most difficult places to scrap pick.

“Old Wei, where are you?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Ah? What did you say? Speak louder!” Wei Chen roared.

“I’m saying, where are you?” Ye Xiu shouted.

“Oh, you’re talking!” Wei Chen turned his head over.

“Stop talking nonsense. Who else in the game would call you Old Wei?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I’m feeling a bit dizzy. What is it?” Wei Chen had only glanced at Ye Xiu, before focusing on the game again.

“I’m asking, where are you?” Ye Xiu asked. Instead of waiting for Wei Chen to reply, he just looked at Wei Chen’s screen. A few seconds after Ye Xiu finished looking, Wei Chen suddenly replied: “Why don’t you look yourself?”

Busy! Wei Chen was truly too busy! He was responsible for leading the group as well as his own character. He had to do two things at once. With Ye Xiu being the third, he had a difficult time managing everything.

After Ye Xiu checked for himself, he notified Tang Rou and Steamed Bun. The three of them immediately set out. Chen Guo wanted to participate too, but seeing how chaotic the battle was from Wei Chen’s screen, Chen Guo felt like it would be best if she didn’t become a burden.

A few minutes later, Wei Chen suddenly said: “You’re coming over? To do what?”

“Scrap pick.” Ye Xiu confirmed that Wei Chen was talking to him and replied back.

“F*ck! Why? What’s there to pick up?” Wei Chen had left the pro scene a long time ago and his perspective had gone back to a normal player’s perspective, but now that he planned on going back to the pro scene, his perspective quickly changed back. None of the equipment in the game was worth squat.

“It’s a rare opportunity. We might not get anything useful, but it will still be good for the guild storage. We’ll have to form a guild sooner or later.” Ye Xiu said.

Wei Chen didn’t refute his statement. How could he not know about the importance of a guild for their team? In the early days of the pro scene, the pro players had to manage the guild as well as practice. During Wei Chen’s time as a pro, he had done both too. Speaking of which, Wei Chen was having trouble adapting to the current structure, where pro players put all of their effort into their own matches. He always felt like pro players, who completely threw the game aspect aside, weren’t reliable.

Ye Xiu and the other two soon arrived at the battlefield. There were corpses and gravestones littered all over the ground, but this also made it easier for Ye Xiu and the others to find dropped equipment.

“Seven o’clock. Coordinates 25865, 45726. Grab that weapon!” Ye Xiu ordered and the three began their scrap picking journey…...

“Little Tang, don’t keep fighting!!” Ye Xiu had said these words who knew how many times. When Tang Rou fought against someone, she would sometimes get too engrossed in it.

“Steamed Bun, don’t pick up that one. It’s worthless.” Ye Xiu often had to remind Steamed Bun this. Steamed Bun would put whatever equipment he found into his inventory.

“Oka okay. That’s good enough. Let’s go!” Once they filled up their inventories, Ye Xiu hastily had them leave the battle. Right after they stored these pieces of equipment in their storages, they received a message from Loulan Slash about a wild boss.

“Let’s go!” The three changed directions, heading towards a different map.

“These are the three main tasks that we will be doing in the near future.” Ye Xiu said in a serious tone: “Scrap picking, killing bosses, and killing Deception.”

Chapter 670: A New Beginning

The news of another Level 70 boss excited Loulan Slash. His gloominess over losing three uncommon materials to Deception had diminished significantly. Taking advantage while the top guilds had no way of interfering in wild boss fights was certainly something to be happy about.

These kinds of opportunities didn’t come often. Wild bosses were one of the most important objectives for the Club guilds. It wouldn’t be too excessive to say that it was their reasons for existing.

After contacting Ye Xiu, who replied that he would immediately head out, Loulan Slash felt at ease. The battle at Darkness Palace had proven that a God leading a group battle could turn the situation from a disaster to a walk in the park. In the beginning, Loulan Slash had even been worried Ye Xiu’s individual influence would be too insignificant to matter!

While he was happy about this point, Loulan Slash couldn’t help but worry about the future of his team: if a God’s ability to lead a team was this incredible, what about us? How will we beat him?

Loulan Slash was both happy and unhappy. The first pro player he bumped into was a top of the top player. The bad part was that Ye Xiu became his reference, crushing Loulan Slash and his team’s confidence. They often realized things afterwards that only made it worse for them. Loulan Slash felt like he was already forcing himself with Team Heavenly Swords, but giving up now wasn’t a possibility. At this point, he had abandoned his initial ambitious hopes and shifted towards a more stable approach.

When Ye Xiu came over, he came over with three others, instead of two. Chen Guo could also follow them and participate. It wasn’t like Chen Guo had no experience hunting Level 70 wild bosses. But her experiences could be summarized as “Hey, there’s a boss! Let’s go try and kill it.” and then die to the boss.

A wild boss wasn’t something that could be beaten by a random group of players. Even the elite groups of the top guilds would die to them from time to time!

So to be more accurate, Chen Gu had never killed a wild boss herself, but rather had been killed by one. Now that there was an opportunity to kill one, she obviously wanted a part of the glory.

The wild boss was the World Tree’s Forest Guardian Vich.

Vich was a complicated boss. Its skills spanned through all of the classes. He used a rifle and could utilize any of the Gunner class skills. Apart from that, he was also proficient in traps from the Thief class. There were often traps hidden all over the forest, making it very frustrating for players to explore the map. Apart from these two attack methods, Vich could also use….. Cleric spells.

A boss that could heal himself! This was undoubtedly very troublesome for players. Interrupting his heals were crucial to hunting him down.

For the Club guilds, winning control of the boss was most important. Killing the boss itself wasn’t too big of an issue for them. However, Heavenly Justice didn’t have any experience killing wild bosses. Loulan Slash was quite worried about a difficult boss like Vich.

The God Ye Xiu was in charge of PvP, while he was responsible for killing the boss itself. How do we actually kill this boss? He was currently looking up guides as references! If the God successfully completed his task and beat the other guilds, and his group ended up getting wiped by the boss, how shameful would that be? If he also needed to rely on Ye Xiu to kill the boss, Loulan Slash would feel too ashamed to ask him for half of the materials.

He felt extremely uneasy. In the end, Loulan Slash felt like he should ask Ye Xiu to teach him!

“Oh, you’ve never killed it before?” Ye Xiu said.

“Yeah!” Loulan Slash replied.

“Let me see!” Ye Xiu said.

“What?”

“To kill this boss, there are a few key things to be wary of.” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh?” Loulan Slash hastily grabbed a pen and prepared to write everything down.

“Pay attention to the positions of your troops. They can never be in a straight line because Vich uses a rifle. Along with the power of a wild boss, he has the ability to have his shots penetrate multiple targets.”

“Got it.” Loulan Slash replied, but he didn’t write anything down.

“This boss also has traps, especially huge AoE poison and ice explosions. If players get hit, you have to make sure to heal them as soon as possible. Ice is mainly for control purposes. Its damage isn’t so bad. but for huge AoE explosions, a single person stepping on a trap could affect a huge area, so when an ice explosion occurs, you have to control the boss’s pathing well. If the boss makes some unexpected move during this time, your players might not be able to react because of the ice explosion hindering their movements. One way to deal with this is to intentionally step on an ice trap, when the situation is still under control, and then everyone can just stand still and attack.” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay okay, is there more?” Loulan Slash asked.

“More? The boss can also heal. Make sure you have some troops responsible for interrupting his casts.” Ye Xiu said.

“And?” Loulan Slash was still asking. He hadn’t written anything down yet. He realized that everything Ye Xiu had said was straight from the guide.

“And?” Ye Xiu asked himself. After a while, he said: “That’s it?”

“That’s all written in the guide!” Loulan Slash said.

“You’ve looked over the guide already? Then why’d you ask me?” Ye Xiu said.

Loulan Slash coughed blood. I didn’t feel very confident after reading the guide, so I thought I should ask you!

“Apart from the content in the guide, are there any other details or techniques I should know about?” Loulan Slash was patient.

But the God’s reply was devastating: “How would I know? I’ve never fought against it before either.”

Loulan Slash wanted to cry. They were all noobs here. They didn’t have anyone with experience.

After listening to Loulan Slash’s questioning, Ye Xiu could tell: “Are you afraid that you can’t kill the boss?”

“Yeah!” Loulan Slash replied. The fight against Darkness Palace’s Night Streak had scared everyone witless. If not, how else could Loulan Slash have been assassinated by Deception? It was because the battle had been so difficult that they were relieved after successfully killing Night Streak, giving Deception an opening.

Forest Guardian Vich was much more difficult to handle than Night Streak, giving Loulan Slash even less confidence in the fight.

“Oh, are there any guilds around?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yeah! Conquering Cloud has already been seen.” Loulan Slash said.

“It’s Conquering Cloud again.”

Clearly, it wasn’t just Ye Xiu and Loulan Slash who wanted to take advantage while the top guilds were at war. These small Club guilds wanted to seize this opportunity to grab some difficult to get resources.

“Yeah. They haven’t even recovered their lost experience yet and they’re here……” Loulan Slash said. Conquering Cloud had suffered huge losses and had even been pursued afterwards. Only a bit of time had passed, which wasn’t enough for them to recover that 20% loss of experience. Loulan Slash’s own stats were still red! He was Level 70, but his stats were equivalent to characters at Level 69. Even though his level hadn’t changed, his stats were still lower, so people still called it a level drop.

“That’s a good thing! You’re even worried about that?” Ye Xiu said.

“I’m worried about the boss.” Loulan Slash said.

“I’m saying that since our opponents are weaker, why don’t you go and deal with them, while I kill the boss?” Ye Xiu said.

“Uh…… what if other guilds come?” Loulan Slash said. If it was just Conquering Clouds, he had confidence in winning, but he didn’t have the skill to crush them with very few casualties. His group would certainly suffer a significant loss. If another fully prepared guild came, he wouldn’t be able to stop them.

“Then it seems like we’ll need to wait and control the situation at a later time.” Ye Xiu said.

“Let them attack it first?”

“Yeah and then we’ll kill the boss and everyone else at the same time.” Ye Xiu said.

It was quite a fierce method because, at a certain point, the first to act usually took the boss’s aggro. Taking the aggro away from them using conventional methods wasn’t likely. The only way was to completely wipe the other team or force them to leave, and then reestablish the boss’s aggro.

Apart from stopping the other side from taking the boss, it made the other side feel disgusted. Even long-time rivals wouldn’t be so fierce as to use this method. After all, in this close circle, competition was important, but if you wanted to trade materials, you had to trade with someone, no? If you offended everyone, it wouldn’t be helpful for your guild’s development down the road. As a result, the Club guilds often wouldn’t be so impulsive like what other normal players might do in these situations. Whenever a Club guild made a move, the guild held itself up to certain norms.

This sort of method not only broke these norms, but there were other things to consider as well. Loulan Slash had clearly thought about this before and hesitated towards Ye Xiu’s suggestion: “That’s not too good, no?”

“Oh? You want to leave some leeway?” Ye Xiu said.

Loulan Slash could tell that it wasn’t that Ye Xiu didn’t know about the faults of this method, yet he still wanted to use such a fierce method? He thought about it again and realized: I’m such a pig! No matter how terrible their conduct is, the one to pay the price would be Heavenly Justice. Ye Xiu was currently working as a temporary worker. Once he finishes his task, he simply takes his portion of the materials and leaves. He won’t have to bear any sort of enmity, so of course he’d want to use this method.

Thinking of this possibility, Loulan Slash rejected it and also said: “If I do that, it’ll come back to bite me in the future, no?”

“That depends on how you do things. If we do it according to what you’re thinking of, isn’t that just who gets there first, gets it? When did fighting for a wild boss ever follow the rules?” Ye Xiu said.

“Then how should we go about doing it?”

“You just need to give them the appropriate amount of face.” Ye Xiu said.

“Give them the appropriate amount of face?”

“For example, if we immediately go up, see them, intentionally not do anything, and then right when they’re about to kill the boss, we suddenly kill them. That isn’t good. However, we can wait outside of their sight for a while, pretend like we arrived late, and then attack them. No one can blame us in this scenario.” Ye Xiu said.

“Is…. there a difference?” Chen Guo asked when she heard Ye Xiu’s explanation.

Chapter 671: The Proper Way to Steal Bosses

“There’s a difference!” The person, who replied to Chen Guo, wasn’t Ye Xiu, but rather Loulan Slash. His in-game tactical skills were just so-so in Ye Xiu’s eyes, but his management ability was quite good. For example, he had seized several opportunities to maximize his team’s publicity. He utilized everything he could use, taunting the other guilds and winning numerous fans.

Now, for a sensitive and urgent issue like stealing wild bosses, he was suddenly not as arrogant as he had been when he had publicized the team. Instead, he hesitated. Loulan Slash was someone who was proper.

Snatching a wild boss wasn’t the same as fighting a verbal battle. The materials dropped from wild bosses were crucial for self-made equipment, which determined the strength of a character, and the strength of a character influenced the strength of a team. The team’s strength was the fundamental reason why Clubs existed.

Hurting someone else’s wild boss was the same as hurting their reason for existence. How could there be no difference?

This was why Loulan Slash had hesitated towards this idea. He knew very well that flinging some words at the Clubs and make them feel disgusted wasn’t the same.

Fighting for a boss required appropriate behavior.

Correct, appropriate behavior.

Chen Guo felt like there was no difference between Ye Xiu’s two suggestions, but Loulan Slash immediately understood that one of these was much more appropriate.

Waiting on the side and suddenly ambushing them, right when the other side was about to kill the boss, and hastily joining the battle after arriving late might seem like the same thing, but the former appeared intentional, while the latter didn’t.

Appearing intentional would portray them as unkind and savage.

Alternately, appearing unintentional placed them within the norms.

Thus, it didn’t matter if you actually appeared late or not, you would have to do it that way. This was what Ye Xiu meant by pretending to arrive late.

Loulan Slash didn’t need Ye Xiu to explain it to him, but it took Chen Guo quite a while to understand after listening to Ye Xiu’s explanation.

With the method decided, there was an art to arriving late.

There was a fine line between the two methods. Everyone knew that inside and out, so if you wanted to pretend to arrive late, the other side wouldn’t let you do that so easily.

If you want to arrive late, you had to know their location, but what if you didn’t have any information on them?

Experienced Clubs would definitely confirm the surroundings were safe before engaging a wild boss alone. They might even arrange for a fake group to misdirect others.

The accuracy of their information was crucial for “arriving late”. Heavenly Justice still had members surveying the situation, but these eyes would certainly be killed off once the other side began attacking the boss.

There were too many things to take care of when fighting against a wild boss. If it was just strength alone, the experience accumulated from thousands of years of struggles between mankind would be wasted.

The small details involved were another part of the game. Loulan Slash couldn’t think of anything. In the end, he waited for Ye Xiu to suggest something.

“I’ll go!” Ye Xiu sighed.

At this moment, only an expert would be able to continue surveying the situation without being caught, and who here was more of an expert than Ye Xiu?

“You…… aren’t you too noticeable!” Chen Guo said.

“It doesn’t matter who goes.” Ye Xiu said and then said to Loulan Slash: “Keep on the lookout for those on the way here. See if any other guilds are also moving. There shouldn’t just be one guild looking to take advantage of the situation!”

“Don’t worry about that!” Loulan Slash had thought of it before and had already made arrangements. Having Ye Xiu tell him how to do everything was too shameful. However, even though he tried to avoid these situations, he was once again given a lesson by Ye Xiu…… Loulan Slash didn’t know if he would ever graduate from this course.

And at this moment, those at the front reported back. Conquering Cloud had gathered together and were about to start attacking the boss.

Conquering Cloud didn’t relax, after seeing that there were no enemies nearby. They still dispatched players to clear the area.

When they cleared the area, they didn’t directly kill anyone. Instead, they gave a warning, saying that they were about to start killing a wild boss, and that they should stay away because it was dangerous. Of course, players could insist on staying. Even so, they wouldn’t kill anyone. As Club guilds, they had to pay attention to their public image, especially when they did things with their guild tags displayed. Then what do they do if the players insist on staying? They would take the next step and make it clear that wild bosses were difficult things to kill in Glory. No one knows what might happen, so it would be best to be careful.

Sometimes, they might be more direct and make it even clearer that the battle can get chaotic. Not just the boss’s attacks, but their attacks might accidentally hit you, so don’t blame us for not telling you beforehand. It’s not like we can add you into our group.

At this point, if you weren’t stupid, you would know what you had to do. If you still insisted on staying, they would definitely “lose control” of the situation and envelop any bystanders into the battle. Once that happened, they would express their apologies. Nicer groups might say “We’ll help you pick up your equipment when you die. Contact us to get it back.” Lazier groups might not care. In any case, they were busy killing the wild boss. If they ignored the items that you dropped, that was also very reasonable too, no?

The Heavenly Justice players at the front didn’t have their guild tags next to them to avoid trouble with Conquering Clouds. Don’t look at how a low-grade Club guild like Conquering Clouds couldn’t usually take any wild bosses, they would still follow these unwritten procedures.

The players at the front clearly thought their troops would be arriving soon, so they insisted on staying. Conquering Cloud would naturally “bring them into the battle and kill them accidentally”, but when they messaged the guild leader, they received a reply telling them to retreat.

“What? We’re not killing the boss?” The information-gathering players were puzzled.

“There’s been a change of plans.” Loulan Slash replied, “Come back! We’re at 48711, 49128. Withdraw and meet up with us!”

The information-gathering players didn’t know what was going on, so they followed orders and left. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was currently rushing over to the boss’s last known location.

Usually, while clearing the field, they would find a place without anyone there and lure the boss over.

Glory was a huge world. Even though there were a lot of players, it wasn’t packed. In addition, not everyone was online for the entire day, so finding a place without anyone nearby wasn’t difficult. As for how to quietly move the boss away, that depended on each guild.

When Lord Grim rushed to the scene, let alone moving the boss away, Conquering Cloud wasn’t even done clearing away the field!

Small Club guilds had their own difficulties too!

Even though they were also Club guilds, weak teams didn’t have much of a status in the players’ eyes. The strength of weak teams were still far greater than normal in-game players, but that should be the case for pro teams anyways! Weak teams were only weak relative to the pro scene. However, to the players, if you kept on losing and losing, you were nothing but trash, even if you were far more skilled than them.

If I look down on you, then I naturally won’t acknowledge you as my superior. Even though I know that it might get troublesome if I don’t leave, leaving just because you tell me to is too disgraceful. I’ll look around for a bit and then leave. Is that not okay?

In front of weak Club guilds, even normal players were starting to talk about face.

In the end, only a third of the nearby players actually left. Conquering Cloud’s guild leader was depressed! Their team wasn’t strong enough! It could even be felt in game. They had just been bullied by Heavenly Justice and now even normal players were looking down on them.

The guild leader really wanted to order his troops to slaughter these bystanders and let them have a taste of their Conquering Cloud’s might. Unfortunately, he knew he couldn’t do it. It wasn’t easy being a little team’s guild leader!

If it were just a few players, accidentally bringing them into the fight and killing them wouldn’t be a problem, but two thirds of them remained. If all of them were enveloped, it would be too obvious. Conquering Cloud’s guild leader was frustrated! He didn’t know what to do yet, when he received a report: not only were there many players still remaining, there was someone else coming over.

“F*ck, who is it!” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader asked a meaningless question. This was a leveling area. There were plenty of players around anyways. Even though there was PK going on everywhere during this world war, it shouldn’t be surprising for someone to wander in.

But when he asked this question, he actually got a legitimate answer.

“It’s Lord Grim.” The person who saw Lord Grim reported.

“F*ck!” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader sucked in a cold breath. Today’s failure was all because of that guy. Conquering Cloud understood very well that, if not for him, they wouldn’t have lost so badly against Heavenly Justice. Heavenly Justice’s coordination in that battle was imprinted deeply in his mind. It wasn’t the sort of coordination an in-game guild should have. There was certainly an expert leading them, and he had seen Lord Grim amongst them.

How frustrating! So f*cking annoying! If he’s coming, doesn’t that mean that Heavenly Justice is coming too?

Conquering Cloud’s guild leader had his players expand their search area when he saw Lord Grim strut over. The guild leader once again sucked in a cold breath towards Lord Grim’s equipment this time. His top-heavy bottom-light style was extremely weird. What was this God doing?

Then, he saw Lord Grim circle around them and actually asked a Conquering Cloud player: “Why haven’t you started attacking the boss?”

Conquering Cloud’s guild leader was so furious, his nose was crooked. Who asked for information in this way? It was way too disdainful.

That player clearly wasn’t prepared for the question. He didn’t know how to reply and looked at his guild leader.

Lord Grim also turned around to look and saw the guild leader tag above the guild leader. He immediately walked over.

“Are you the guild leader? Why haven’t you started attacking the boss?” Ye Xiu actually straight up asked the guild leader this question.

Chapter 672: The Calmness of a Weak Team

Conquering Cloud’s guild leader obviously knew who exactly he was facing. Usually, he would be excited about meeting a pro player in game, no matter who it was.

But how could Conquering Cloud’s guild leader feel excitement in his current situation?

Speaking of which, it was truly quite pitiful for the fans of weak teams. Strong teams had Gods, a beautiful win rate, and an incredible match record. Any of these were enough to make fans discuss their favorite teams enthusiastically. However, weak teams didn’t have any of these. The reasons people would support weak teams clearly wasn’t enamored by their glorious achievements. Due to this reason, the fans of weak teams were generally more loyal because there wasn’t much they could support. They started off in a low position. Even a tiny improvement was enough to make them satisfied.

These fans were a group of down-to-earth players, but that didn’t mean they didn’t like achievements either.

They also hoped their team would have amazing players, exceptional characters, and an intimidating win record.

Conquering Clouds once possessed such a quality.

Sun Xiang!

Conquering Clouds had unexpectedly uncovered such a talent. As soon as he came onto the stage, he attracted countless eyes. Sun Xiang had obtained the greatest glory one could achieve as an individual. In his very first year in the Alliance, he was already being mentioned alongside the other Gods. That year, Conquering Cloud’s win record was unprecedented, with regards to them, of course.

But their happiness was short-lived.

Many people expected great things from Sun Xiang and looked at him favorably, but none of it seemed to have anything to do with Conquering Clouds. The attention given to such a talent couldn’t be considered as attention to their team.

The fans of Conquering Clouds didn’t want to admit it, but they could only do so.

As Sun Xiang performed more and more spectacularly, they were filled with joy, but also filled with worry and uneasiness. In his second season, when Sun Xiang continued to play with Conquering Clouds, the fans were as excited as if they had just won the championships.

Yes, for a weak team, finding happiness in the team was very easy.

Unfortunately, good things didn’t last forever. During this season’s winter, he transferred to another team. Team Excellent Era’s captain, Ye Qiu, the greatest player in Glory’s competitive history, retired. Following afterwards, Sun Xiang announced his transfer to Team Excellent Era to succeed Ye Qiu’s position.

Conquering Cloud’s fans obviously felt bitter, but they still held their reasoning.

As fans of Conquering Clouds, they had been prepared for such a move long ago. They sent their blessings to Sun Xiang and even felt proud that someone from their team had been able to succeed a God like Ye Qiu.

They didn’t hold any grievances towards anyone and simply continued to quietly support their team.

Fighting for wild bosses?

Truthfully speaking, Conquering Cloud didn’t have an elite team responsible for wild bosses. This sort of competition was similar to their situation with a talent like Sun Xiang. From the very start, none of it seemed to be related to a weak team like Conquering Clouds.

But they would never give up on such an opportunity.

The playoffs were one such opportunity.

The fans of the strong teams were busy waving flags and shouting battle cries, pouring out their emotions either due to being eliminated or for winning. This was a long-awaited event for fans of teams like Conquering Clouds. They didn’t have the status to take part in it.

They would only watch quietly from the sidelines when such opportunities suddenly appeared in front of them.

The powerful guilds practically monopolized the wild bosses, leading their fans and contesting them. They hadn’t relaxed in their wild boss hunting all year, up until now.

It was hard to say how much of an improvement killing a few wild bosses could provide to a team, but if there was an opportunity, then why waste it?

The small Club guilds, who almost never participated in wild boss fights, had gathered their players together and spread across the world of Glory, searching for wild bosses.

Conquering Clouds was naturally one of these guilds, but they had unfortunately encountered Heavenly Justice at Darkness Palace.

They knew that Heavenly Justice was about to have a team join the Alliance. Their entrance came with quite some noise. The talk about Heavenly Justice even overshadowed their own. How could they accept that so easily?

If an elite group from a strong team came, they would resign themselves to their inevitable loss, but they felt like they could still contest Heavenly Justice.

However, they suffered a crushing defeat!

Even an elite group from a powerful Club guild wouldn’t have beat them so badly.

The reason was very obvious. It was because of the person heading over towards him. It was because of this guy’s help that Conquering Clouds had suffered such huge losses in that fight. Conquering Cloud’s guild leader shotcalling and tactics couldn’t compete with a God’s.

And now this person was walking around so casually in front of him, asking such an arrogant question.

Were they born to be looked down upon?

Even though they were weak and the person looking down on them was Glory’s greatest of all time, Conquering Cloud’s guild leader still felt like it was a blow to his pride.

But perhaps he was already used to being looked down upon, despite being angry, he didn’t make any movements. Their feeble strength was a fact and, in any competitive platform, the skilled were respected.

“You’re still not fighting yet? Where are your people?” In the end, Conquering Cloud’s guild leader replied calmly to Ye Xiu’s question.

“Oh, I’m here to investigate. My people are still far away.” Ye Xiu said.

So straightforward…...

Conquering Cloud’s guild leader didn’t know what to say. Under normal circumstances, let alone admitting that you were investigating, just from your guild tag alone, killing you off immediately didn’t need any explanation, but facing this person, would they even be able to kill him if they tried?

Conquering Cloud’s guild leader couldn’t help but ask himself this question. Even though he had two hundred players on his side and his opponent was only one, he had heard that when this God entered the Heavenly Domain, the top guilds had allied together and chased after him. And the results? In the end, it was settled by leaving the matter unsettled. The other side was able to steadily climb his way up to level 70.

As for why they left the matter unsettled, he didn’t need to hear it from others to know. It was naturally because they had no other choice!

If all of the top guilds couldn’t do it, Conquering Cloud’s guild leader doubted that he had any sort of chance of succeeding.

The fans of small teams possessed steadfast hearts! As the leader of these fans, Conquering Cloud’s guild leader appeared calm. They were originally at the bottom. How could they go any lower? Just like this wild boss. It wouldn’t have originally gone to them. If they got it, they would profit. If they didn’t, they didn’t lose out. There was no pressure on them, so when facing tough opponents like Changing Spring, Jiang You, or Arisaema, Conquering Cloud’s guild leader would initially be depressed and become calm.

“Tell your people to come!” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader said.

“Oh? You’re not going to move it away?” Ye Xiu was surprised.

“It’s not like it matters. We wouldn’t be able to shrug you off even if we tried, no?” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader said.

“That’s true.” Ye Xiu confirmed, “But do you think that if my people come, you’ll have the ability to face them?”

Conquering Cloud’s guild leader fell silent. Their tragic defeat at Darkness Palace was still fresh in their minds! Everyone was silent. No one said anything. They quietly listened to the conversation between their guild leader and their enemy.

“So you’re saying we should quietly watch you guys?” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader said.

“Sure. I would never reject that offer.” Ye Xiu said.

Conquering Cloud’s guild leader was depressed, but a small character was a small character. He knew when to give up. In the end, he sighed: “It looks like that’s our only choice.”

“But I have a proposal.” Ye Xiu suddenly spoke.

“What is it?” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader was ready to order his people to escape at any moment.

“Alliance!” Ye Xiu said.

“What?” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader felt like he had heard incorrectly.

“Our current situation is only temporary. It’d be a miracle if we could keep this up for two weeks. Once this period ends, those guilds will certainly come back to compete for wild bosses. When that time comes, our strength will go back to being insufficient, no?” Ye Xiu said.

“Even with you?” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader said.

“Why are you worried about me? You should be concerned with yourself.” Ye Xiu said.

“.......”

“Then what are you trying to say?” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader asked.

“We should cooperate together and break the wild boss monopoly held by those top guilds.” Ye Xiu said.

Conquering Cloud’s guild leader stared blankly.

“I feel like you’ve never thought of doing this before.” Ye Xiu said.

“I’ve thought of it before, but even if we allied together, I’m not sure if we’d be able to beat the top guilds.” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader said.

“But if you don’t try, then you won’t even have a chance at all.” Ye Xiu said.

“In any case, it’s not like you’re doing anything else. Why not give it a try? Isn’t it boring running dungeons everyday? Look at how the Heavenly Domain is set up. It clearly encourages PK. As a Club guild, shouldn’t you be a model for others?” Ye Xiu said.

“How are those even connected?” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader was depressed.

At this moment, Ye Xiu received a message from Loulan Slash. Seeing that Lord Grim had gone over, but hadn’t reported back in a long time, Loulan Slash felt uneasy.

“Relax. Discussion.” Ye Xiu replied.

“Discussion?” Loulan Slash asked. Did I do something wrong? Why did he use that word?

“Discussing an alliance.” Ye Xiu said.

“Alliance?” Loulan Slash was still confused.

“Alliance to kill wild bosses.” Ye Xiu said.

“Split between three?” Loulan Slash was somewhat astonished. Normally, with a God helping them, they had an overwhelming advantage. Why did they need extend an olive branch to Conquering Clouds?

“Not necessarily. It could be between four, five, six.” Ye Xiu said.

“What are you trying to get at?” Loulan Slash asked.

“We should establish an alliance that can compete with the top guilds for the long term, not just using this opportunity to do a small bit of stealing.” Ye Xiu said.

Loulan Slash immediately understood. The top guilds were currently busy. Once this hype period was over, the fight for the bosses wouldn’t remain the same as they did now.

“You were on planning on doing this from the start?” Loulan Slash asked.

“No. I just thought of it.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 673: It’s All a Misunderstanding

I just thought of it…….

Loulan Slash muttered to himself. He didn’t need Ye Xiu to explain it to him to know that this would be a long-term solution, but even so, he wasn’t very happy with Ye Xiu making such a decision on his behalf. This was completely different from when he was acting like a dog following him around everywhere. That could be considered just a joke, but Ye Xiu directly deciding something for him was a completely different matter.

Loulan Slash had to express his complaints: “Why didn’t you tell me about this before making such a decision?”

Yes, he just wanted to be informed of it beforehand. Loulan Slash liked this plan. He wasn’t against it, but he needed to be the one to make the decision. Even Ocean Ahead, Homeward Bound, Thousand Falling Leaves, or Night Tide would be fine too. Ye Xiu shouldn’t be allowed to help Heavenly Justice make such an important decision. This time, Loulan Slash felt that Ye Xiu had gone too far.

‘Oh, aren’t I doing that right now? What do you think of it?” Ye Xiu replied.

“......” Loulan Slash choked. This this……. this was how the matter would be resolved?

Loulan Slash wasn’t satisfied! He felt like Ye Xiu should be aware of his stance.

“What if I don’t want to?” Loulan Slash replied. He was ready to let Ye Xiu know. Didn’t you already decide? Did you really think that I would definitely accept your plan? You were right in the fact that I have no objections, but what if I don’t agree to it? What are you going to do?

“Oh? You’re not going to participate?” Ye Xiu replied and even typed out an astonished emoji.

You must be surprised! Haha! Now you know that you shouldn’t take everything for granted! Know that you can’t make decisions on behalf of Heavenly Justice! Loulan Slash was still enjoying himself, when Ye Xiu suddenly messaged: “If you’re not going to participate, how are you going to get any bosses in the future?”

“Ha ha, maybe I have a different way!” Loulan Slash replied.

“Okay okay!” Ye Xiu replied, “So you had backup plans. I hadn’t thought of that. Looks like we’ll be adversaries in the future. Good luck!!”

Wait wait wait wait!!

Loulan Slash was dumbfounded. Something wasn’t right! Before he could even react, the guild system notified him that Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and Steamed Bun Invasion had all left the guild. Afterwards, Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Chen Guo said their farewells and prepared to leave.

“Hey hey hey! Where are you guys going?” Loulan Slash called out to them, when he suddenly understood.

“It’s a misunderstanding! A misunderstanding!” Loulan Slash cried.

The three characters stopped and looked at him. Their characters’ expressions were cold and indifferent. In reality, they were puzzled: What? What had happened? What misunderstanding?

Loulan Slash finally realized what had happened. Ye Xiu hadn’t made any decisions on his behalf. He was making his own decision. Loulan Slash had forgotten why Ye Xiu had even been in his guild to begin with: it was just to for them to temporarily take advantage of their guild’s extra stat points. Ye Xiu wasn’t there to serve his guild. Their statuses were equal. Ye Xiu was working alone. He just hadn’t created his guild yet, so he was staying with Heavenly Justice until he did so.

So it really had been a misunderstanding, but this misunderstanding wasn’t easy to explain. Loulan Slash had brought this upon himself. When he saw them leave his guild, Loulan Slash finally realized: in that alliance plan, his Heavenly Justice had been crossed out as someone who wouldn’t be joining.

F*ck! How could I not take part in this?

If Ye Xiu really did what he said he would do, the small Club guilds would ally together. The top Club guilds would still be as powerful as ever. How could his Heavenly Justice compete with them both alone?

Loulan Slash didn’t want to be the unique one. Not at all. As he shouted at them to stop, he hastily messaged Ye Xiu to explain in a shameless manner: “You’re too decisive! I never said I wasn’t going to participate. I was just thinking over it!!!!”

“Think? What’s there to think about?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Yeah, there’s no need to think about it, but I accidentally spilled some water on my keyboard, so I was in a bit of a fluster. I thought too much for a second there. I just decided that I had to participate, right? Isn’t that obvious?” Loulan Slash regretted how the other side could see his impatience.

“Oh, then come over here! We haven’t noticed any other guilds coming, so us three will kill it together!” Ye Xiu replied.

Three!

Loulan Slash saw this number. As expected! Ye Xiu hadn’t considered himself a part of Heavenly Justice. They were separate entities. Loulan Slash had assumed it on his own and regarded Ye Xiu as laboring for him.

Loulan Slash hastily led his team over to the boss, while inviting Soft MIst and Steamed Bun Invasion back to the guild. However, the invites were denied. When he looked again, he remembered that those who left a guild couldn’t join another one for five days. Loulan Slash had forgotten about it in his anxiousness.

Sigh sigh sigh!

Loulan Slash sighed. He originally had a close relationship with Ye Xiu, but with just one blunder, he widened had it. They originally had Heavenly Justice next to their names, giving Conquering Clouds and any other guilds a warning. And now? Ye Xiu wouldn’t directly join Conquering Cloud right?

Loulan Slash was somewhat fidgety. He forgot about the notification he got: those who left the guild wouldn’t be able to join another guild for five days.

When Heavenly Justice arrived, Ye Xiu and Conquering Cloud’s guild leader had already finished their discussion. With their alliance in place, the bit of enmity between them went away. The two were happily chatting together. Quite a few Conquering Cloud players had come over too. Who was this? God Ye Qiu! To be able to meet him in-game was definitely something to be excited about!

When Loulan Slash came over and saw Conquering Cloud’s guild leader chatting away with Ye Xiu, he felt sad and depressed!

It’s all my own fault! Why did I have to say all that when I didn’t even understand the situation?

“God……” Loulan Slash went over and gave an awkward greeting.

“You’re here? Let’s start then. We’ll split the rewards evenly three ways. Will that be an issue?” Ye Xiu said.

It seems like Ye Xiu would be considering himself as an equal entity, but his abilities didn’t need to be discussed. How could Heavenly Justice or Conquering Clouds not know of his capabilities in leading a group? So even though the other side had fewer people, none of them objected to him taking an equal share. Even though he had fewer people, all of them were experts.

“You guys have probably never fought against this boss before, right?” Ye XIu asked the two guild leaders.

“Yeah.” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader and Loulan Slash confirmed it.

“Then I’ll be responsible for leading this operation!” Ye Xiu said.

Neither of them objected, but Loulan Slash also knew that Ye Xiu had never fought against this boss before either, but starting something new was never easy!

The two guilds working together would have around four to five hundred players in this small area. It was unusually noisy. The two sides had fought against each other just a short while ago at Darkness Palace. All of a sudden, they would now be cooperating with each other? This sudden change in relationship was a familiar one for the big Club guilds, but for these guild players, who rarely competed, it took some time for them to get used to.

Furthermore, this was for a wild boss. Four full groups weren’t necessary. They might accidentally injure one another too, which would prove to be troublesome. As a result, the two guilds chose their strongest members and had them form a group. Everyone else dispersed and were in charge of being on the lookout. Without any other guilds around, didn’t that mean they would be doing nothing?

“Then shall we start?” Ye Xiu looked around. Loulan Slash and Conquering Cloud’s guild leader would obviously be a part of the main group.

“Let’s start!”

“Team one……”

“Team two…..”

Ye Xiu started giving instructions. Sometimes, he would speak. Other times, he would type. In any case, the group chat would be very clean during these times, so typing out the instructions wouldn’t be difficult to see.

The front lines would consist of Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, Soft Mist, and Loulan Slash’s team. Their skill level surpassed top normal players. As for the other members of the group, they would be dealing damage whenever they were given the opportunity to do so. From time to time, they would need to make adjustments according to the instructions given.

Chen Guo’s Chasing Haze was amongst these players. When she looked around left and right, there were numerous Heavenly Justice and Conquering Cloud players surrounding her. The only Happy player was herself! How lonely…….

Chen Guo was depressed! They needed to hurry and establish their guild! They should at least have some number between ten and twenty people here!

With Ye Xiu leading and several experts helping, Forest Guardian Vich wasn’t an easy task, but it still went smoothly. From an overall perspective, even though they weren’t a big Club guild, they didn’t lack elite teams. Along with a God like Ye Xiu, the elite teams from the guilds were more than enough.

The wild boss was steadily eaten up. Ye Xiu’s precise decision-making helped a lot. Loulan Slash and the others let out a sigh of relief. With his leading, it really had been quite easy to beat this wild boss. As long as no outsider messed things up, the boss wouldn’t give them any trouble.

But their fear came. Conquering Cloud’s guild leader received a message that Guild Radiant was coming.

Guild Radiant belonged to Club Radiant. Team Radiant placed 17th in the regular season. They were clearly a bottom-tier team, but they wanted to take advantage of this situation to snag a few wild bosses as well.

“Are they close?” Ye Xiu asked, when he saw the message from Conquering Cloud’s guild leader.

“They should arrive before we finish killing the boss.” Conquering Cloud’s guild leader said.

“Then we should let them come! With our current situation, it’ll be quite convenient to talk about things once they arrive.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 674: This Situation Isn’t Right!

Radiant wasn’t actually certain that a boss had spawned. They simply had a similar line of thinking and stationed their players all throughout the world to be on the lookout. In the end, players from Radiant discovered unusual movements from Conquering Clouds at the World Tree and immediately reported back.

When Radiant heard the news, they were quite excited! If the other side had already grouped up, it meant they were about to start attacking the boss. If they hurried over and snuck up on them, maybe they would be able to steal the boss?

Radiant formed two groups of players and rushed towards the World Tree. The Radiant players, who had discovered the unusual movements, saw Conquering Clouds shoo them away, confirming their suspicions: a wild boss had definitely spawned here.

“Force your way past them!”

Hearing that their players were being cleared from the field, Radiant’s guild leader ordered the two groups of players under him to prepare to sweep Conquering Cloud in one go.

But when they arrived at the location, they weren’t met with any resistance. Conquering Clouds seemed to be intentionally avoiding them, allowing Radiant to reach the boss’s location without any pressure.

“What’s going on?” Radiant’s guild leader was puzzled. The opposing side wasn’t stopping him from reaching the boss. Were they still fighting for the boss? This didn’t make any sense?

“Wait.” Radiant’s guild leader felt like there must have been a trap set somewhere. He felt a bit afraid to continue venturing deeper and hastily called his troops to halt.

“Everyone, wait here for now. I’ll go take a look ahead with a few others.” Radiant’s guild leader positioned himself as a scout and picked out a few players to go with him. They formed a small team and ventured deeper to investigate.

Not long afterwards, they quickly saw a huge commotion up ahead. A whole bunch of players seemed to be scattered around, but they were actually organized, aiming for the same target as if they were fighting the boss.

Why was it “as if”? Because Radiant’s scouts saw that some of these players had Conquering Cloud guild tags, while others had Heavenly Justice guild tags.

What sort of situation is this? Radiant’s scouts were puzzled. In an ideal world, two guilds would be fighting together alongside one another! However, something like that had never happened before! Wild bosses were such valuable resources. It was difficult for guilds like them to even have an opportunity to kill one, yet they were actually cooperating with one another and giving half of their troops to the other side? How could things be so perfect?

It’s a trap! There was definitely a trap hidden somewhere!

Radiant’s guild leader thought, but he didn’t know if this trap was for Radiant, or if those two guilds were plotting something against each other. If it was the latter, then it would be easy pickings for Radiant! On the other hand, if it was a trap for Radiant, what was the trap? Have them believe it would be easy pickings? Radiant’s guild leader was completely dumbfounded. There were no hints of them setting up any sort of net.

“Guild leader, what do we do?” Someone next to him asked.

“Something feels fishy!” Radiant’s guild leader hesitated. He looked around left and right, but no one seemed to notice them. Since there were only a few of them, by sticking close together, they easily avoided the sight of any nearby players.

“Can you see the boss?” Radiant’s guild leader stuck out his head, hoping to see something abnormal amongst the crowd of players.

“They should be attacking the boss, right? Why else would they be causing such a commotion?” One person said.

“But it’s too peaceful! That’s not logical at all!” Radiant’s guild leader didn’t understand at all. No matter how much he couldn’t understand, they still had a goal in mind. The boss’s health wasn’t going to wait for them. They also didn’t know when this crowd of players started attacking the boss. What if the boss was killed by the time they got there?

Radiant’s guild leader sent a message back, telling everyone to hurry over while they continued to observe the two guilds.

After receiving the message, Radiant’s players immediately set out. The two guilds obviously noticed the movements of such a large group of players. Conquering Cloud’s guild leader and Loulan Slash continuously received updates.

It was very obvious what the other side wanted. Perhaps it would be best to defend against them, so the two guilds organized their leftover troops to gather together. When Radiant arrived, the players from the two guilds that had been spread out earlier converged. Radiant’s guild leader saw this scene. Holy sh*t, they have so many people! It seemed like these two guilds really were partners? Why were they so against Radiant? Were these two guilds getting married?

The two sides faced each other, but because their guild leaders hadn’t given them any orders, neither side moved. They were all elite teams and were well disciplined. If their guild leader didn’t tell them to do anything, they wouldn’t provoke the other side, so the situation a stalemate.

“Ahem…..” Radiant’s guild leader felt like he should say something. He went to the front of his troops: “What are you guys doing?”

“We’re killing the boss! What else would we be doing?” Someone answered back as if it were obvious. Radiant’s guild leader had a title next to his name, indicating that he was the guild leader. The other side wasn’t a part of Radiant though, so they didn’t care.

“Killing the boss……” Radiant’s guild leader really wanted to know why they weren’t fighting each other, but how could he ask that? In the end, he said: “Really? How’s it going?”

“We’re almost done!” The other side replied.

“What are you trying to do? Do you plan on stopping us?” Conquering Cloud’s players shouted.

Radiant’s guild leader looked at them with disdain. In his heart, he was thinking about how stupid these people were. If we’re not here to stop you, do you think we’re here to watch? These people must have never killed a wild boss before!

Radiant’s guild leader thought because their guild had gotten a few wild bosses before. Even though they were powerless against the large guilds, Radiant had never given up on pursuing wild bosses. The Heavenly Domain was so vast. Even if the big guilds spread their net wide, there would always be a few fish that slipped through. Radiant relied on this method to snatch a few wild bosses. However, because of their goal, the number of times that they had been wiped by the big guilds was more than the number of wild boss kills they had managed to secure under their belts.

Sometimes, they would arrive first and start attacking the boss, but the big guilds ended up catching them and wiped them out along with the boss.

Even so, Radiant’s guild leader felt like they were still on the competitive side. They were one grade higher than those guilds who didn’t even dare to compete for wild bosses. In his eyes, Conquering Clouds was naturally a lower grade than them. As for Heavenly Justice, they didn’t have anything besides money!

Although he believed that Radiant had more experience than those two guilds, seeing how those two guilds were allied with each other, Radiant’s guild leader didn’t dare to fight them one versus two! He blamed the unclear reports from the players that had informed him. If he knew there were two guilds, he would have brought more people!

Radiant’s guild leader was wondering what he should do right now! Suddenly, he heard cheers of celebration and he knew that it wasn’t good. Sure enough, the wild boss had been killed and the two guilds were cheering as a result.

F*ck. These two guilds actually committed adultery?

Radiant’s guild leader saw that the boss had fallen, yet the two other guilds never attacked each other once. In the end, they even cheered together. It really made him speechless.

These people were truly amateurs! Instead of fighting over the wild boss, they actually allied together! Radiant’s guild leader thought resentfully. He was already planning on leaving, when he saw the players from the two guilds disperse. Conquering Cloud’s guild leader Yue Ziqin and Heavenly Justice’s guild leader Loulan Slash were walking over.

Between these two was a weird looking top-heavy guy, who instantly made Radiant’s guild leader….. No, the entire guild of Radiant pay attention. When this guy got closer and they could finally see his ID, Radiant’s guild leader felt his head go dizzy.

F*ck, isn’t he that guy?!

Radiant’s guild leader stood dumbly there, forgetting to tell his guild to leave. These three walked up to him. Conquering Cloud’s guild leader, Yue Ziqing, was familiar with him, so he introduced him to the other two: “This is Radiant’s guild leader White Stream. I don’t know if you two know of him?”

“It’s an honor to meet you.” Loulan Slash said. This wasn’t him being polite. Even though Radiant was a bottom-tier team in the Alliance, a pro team was still a pro team. Their guild was still quite powerful. Loulan Slash had conjured a storm and his popularity appeared to be soaring. However, his foundation still couldn’t compare to these Club guilds. They had real and loyal fans! Their team was doing so poorly, yet they still didn’t leave their team. If they weren’t loyal fans, what were they?

“Mm mm……” Ye Xiu nodded twice. He was being sincere! Saying it was an honor to meet him would be a lie. Even though Radiant’s guild leader could be considered a top figure in the game, his status wouldn’t even reach Ye Xiu’s ears. Ye Xiu was currently wondering who was in Team Radiant. Was there anyone noteworthy?

“This is Heavenly Justice’s guild leader Loulan Slash. This is, he he, I don’t need to introduce him, do I?” Yue Ziqin introduced them to White Stream.

“Mm……. ha, that’s…… right…..” White Stream didn’t know what to say. He was staring at Lord Grim. He wasn’t prepared at all to meet this God. His brain was currently short-circuiting.

“Right what? What do you want to say?” Yue Ziqing said. His relationship with White Stream wasn’t bad. Of course, his personal relationship wouldn’t get in the way of guild matters like competing for bosses!

“Ha, it’s like this.” Ye Xiu said, “You saw us killing the boss together, right?”

“Yeah…..” White Stream said.

“It went smoothly, no?” Ye Xiu said.

“Uh……” White Stream thought: It went smoothly because I hesitated too much. Had I acted, it wouldn’t have gone so smoothly…...

“We’re cooperating together to kill bosses. How about it? Would you like to join us? If you do, once this period is over, we might not necessarily lose out to Tyranny, Tiny Herb, or Blue Rain!” Ye Xiu said.

How aggressive! White Stream thought. God Ye Qiu had directly called out Tyranny, Tiny Herb, and Blue Rain. These were team names! If it were me, I’d be saying Tyrannical Ambition, Herb Garden, and Blue Brook Guild? Tsk tsk tsk, there’s such a huge difference between us.

White Stream’s mind wasn’t there. His focus was all over the place.

Chapter 675: Let's Cooperate!

Speaking of which, Ye Xiu was more used to calling these guilds by their team’s name. For White Stream to notice such details, he could be considered quite meticulous. However, he was noticing things, he shouldn’t be noticing, and noticing things, he shouldn’t be noticing. It was only after he thought about these things for awhile did he suddenly realize the other side’s intentions.

“Cooperate…..” White Stream quickly calculated. He knew that this method would work against the big guilds, but there was one issue. Would such an alliance be stable enough for something as important as a wild boss?

“This was the equipment and the materials that dropped from the boss just now. If you joined us, we’ll distribute these evenly between the four of us, instead of three.” Loulan Slash said, while writing out a list of items and sent it to the other party. The list sent to him was naturally the rewards dropped by the wild boss. Right when the list was sent to him, Loulan Slash dumped out all of the drops onto the floor.

D*mn!

White Stream had the urge to rush forward at this moment. Why did everyone want wild bosses? Because of its drops. Now someone just threw them onto the ground. He really wanted to come forward and take them, but he wasn’t brazen enough to do so. These items were dropped by the player, not the boss, so the system wouldn’t protect them.

In the end, he didn’t take any action and could only swallow down his saliva. If they dared to throw these items at his feet, it meant that they felt safe to do so. Let alone God Ye Qiu standing there, in that instant, White Stream felt countless cold gazes shoot towards him. Of course, this was only figurative because he himself was outside of the game. However, this feeling told him: don’t make any rash movements; we’re prepared!

Afterwards, White Stream saw those three characters crouch around the pile of items, which even the powerful guilds would envy, and start distributing the items among themselves. The three chatted with each other with smiles and took the items they needed.

Yes, White Stream wasn’t seeing things. They were distributing the items among themselves. Wild bosses were so rare and difficult to kill. How could there be just a few items? Forest Guardian Vich had dropped a total of 19 items, 2 of which were Orange equipment and the rest materials.

In the eyes of the players, Orange equipment dropped from a wild boss was considered the best equipment that they could obtain. In Glory, only Silver equipment created by pro teams could surpass Orange equipment. However, not even pros necessarily had all Silver equipment. Those who didn’t have Silver equipment would have to rely on Orange equipment dropped by wild bosses. There were no Purple equipment in the pro scene. In the pro scene, Purple equipment was poor enough to make players angry, even if the majority of players in the game didn’t even have Purple equipment.

Even though Orange equipment was widely used in the pro scene, Silver equipment were still better. Orange equipment was simply temporary placeholders. The pro scene had only recently started developing. After another eight of ten years, there might not be any Orange equipment at all.

All that being said, the value of an Orange equipment dropped from a wild boss wasn’t any lower than a wild boss material because Orange equipment could be used as research materials for equipment development. With the equipment editor, they could figure out how this equipment had those stats. After obtaining this information, was it possible to elevate the stats to another stage? If the stats of this level of Orange equipment were to be upgraded, wouldn’t a Silver equipment be born? Even though this sort of Silver equipment couldn’t be compared to a custom-made Silver equipment, for Clubs without a lot of resources, this was a common method used to improve their strength.

This kind of research wasn't easy as there were times when the equipment couldn't be restored during the research. Due to this, there was a need to have multiple of the same equipment to compensate for these mistakes.

Of the two pieces of equipment that had dropped just now, Yue Ziqin took one of them away, probably for research. Ye Xiu took the other, after seeing that Loulan Slash wasn’t interested in it. For Ye Xiu and his team, this piece of equipment could help them improve their strength. Next, the materials were distributed after a brief discussion. White Stream watched them from the sidelines. He felt that none of them had lost out. Nineteen items. Even after being distributed amongst three people, each would still get receive quite a number of items. White Stream agreed with the way they distributed the drops.

Afterwards, the three characters stood up again and gazed at him.

White Stream knew the three of them intentionally distributed the items in front of him, showing him that they would distribute the items fair and square.

“If we divide these items between four…..” Ye Xiu spoke, marking the start of a new conversation.

“If we divide them by four, the items would be easier to distribute.” Yue Ziqin said.

“I agree. How about you take out that Violet Fragment and Oak Vine, God Ye Qiu takes out the World Tree Fragment, and I take out a Red Berry and a Sober Stone. These five should be enough for White Stream.” Loulan Slash suggested.

“Wait a minute, why should I give away a Violet Fragment? I can also give a Sober Stone.” Yue Ziqin said.

“What? Are you saying that your Red Berry is the same value as my Oak Vine?” Loulan Slash asked.

“Does it matter whether the item given is of same value of not? It's fin, as long all four of us get similar values. Yue Ziqin replied.

“The items you’re giving up aren’t fair. Also, your remaining items on your side are worth more than what we have.” Loulan Slash said.

“Now we’re dividing by four, so a bit of a difference is fine.”

“Giving your Violet Fragment and Oak Vine to White Stream is the correct way!” Loulan Slash said.

“If I’m giving a Violet Fragment to White Stream, then you have to give a Water Fire Crystal.” Yue Ziqin said.

“Water Fire Crystal? You b*stard, are you doing this on purpose? Do you think I don't know the value of Water Fire Crystal?” Loulan Slash angrily refuted back.

“Alright, alright. Both of you, stop arguing. You guys already arguing like this for such a small matter. Why don't you guys argue again after the next boss?” Ye Xiu finally stepped in to resolve the situation.

Meanwhile, White Stream almost drooled out from listening at them.

This guy was shouting to give him this while the other was demanding to give him that. It caused him to almost take it as real. He even almost went to trade with them.

Violet Fragment, Oak Vine, World Tree Fragment, Red Berry, and Water Fire Crystal… White Stream craved for all of them! He strongly wished that these guys would give all of it to him. But then, when Ye Xiu stepped in, he realized that it was only a conjecture and not for real. D*mn, they weren’t actually giving all of those to him. He almost tricked himself.

Thinking about it again, it felt like they purposely fighting in front of him. It was the same as when they were laying out all of the items on the ground. Were they trying to entice him to join them? Even though he knew what they were trying to do, he was really looking forward to it!

How about… he try following these guys?

White Stream still wasn’t confident. Would these people distribute the dropped items fair and square and not manipulate them to their own advantage? If these people teamed up with each other, then his guild would easily kicked aside by them anytime.

Just as White Stream was still hesitating about it, Yue Ziqin suddenly received a message: “Oh! Another boss spawned.”

“Really? Where? Our side still hasn’t received any news.” Loulan Slash shouted out.

Yue Ziqin didn’t immediately reply, instead he asked White Stream, “Do you want to come with us?”

Another wild boss? White Stream’s side also hadn’t received any news. The Heavenly Domain was too large and wild bosses randomly spawned. If it was just their guild, it wouldn't be strange to miss a boss. Even with all the guilds working together, bosses sometimes wouldn’t be discovered by any of them.

If they didn’t have any information on a boss, it was possible that they wouldn't know if there was a wild boss fight even happening. Rather than a nonexistent chance, why not try working with them? He could also observe their attitudes towards him too.

“Okay! I’ll go too!” After thinking about it for a while, White Stream agreed to follow them.

Yue Ziqin announced that the newly spawned boss was the Swordsman Protector Kayou of Sighing Ravine.

“Another level 70 boss!” Loulan Slash was excited. Today, they had killed three level 70 wild bosses. Even though the number of items distributed reduced each time, it was still better compared to before, where they couldn’t even find one!

“Is there a need to be surprised about this?” White Stream looked down on them, when he saw that other guild leader was so excited just from hearing the name of the wild boss. He was showing off his superiority to the other guilds for having killed a wild boss before. Though he acted this way, he was actually quite excited too!

“Shall we go?” Loulan Slash didn't refute back. Speaking of which, he immediately felt embarrassed after that. The other guild leaders didn’t act like him when they heard the name of the wild boss and yet he acts like such a peasant, how unsightly! He was going to enter the League as a pro player next season, yet he was still acting like this. So embarrassing! He should learn more from God Ye Qiu’s calm demeanor.

“Let's go!” They called out to their troops and set out. Three guild leaders each leading two groups of players. It was very noisy. On the other hand, Ye Xiu’s team was more solemn. With only four people in their team, they wouldn’t even be able to be spotted if they were thrown in amongst the crowd of players. In addition, their equipment might be remarkable in normal teams but compared to these elite groups, theirs was too mundane. Let alone Orange equipment, they didn’t even have any equipment from a hundred player raid dungeons. How could they compare with the elites of these Club guilds?

Conquering Clouds and Radiant didn’t do well in the competition for wild bosses, but that was because they were up against strong opponents. However, for 100 player raid dungeons, their teams could still challenge those.

Chapter 676: Dagger Team

Ye Xiu’s group, as well as the players from the three allied guilds, returned to the nearest city and teleported as near as they could to the Sighing Ravine.

They were fairly spread out as they moved. After all, the situation still wasn’t very stable. If their movements caught the attention of the club guilds, they might get dragged into the war, so the three guilds tacitly kept a low profile while traveling.

Conquering Clouds wasn’t the only guild to notice Sword Master Kayou. Compared to Ye Xiu and the others, who had to travel through several locations to reach the boss, this guild grouped together quickly.

After clearing the surrounding area, they prepared to move the boss away. Yue Ziqin immediately received reports that his players were being shooed away. This other guild was Parade.

Team Parade had placed 16th this regular season. Along with Team Radiant and Team Conquering Clouds, who placed 15th and 17th in the regular season, these three teams were just as bad as each other. With similar placings, they were in a similar situation in the game. Usually, Parade lived the life of poaching a few wild bosses. Seeing how the big guilds were all fighting one another, why wouldn’t they take advantage of this opportunity and reap some rewards? They were also busy wandering around the world, looking for bosses.

No one knew exactly when this Sword Master Kayou had spawned. In any case, Parade had been the first to arrive. Sighing Ravine had complicated terrain, making it easy to hide a boss. After clearing away any surrounding players, Parade began moving the boss away to somewhere without any enemy eyes.

This kind of remote leveling area hadn’t become a battlefield for the ongoing world war. For this sort of chaotic killing without any real purpose, the fires of war would spread and then shrink because, when a player died, that player would have to revive elsewhere, so the battles would slowly concentrate near the cities and then towards the revival points.

Sighing Ravine was already a remote area away from the populated places. This area wasn’t crowded, but it wasn’t completely empty either, although it was more on the unfrequented side. Even more so at the time of night like now. Parade pulled the boss along and soon found a suitable location. Afterwards, they had a few scouts spread out and pay attention to any suspicious players nearing their location.

Truthfully, there was no such thing as an unsuspicious player! In this type of situation, if you were a player in the general vicinity, you were considered suspicious. It didn’t matter if you were in a guild or not. You would be closely watched by Parade.

However, since they weren’t clearing the area, Parade would only pay attention to them. They wouldn’t take the initiative to give them a warning. If they did that, wouldn’t that be the same as saying 300 silver taels were hidden here? That would just be telling the world that they were killing a wild boss at this location!

The scouts who spread around the map wouldn’t have Parade’s guild tag displayed next to their names.

Ye Xiu and the others were still quite far and their intel was poor. After Conquering Cloud’s players were cleared out of the area, they couldn’t stay there and give any updates. When the main troops arrived, they could only vaguely which direction Parade took off.

“We have to hurry!” Ye Xiu looked at the time. He was worried that by the time they found the boss, the boss would already be dead.

“Spread out to save some time!” The three guild leaders didn’t hesitate. They led their teams towards the general direction. Whenever a split road appeared, they would immediately split their troops. The three guilds had 6 groups for a total of 60 teams or 600 players, which spread out and searched the area.

Their initial direction was accurate, so with this many players searching, along with some experienced judgement, a team from Heavenly Justice discovered a few of Parade’s movements.

When Heavenly Justice made their discovery, Parade noticed them too. It didn’t matter if this team didn’t have a guild tag. If you’re a player, you’re suspicious! Seeing that this team was getting closer to the boss, Parade sent some people to stop them.

Heavenly Justice’s team was killed, but although they didn’t see the boss himself, being attacked was also an indicator. The team reported back and the three guilds all headed towards this location. After Parade wiped out this team, they didn’t immediately pull the boss elsewhere. After all, this team was simply killed because they were suspicious. They didn’t actually know that this team was searching for the boss.

Killing people for no reason wasn’t good, especially for a Club guild. As a result, the players sent to wipe out these suspicious players wouldn’t be someone well known in Parade or have a guild tag on their name. When was it a good time to use open accounts? Now, of course!

If these suspicious players were from a guild, then both sides were well aware of the reason. If these suspicious players were normal players, Parade couldn’t let these players speak badly about them.

Parade continued to fight the boss, while paying close attention to whether there would be any aftereffects from killing this team. Sure enough, many more players were starting towards their location. Parade immediately knew that they hadn’t killed random passersby, but players actively searching for the boss.

Then should they continue fighting or should they hide?

Parade’s guild leader was called Martial Awareness. After thinking about it, he decided to stay and fight. They could use the terrain to their advantage and form a defensive formation around the location. As long as they could stall for long enough, they would have enough time to kill the boss.

Martial Awareness quickly gave the order. He immediately commanded the sub-guild leader to lead a portion of their troops to set up a defensive wall, while he led the team in killing the boss.

They weren’t very familiar with killing this wild boss, but players from Club guilds still had good equipment and skills. From an overall perspective, they were still strong, unlike Heavenly Justice whose only top experts were Loulan Slash’s team, while everyone else was just average. Facing a wild boss, which required many players to defeat, Heavenly Justice couldn’t compare to any of the Club guilds in this sense.

Martial Awareness’s assistant led a group of players and started making arrangements. Their scouts had returned for more support.

Not long afterwards, the sounds of jumbled footsteps gradually echoed throughout Sighing Ravine. They started getting closer and closer. When this Parade sub-guild leader heard the sound getting louder and louder, his expression started to change. It seemed like there were a lot of people coming.

Of course, there were a lot!

The three allied guilds had a total of six hundred players. They outnumbered Parade by nearly 3 to 1, and the group led by Parade’s sub-guild leader by 6 to 1. But more important was the person leading this huge six hundred player army.

Ye Xiu!

Known as the Glory Encyclopedia and a God, how could he not be well versed in tactics? As their troops advanced, the ravine was still as quiet as ever. Even the allied guild leaders knew something was going on. How could Ye Xiu not realize that there must be some sort of trap in that entrance up ahead.

But who cares if there was an ambush?

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim turned back and looked behind him. The players from the three allied guilds had nearly all gathered together. For the ravine to be so peaceful, Parade must be the only guild there. With such an overwhelming numbers advantage, any sort of ambush was worthless.

“Charge!” Ye Xiu didn’t even try and arrange any formations. He just said one word.

If they only relied on their sea of people to charge through, they would certainly be slowed by the terrain. But the ones leading the charge were daggers that would pierce through the enemy defense.

Lord Grim, Soft Mist, Steamed Bun Invasion.

Loulan Slash’s five-player team.

Yue Ziqin and White Stream couldn’t be considered as weak either. They were experts, who were responsible for leading their entire guild. A total of 18 players led the charge and made the first turn around the corner.

“ATTACK!!” Parade’s sub-guild leader wasn’t polite and gave the order as soon as he saw them.

The prepared attacks flew out, but the opposing seemed to be closing in on them faster than their skills could be released. In the blink of an eye, all sorts of skills fell, not just from Parade, but also from the allied sides.

The dagger pierced into the heart and continued through it.

Eighteen elites. The ten from Conquering Clouds and Radiant were somewhat weaker, but Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, and Loulan Slash’s team far surpassed the skill of a normal player. In an instant, they trampled through the enemy ranks.

Parade’s sub-guild leader could tell that the other side had a lot of people and was already uneasy, but how could he have known that they would immediately get rushed through in one go? He even went up himself to defend, but a brick landed on him, a spear launched him into the air, along with a bunch of other skills.

F*ck!

How did he turn into a ghost?

He could only blame his sub-guild leader tag being so eye-catching. It was always best to kill the leader first if there was an opportunity to. It was like this in war, on the streets, and in the game.

The leader was killed not long after the battle began. It didn’t need to be said that Parade’s defense fell into shambles.

They couldn’t even defend against these 18 elites, when the rest of the troops arrived. That sea of people completely devoured them.

“F*ck!”

Martial Awareness received his sub-guild leader’s message. He was still busy killing the boss. He just looked at it, but didn’t have time to reply. When suddenly, the players next to him clearly made a mistake. He immediately shouted: “What are you doing! Focus! Where are you looking?!”

“Guild leader….. Look behind us……” Someone beside him stuttered.

Martial Awareness turned around to look. F*ck! What the hell was this? Where’d everyone go? Why are there so many people? Who are these guys? Bringing so many people for a boss, have some integrity!

The sea of people had arrived in front of Martial Awareness’s group. Trying to bring the boss away now was impossible. They lost focus out of terror and Sword Master Kayou killed four of them in one slash.

At this point, the guild tags on the players bared their fangs. Martial Awareness immediately realized that it wasn’t just one guild, but three guilds! What’s going on? Were they allying together to swallow them up?

At this moment, a top-heavy weird-looking guy stood out in front of everyone. Martial Awareness glanced at him and was furious! F*ck, what’s this? You’re sending this guy out to make fun of me? But soon afterwards, he saw the ID on this weird guy’s head: Lord Grim. Martial Awareness’s heart fell to his feet.

He knew very well who this person was. At this moment, Lord Grim calmly spoke: “Guild leader, let’s put the boss aside and have a chat?”

Chapter 677: Just Kill More

Let’s put the boss aside…...

Even if Parade wanted to stop, the boss had to agree too! Bosses couldn’t speak or communicate though. Under the hungry gazes of the three allied guilds, Parade continued to defend against the boss as their sweat drenched their backs. Martial Awareness knew that they wouldn’t be able to win this time.

Their group had the terrain advantage, yet they were still instantly crushed by their opponents. Such a powerful force wasn’t something that Martial Awareness could contend against, especially when a God was the one leading the enemy’s forces. What exactly was going on?

“What do you want?” Martial Awareness spoke hoarsely. In this type of situation, he already had intentions of shrinking back, but as a guild leader, his pride couldn’t bear it. The other side was too cruel and direct, not leaving him any room to move. After crushing my forces, he wants me to sit down and chat? What the f*ck is there to talk about? We’ll have to listen to anything you say anyway.

“Let’s be allies! We’ll split the boss drops equally.” Ye Xiu said.

“Hm?” Martial Awareness felt like he had heard incorrectly. What type of situation was this? They could simply step over Parade’s corpse and take the boss. Why was he talking about being allies and splitting the boss?

Martial Awareness wondered. Is this some sort of trick? But did the other side even need to play any tricks in a situation like this? Clearly not.

What’s more….. The three guilds standing next to each other were already a bit weird. Along with a God like Ye Qiu leading them, Martial Awareness suddenly realized that it might not actually be a joke.

“Not just now, but later. We’ll kill them together and split the loot.” Ye Xiu followed with the main point.

“Oh?” Martial Awareness understood that this was the key point. Was this going to be a long-term alliance? That doesn’t sound too bad!

“Hurry up and decide! The boss is about to die. If you don’t agree, we’ll have to steal it.” Ye Xiu said.

So direct and domineering…… Ye Xiu displayed such an attitude, after displaying their overwhelming strength. Did Martial Awareness have any choice? None. Even if he wasn’t certain, he should still agree for now and see what the other side would do first.

“Okay, I agree.” Martial Awareness quickly replied.

“Then, this boss will be split between us five.” Ye Xiu said.

“Five…..” Martial Awareness repeated this number and realized that Ye Xiu counted as his own separate entity.

“Yes. Do you need help killing this boss?” Ye Xiu asked.

“No need. More people will only make it messier.” Martial Awareness said. Even though the sudden attack had previously killed several of their members, they quickly regained their foothold. Relying on their current troops, killing Sword Master Kayou wouldn’t be too difficult. However, if more groups joined, they would need to worry about not accidentally injuring one another. More than one group fighting only worked when they were all from a single guild with good tacit coordination. A bunch of guilds swarming around would make things much more difficult.

“Okay, then we’ll watch.” Ye Xiu said. Sure enough, the three guilds didn’t go up and help. They didn’t surround them and stop them from escaping either. They really did just stand there, quietly watching from the sidelines..

They’re really confident!

Martial Awareness thought. They were letting him kill the boss. When the boss was killed, he could quickly pick up all the loot. Even if he died, how many would drop? He wouldn’t lose out either way!

This reasoning is very simple, but the other side was still allowing it to happen. What are they relying on?

Martial Awareness felt somewhat uneasy. With the boss almost dead, he didn’t need to lead his guild anymore. They could do it on their own. After Martial Awareness pondered for a bit, he immediately understood.

The other side was waiting for him to express his sincerity!

Allying together to kill a boss wasn’t a trap! It really was what he’s planning. After killing the boss, I need to share the loot with everyone for the alliance to be formed. If I try and take advantage in front of their eyes, I would still profit, but I would lose out on being apart of that beautiful scene.

Yes, a beautiful scene. Four guilds allied together led by God Ye Qiu. If they joined the wild boss competition, what would that scene be like? Martial Awareness was already looking forward to it. Everyone needed wild bosses, but their small guilds had another name for killing wild bosses: poaching!

Not competing or fighting for one, but poaching. Utterly despicable stealing.

But what could they do? They wanted to compete with the big guilds, but the big guilds would simply crush them. They couldn’t call that situation competing, but gifting them free equipment.

The small guilds could only avoid competing against the big guilds. Picking out the ones that no one noticed and stealthily killing them, wasn’t that what poaching was?

But with an alliance, their four guilds could compete with everyone else. It wasn’t like the small guilds had never thought of it before, but with the struggle between the guilds, establishing an alliance wasn’t easy. They would always scheme against one another, unable to cooperate. Like that, they couldn’t compete against large Club guilds. It wasn’t like there hadn’t been any precedent.

But it was different this time. Martial Awareness turned around and glanced at that top-heavy guy. The difference was that this time, they had a God.

God Ye Qiu’s status was too overbearing. They did not like it, but they couldn’t deny that his skill far surpassed their own. Only words that came out of someone like him would be able to persuade anyone. Only someone like him could be trusted.

Of course, more importantly….. The wild bosses were practically being monopolized. The small guilds kept throwing medicine at a dead horse trying to break this monopoly. To make this happen, as long as the method sounded plausible, they would be willing to try it.

After Martial Awareness thought about it for a bit, he decided that he wouldn’t be someone who lacked foresight. He would have Parade join the alliance and split the wild boss’s rewards among everyone.

The boss fight was nearing the end. When Sword Master Kayou dropped to 10% of his total health, the situation became a bit messy because of his Enrage, but Martial Awareness led his group and held on. Despite the casualties, they let the others know that they weren’t so bad as to be unable to take down a wild boss by themselves.

Finally, Sword Master Kayou fell. Parade didn’t express any joy though. There were six hundred players watching them. How could they be excited? The boss died, but they could still die at any moment.

“Okay, the items are here.” Martial Awareness didn’t immediately pick up the items and instead called out to the three other guild leaders and Ye Xiu.

He was being thorough with his actions. If he immediately picked up the items, only he would know what items dropped. If that happened, Martial Awareness could say what had dropped and hide items that he didn’t want to give away. The drops from wild bosses weren’t fixed. With good luck, there would be more drops. With bad luck, there would be fewer drops. There could be a difference of ten between the best and worst luck.

Martial Awareness stayed far away and didn’t pick up any of the items. Instead, he called for them to come over. The others couldn’t pick any of them up, but they could still look at them and see how many there were and what had dropped. Martial Awareness was very careful in his actions.

“Okay.”

The others replied and came over to look. The three guild leaders and Lord Grim went up to Sword Master Kayou’s corpse and checked the drops.

“A total of 21 items.” Martial Awareness said.

“Our luck’s pretty good! The last one we killed only dropped 19.” Ye Xiu said.

Forest Guardian Vich. Martial Awareness knew which boss they were talking about. When a wild boss was killed, the system would announce it. Thinking of how the the big guilds were busying PKing and unable to do anything else, he saw, as one of the small guilds, that the big guilds looked down on them and took these bosses one after the other. It made Martial Awareness feel overjoyed. He checked the global chat again and again, enjoying the announcement saying “Guild Parade has killed Sword Master Kayou.”

“21 drops split between five guilds. Parade can take the extra one. After all, they were the ones to kill it.” White Stream said. He hadn’t gotten anything from Forest Guardian Vich. Seeing the drops displayed in front of him, he was starting to feel impatient.

“An extra one? How shameful! They did all the work. We didn’t do anything at all and we’re just going to give them one extra? Thats no good!” Conquering Cloud’s Yue Ziqin wasn’t greedy and spoke fairly.

Martial Awareness heard them speak and he thought of the future. He laughed: “It must have been tiring coming all this way from so far. No worries. We’ll split it that way!”

“What are your thoughts?” Loulan Slash was still annoyed at his overthinking from before. Now, he wanted to hear from Ye Xiu. So what if he acted like a b*tch or a little kid?

“I say there’s no need to be so picky. There are plenty of bosses. We can just kill more.” Ye Xiu said.

How domineering!!

The four guild leaders quietly thought.

Snatching wild bosses was an extremely difficult task in Glory and he just casually said “Just kill more.” It was as if they were eating together and someone said “Just eat more.” Such a casual and nonchalant reply really made the four guild leaders respect him. That was air of a God.

“Okay! We’ll split it between everyone and Parade will take the extra!” Loulan Slash said.

The other two didn’t say anything. Martial Awareness heard God’s words and picked an item. The others took turns taking an item. They didn’t bicker over the details. Why? Because Ye Xiu’s words had knocked them off balance. After killing a boss, there was no need to bicker over who should get more or less. Just kill more. The more they killed, the more total drops there’ll be. Every small difference in drops would average out in the end and become negligible.

Chapter 678: Crimson Scene

Four guilds.

Although one of Parade’s groups had been wiped out, they had been rather heroic, fighting the boss. Compared to the other three guilds, they had fewer players remaining, but with a promising future, Parade’s performance didn’t lose out to the other three. Besides, they still had many more people than Ye Xiu’s group. There were only four people on Ye Xiu’s side.

Chen Guo felt the need to hurry and establish their guild, after seeing the elated and overjoyed looks of the players from the other guilds. She started to count with her fingers to see if she could think of 20 players to create a guild together. With Chen Guo’s experience with the game, this was doable. But after scrolling through her friend’s list, it didn’t matter whether they were in Excellent Dynasty or not. All of them were in a guild already. This was because no one wanted to miss out on the stat points rewarded by the guild’s guardian. Even players who were determined not to join any guilds didn’t like missing those stat points. They often complained to the game company why they needed to join a guild in order to receive those stat points.

However, switching guilds wasn’t a difficult task. Chen Guo didn’t try to persuade her friends one by one. She just sent it out in the notification group, asking if any of her friends were willing to come and give her a hand.

Chen Guo had good relationships with people. Apart from a few, who were really attached to their guilds and expressed their apologies, many of them were just there for the free stat points. They weren’t very loyal to their guilds and said: “If you’re planning on establishing a guild, then of course I’ll help you out.”

Chen Guo received these kinds of replies and easily gathered 20 people. However, she was clear that these friends were only joining to meet the required numbers, so they wouldn’t be very loyal to the guild. This meant that they wouldn’t be interested in any guild activities They were the types of people who would play with their close friends. To them, guilds were only a source of skill points. So even though Chen Guo had received help from these friends, she still needed to hurry and take down the guild guardian.

But to obtain a guardian, one needed the appropriate guild level, which was something that needed to be leveled by the guild players. Those guys were there take what was readily available, so they couldn’t be counted on. As for people like Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, and Steamed Bun, it would be a waste to have them spend time completing guild quests. Would Chen Guo have to do everything by herself in the end? Chen Guo began to sweat just at the thought of it. Tthis wasn’t something that could be achieved by a single person. It seemed that Chen Guo would need to recruit people from the outside.

When Chen Guo was thinking about this matter, Ye Xiu was having a discussion with the guild leaders of the four guilds about their following grand plan. They felt that they already had enough members in the alliance and that there was no need for any more members. After all, there would only be around 20 items dropped from a wild boss. If there really was an alliance between all 20 Club guilds, then would that mean every guild would only receive one material after killing the wild boss? It felt pretty tight. Furthermore, there were times where there were fewer than twenty items. In that case, it would be awkward if there weren’t enough to divide between everyone.

They would experiment with four guilds first and recruit more allies if it didn’t work. After all, this wouldn’t be difficult to do because there were only a few major guilds who had the capability to win over the wild boss. There were still queue of guilds who couldn’t get anything!

The few were chatting while waiting on any news about wild bosses. But after chatting to a point where they were searching for things to talk about, they felt that something wasn’t right.

This was not how they should hunt for a boss! Who would just hang in the game waiting for news? They should still use this time to do whatever they needed to do! Everyone should only come together immediately after receiving any news on the boss.

When they thought of this, everyone prepared to leave and do whatever they needed to do. Now that Ye Xiu had gained three guilds as his allies, he promptly requested the three guilds to be on the lookout for Deception.

“God, are you really going to keep killing him. Aren’t you taking this too far?” Loulan Slash joked. He was someone who had interacted Ye Xiu for a long time, he wouldn’t think that Ye Xiu was someone who hated someone so deeply just after one incident and kill that person endlessly!

“I think his skills are pretty good. I plan on recruiting him into my team.” Ye Xiu said.

“Huh?” Loulan Slash was also thinking about doing that! But what does killing him continuously have to do with recruiting them into the team? If you want to recruit someone, shouldn’t you treat them nicer?

Although that was what Loulan Slash thought, he couldn’t really hold any opinions against God’s method of doing things. Since God already had intentions of roping in Deception, he decided to give up on Deception. His Heavenly Swords was getting ready for the Alliance and he had done all sorts of preparations already. Even though Loulan Slash didn’t have many players like Deception, he didn’t have so few that he desperately needed more, so he wouldn’t have any sentiments if Deception were taken away.

After each guild had left, the team did whatever they had to do. Ye Xiu led Tang Rou and Steamed Bun to scrap pick again. Chen Guo told Ye Xiu about the guild’s situation. Ye Xiu didn’t have any opinions towards it. Chen Guo immediately gathered her group of friends together. Those people had a guild, so they naturally had to leave it. They would only be able to accept her guild invite after five days.

Ye Xiu’s group of three scrap-picked for a while without seeing any news about any wild bosses spawning. Their work and rest routines recently were quite good They had stayed up pretty late tonight, so Ye Xiu notified the allied guilds that they were going to log off.

Of course, the guild leaders felt regretful. They wanted God to be a robot that stayed online for 24 hours, but they knew that this was impossible. In any case, their current alliance was harmonious and unified. The big guilds wouldn’t meddle with them for now. The four of them combined would most definitely be a strong power. Ye Xiu’s absence wouldn’t hinder them from killing the boss if it appeared at night. And if Ye Xiu didn’t join in, he wouldn’t be able to receive any of the materials that dropped, so there weren’t any objections to this matter. This was one of the reasons why Chen Guo wanted to hurry and create a guild quickly. If they relied on Ye Xiu for everything, they would miss out on many opportunities because he couldn’t stay online for the entire day.

As for Wei Chen, the world war was still as intense as ever, Wei Chen didn’t even lift his head when the people told him to go rest. He gave two messy hums. No one was able to tell whether he would sleep or not. In any case, the few just left first.

After returning to the practice room on the morning of the second day, Wei Chen’s posture didn’t seem to have any differences compared to last night.

“Tsk tsk tsk despite being so old, your ability to stay up all night hasn’t seemed to decrease from all these years.” Ye Xiu said.

“F*ck off” Wei Chen stretched as if he weren’t in the middle of an intense battle.

“How are the battles going?” Ye Xiu held a cigarette in his mouth and watched Wei Chen from behind.

Wei Chen also lit one and forced a bitter laugh: “How else could it be? It’s a pure waste of time.”

“You seem pretty into it.” Ye Xiu said.

“It’s not bad to be feeling hot-blooded again.” Wei Chen said.

“What about the wild bosses from last night?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Three announcements.” Wei Chen said.

“Oh? Which three guilds were they taken down by?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Heavenly Justice, Conquering Clouds, and Radiant.” Wei Chen remembered all.

They were all from the alliance, Ye Xiu immediately knew that their alliance was working very well. Just as expected, the moment he logged online, the four guild leaders of the four guilds came over enthusiastically to report their success. The number of wild bosses that they had killed last night weren’t three, but four. Wei Chen was engaged in an intense fight so he had missed one of the announcements.

“Not bad, not bad at all!” Ye Xiu said.

“Haha, this is the loot from yesterday. Have a look, is there anything you need?” Loulan Slash sent over a dense list of items. Although it was normal to not receive anything since he hadn’t been there, God’s position was different, the allied guilds let him have some special privileges. It was evident that Loulan Slash’s list of items was the complete list. It wasn’t just the ones he had received. He couldn’t have come to this decision for the other three guilds on his own, so this must have been the result after a discussion between the four guilds.

“Haha, there’s no need. I didn’t even participate, how can I take any.” Ye Xiu refused. He didn’t want to be given special treatment because of his status. He couldn’t just focus on what was happening in-game. Once the guild in Chen Guo’s hands developed, they might have to get someone else to take over these responsibilities in the future. It would be good if he started off being equal with everyone.

“Did anyone see Deception last night?” Ye Xiu asked them.

“No.” The few guilds all replied. Ye Xiu knew where Deception had logged off, so he naturally told them about the location. At that time, they expressed confidently with a pat to their chest, saying that there’s no problem because they would join up and organise someone to take turns watching over the place.

“You guy’s aren’t going to take a break?” Ye Xiu asked the four soon afterwards.

“Not tired yet!” The four gave the same answer. They were too excited. They had never killed wild bosses before with this much delight. Even though the four allied guilds only received a quarter of the reward each, it was very satisfying to see their own guilds appear on TV again and again. At this moment, the materialistic profits weren’t as important.

After Wei Chen finished smoking, he finally got up to have a rest. He wasn’t made of iron. Despite gaming with so much enthusiasm last night, his energy had come to an end and his face was filled with fatigue.

There were people like Wei Chen, who gamed the whole night and went to rest, but there were also people who had slept for the night and had gotten up to dive into the battle again. Only compared to last night, most of the player’s hot-blooded enthusiasm had finally been extinguished. Once they were calm enough to see their stats in red and their empty equipment section, the players wouldn’t understand why they had been so excited last night for.

After such an intense battle, the absolute majority of the players were unable to make up for the losses they had suffered yesterday. In the morning, the world war in the game had loosened up much more. Many people swayed around with incomplete equipment sets as if they didn’t know what they should do.

At this time, the pressure had on the players that belonged to the big guilds decreased greatly . Their battles were unified and with discipline. Although there were losses in the fight, at the same time, they also plundered equipment from the opponents that they had killed. Afterwards, the guild allocated these stolen equipment to everyone, so they were just trading equipment in a sense.

However, no one could skirt around the penalty that one would lose experience for dying. At this moment in the Heavenly Domain, the stats of the majority of the players were red as if they were coated in blood.

Chapter 679: It’s Just a Level 60 Wild Boss

How could these injured players still have the passion to continue fighting? The vast majority of them were starting to feel annoyed at their previous hot-bloodedness. There was always silence after noise. This time’s world war had erupted quickly. The first signs of its development started at the beginning of the playoffs. By the time the first round of the finals finished, the war had reached its peak. That night, very few of the still fighting players left the battlefield in good condition, especially the individuals who fought alone; they were practically running around naked, when the sun rose.

If they were able to actually win some honor, the war could be considered meaningful. The loyal fans definitely wouldn’t feel any remorse. The problem was that no guild had suffered any significant losses. Which guilds had been slaughtered until they were left running away, crying for their parents? None. The small advantages gained in any of the battlefields didn’t affect the overall situation. The big Club guilds involved in the world war wouldn’t be shaken in just a single night.

This war was purely a show of intent. Apart from venting their emotions, it was completely meaningless. After a burst of passion, emptiness would naturally follow. Their hearts would be empty as well as their inventory.

Many of the players wanted to cry! Of course, there were no lack of players, who found the experience thrilling. They skipped delightedly without any clothing over to others and bragged about how they sliced off the head of an arrogant enemy last night. These people clearly pursued happiness.

Ye Xiu had Lord Grim to walk around casually. Most of what he saw were players standing around at a loss for what to do. The big Club guilds wouldn’t be so idle though. They bragged on the global chat about how brave or fierce their players had been in the world war and how their team’s fans didn’t lose to anyone.

From the announcements given by the Club guilds in the global chat, it seemed as if everyone had won in this war. But from the appearances of the players all over the streets, it seemed as if everyone had lost this war.

Ye Xiu wasn’t too surprised by this scene. A war based purely from passion would end with this result. It was just a game though. If no one had any passion and everything had to be done based on what benefits or profit one could gain, the game wouldn’t be fun.

The various Club guilds praised their players for being mighty, while consoling them for their losses. The guilds all had some kind of equipment compensation event. It wasn’t too important if someone wanted to take advantage of it.

They distributed their equipment to everyone. It was more important to provide care for their fans and let everyone know that they were one group. For the Club guilds, their attitude towards their supporters was important.

How could these Club guilds not be skilled with these strategies? Their players fought until they were covered in red and then they had to pay for their losses. It sounded painful, but this was the passion of their players. In truth, the Club guilds liked this sort of passion. If everyone was cold and rationale, a lot of work would be difficult to do.

“To think this war would end so quickly.” The four allied guild leaders sighed. They hoped that these big Club guilds would never stop fighting. But it looked like that this period had come to an end. Many players couldn’t continue on with their injuries, so the war slowly died down.

“No problem! There’s still the second round of the finals!” The guys, who were taking advantage of this situation, obviously hoped that the second round of the finals would cause another war to erupt.

“How many wild bosses are left this week?’ Ye Xiu asked Loulan Slash.

Loulan Slash had a detailed count. “36.” He replied.

After the guild war ended, while they comforted their fans, they also began competing for wild bosses again.

“There are still 36 wild bosses remaining this week. Among these, there are nine Level 70 ones. Last night, when everyone was still busy, a total of 7 wild bosses spawned. Among them, four were Level 70. They were Darkness Palace’s Night Streak, World Tree’s Guardian Vich, Sighing Ravine’s Sword Master Kayou, and Setting Sun Waterfall’s Hidden Warrior Alyan.

Don’t look at how the big Club guilds were busy PKing. They didn’t stop paying attention to wild bosses, especially the important Level 70 ones, which were given more details.

“It seems like a few guilds took advantage of the situation.” The various big guilds thought. It didn’t matter who killed them. If they set out, those guilds had no chance anyways.

“While we have nothing to do, have everyone be on the lookout for bosses.” The various big guilds all gave similar orders to their subordinates. The finals wasn’t over. They didn’t know whether the fires of war would erupt again. In any case, as guilds who could control themselves, they definitely wouldn’t take the initiative to provoke a war. The big Club guilds let these 7 wild bosses go and participated in this unfavorable world war to side with their fan’s passion and resolve.

Now that things were looking calm, they wanted to take a break. Of course, this break didn’t mean vacation. Wild bosses still needed to be won.

“Understood!” The players gave a resounding affirmation to their respective guild’s orders.

Time slowly passed. There weren’t too many players in the early morning. Everyone had sorted out their emotions and made up for their equipment. As for the Club players? They adjusted quickly, especially the elite teams. After this huge war. The guilds spent great efforts to regroup everyone back together. Everyone’s equipment was compensated and they worked hard to regain their lost experience. In such a chaotic war, everyone had died at least once, unless you never fought on the front lines.

Everyone was done methodically up until the various big guilds suddenly received a message.

Rising Sky Strait, Level 60 boss, Ocean Returner Ganliya.

“It’s just a level 60 wild boss?” The core members of the big guilds said. Level 60 wild bosses weren’t something they coveted. Let alone the elite teams, they didn’t need a fixed group to send over. Just send whoever was nearby!

“It’s just a Level 60 wild boss?” What the big guilds didn’t know was that several smaller Club guilds had the same attitude as them. They would certainly raise their eyebrows if they knew about this. When did these guilds ever express such indifference towards wild bosses? Even if it was a Level 60 one.

Rising Sky Strait.

The various guilds, who received reports of the boss, quickly dispatched players to hurry over.

On Blue Brook Guild’s side, Blue River was controlling his main Heavenly Domain account, Blue Bridge Spring Snow. He was leading his hastily put together group to Rising Sky Strait.

After experiencing a world war, the guild players were exhausted. How could Blue River not feel bad standing out to share some of the burden? As a result, the position of leading a group to snatch a wild boss, which he didn’t like to do, landed on him.

“If we get there fast, it’d be great if we could kill the boss before anyone arrived…….” Blue River thought rather extravagantly.

Clearly, Blue Brook Guild wasn’t the quickest to arrive. Midway, they received a message from up ahead. A guild had already gathered there and was starting to clear the field.

“Which guild? So fast!” Blue River asked.

“Parade.” The other side responded.

“Parade, huh. So they want to poach….” Blue River thought to himself. He had knowledge of the strength of various powers. He was very clear about the strength of these smaller Club guilds.

“Hurry!” Blue River shouted to his group. Even though it was just Parade, the boss was only level 60. Killing it wouldn’t be difficult for them. If they arrived too late, the boss might already be dead.

“Be careful and watch it carefully.” Blue River contacted the scouts up ahead.

“Another guild has arrived.” The other side replied.

“Oh, which guild?” Blue River hastily asked.

“Heavenly Justice!” The other side reported.

“Oh, that’s perfect. Let them fight it out. When we arrive, they’ll be easy pickings.” Blue River was delighted.

“Another guild has come.” The scouts continued to message, “Radiant.”

“Oh.”

“Conquering Cloud has also come!” Another message came.

“What’s going on? How could these guilds be faster than us?” Blue River was a bit depressed. Wild bosses depended on manpower. The more players a guild had, the larger their intelligence network would be. As a result, the top Club guilds with their huge fanbase had a huge advantage over these smaller Club guilds. Yet these four smaller Club guilds had arrived first, while their Blue Brook Guild was still only halfway there, which meant these guilds’ intelligence network was much faster than theirs.

But it didn’t matter who got there first. The boss still had to be fought over. If they couldn’t move the boss away, then it was actually better to arrive late! Blue River thought. He messaged the scouts up ahead: “Give me reports about the situation whenever you can.”

“Herb Garden has come!” The scouts replied.

“How lively…..” Blue River mumbled.

Waves slammed fiercely into the the stone shores of Rising Sky Strait. A huge battle had already began on shore. The first to arrive was Parade. They weren’t polite and started fighting the wild boss Ocean Returner Ganliya already.

A group from Herb Garden had arrived. This group consisted of nearby players as well. The player leading the group was called Amaranth, an absolute core member of Herb Garden. A core member like this was definitely trustworthy. Letting him pick up the items wasn’t an issue.

When Amaranth led his group over, he suddenly felt confused. Parade was attacking the boss and around them were three guilds just standing there, watching.

He could understand if these spectators wanted to wait and attack Parade later, but why was Parade doing nothing? Parade could clearly see the oriole standing behind them, yet they’re just continuing to slash around as the mantis. What were they thinking?

Amaranth was puzzled, so he didn’t move either. Who didn’t want to wait and kill them later for easy pickings? It simplified matters! And like this, guild after guild arrived. Tyrannical Ambition, Blue Brook Guild, Samsara, Misty Rain, even Excellent Dynasty. Even though they had been relegated, they still had aspirations.

The guilds had all arrived. They were all confused as they watched in wonder. The Parade players killing the boss were a bit nervous! F*ck, why are there so many people? Are you all here to watch us perform or something?

Chapter 680: Actual Helpers

Blue Brook Guild wasn’t early at all. By the time they arrived, old rivals like Herb Garden, Tyrannical Ambition, and Excellent Dynasty were already there. Blue River looked around. He hardly knew anyone among the normal players, but it was hard not to recognize the people leading because they were old and core members of their respective guilds.

Although they were opponents who constantly fought each other, the people managing the guilds also had professional attitudes like the pro players: “enemies in the match but friends outside of it”. No one was lenient when snatching the boss, but since they hadn’t started yet, it wasn’t strange to gather together and chat.

Blue River saw the group leaders of the guilds huddled up and muttering, so he came up to greet them.

“Oh, it’s Blue Bridge! Long time no see.”

The people huddled together greeted back. Blue River hadn’t been leading groups to fight bosses recently, so there were less interactions between him and the other guilds. This made made the “long time no see” natural.

“Mhmm……” Blue River answered, he didn’t have to explain and went straight into the conversation: “What’s going on here?”

“Parade attacked the moment they arrived and are now trapped. It seems that they’re now in an awkward position. They can't walk out of it and they would be killed by the boss if they don't fight back. Tsk tsk, what a tragedy!” They came up with such a conclusion after observing.

“Oh…..” Blue River replied, but he felt something wasn’t right, and it was soon brought up by Herb Garden’s Amaranth: “There's quite a lot of guilds today. It seems like this will require quite some effort.”

Yes, there were a lot of guilds.

It was rare to see guilds like Parade, Conquering Clouds, Radiant, and Heavenly Justice in battles for wild bosses. Although they didn’t see them as threats, it was annoying to have four additional guilds, when they already had numerous other big guilds because everyone only fought for themselves. It was hard to find a time to dive and cut into the fight. Everyone hoped to gain the advantage of attacking later, but the boss’s health didn’t wait for players. Who would lose their patience and interfere first?

They wouldn’t discuss about this matter. These were methods that the big guilds would use in the following competition. Who would discuss about how they would fight?

Parade was fighting in a huge group. The boss’s figure wasn’t prominent. However, Ocean Returner Galiya was still pretty noticeable, so Blue River was able to find the target with ease. When he checked the boss’s HP, it had decreased quite a lot. After looking around, every guild was prepared to act at any moment.

After Blue River joined the group for a short chat, all of the group leaders scattered and returned to their players. The guilds started to be aware of one another’s actions, while planning how to make their move. At the same time, Blue River started to receive messages coming from the core members of other guilds. Tyrannical Ambition suggested an alliance to get rid of Herb Garden, while Herb Garden said Excellent Dynasty had offered to work together to get of Blue Brook Guild, and Herb Garden didn’t approve to use those methods and suggested for an alliance to get rid of Excellent Dynasty instead. After that, Excellent Dynasty messaged about working together to get rid of Tyrannical Ambition…...

Here it comes again…...

Blue River looked at all of the messages, the draining feeling on his mind returned. He didn’t wish to take part in these courteous, but insincere and deceiving tussles. But these things were unavoidable if one were to lead a group to snatch a wild boss. Especially if it’s in these kind of situations, where it seemed peaceful, but the fight had yet to start. It would have been less troublesome if they just started fighting in the beginning.

“Sure!”

“Sure!”

“Sure!”

“Sure!”

…...

Blue River was really tired of these things and didn’t bother to analyze the given information to find any opportunities. He just accepted them all without responsibility.

Finally, the boss’s HP had dropped to a quarter of its original health. Under normal circumstances, everyone would have started to make a move at this time. However, the big guilds were able to keep their cool. They wanted to leave this opportunity to Conquering Clouds, Radiant, and Heavenly Justice and have them make their move first.

No one would have thought that the smaller Club guilds were able to hold their cool even more so than the big guilds. Despite the drastic drop of the boss’s health, they were still able to hold their cool and not make a move.

“F*ck...... small guilds are just small guilds. Have they ever snatched a wild boss before? Do they have any common knowledge?” Someone complained from the big guilds. In reality, Conquering Clouds, Radiant, and Heavenly Justice weren’t small in the eyes of normal players at all. However, they were still small in their eyes. As for the guilds built by normal players with a few hundred people. D*mn, do those even count as guilds?

The small guild’s calm movements placed the big guilds in an awkward position. They couldn’t just make their move and let the small guilds gain the initiative and strike their backs, no? No, that would be embarrassing, so they continued to wait.

The big guilds remained inactive and continued to watch the boss’s health decrease. When the small guilds still made no move, many wanted to rush over and remind them : “Hey, if you don’t attack, then no one’s going to get that boss!”

The boss’s health went from one quarter, one fifth and then to one sixth…...

Motionless, motionless and still motionless.

The small guilds were motionless like a mountain while the big guilds were sitting on pins and needles. At last, someone came to a realization: If we’re here, they wouldn’t be dare to move.

Yes, they must be intimidated because we’re all here…...

When someone thought of this, the three small guilds finally made their move.

“F*ck!” People who thought so felt as if they had been proven wrong, so they felt embarrassed.

The three guilds hadn’t been moving, but once they did, they moved in such a thunderous way. Each player bared their fangs and claws as they leapt towards Parade.

Yeah! That’s more like it!

Fight, kill! Make it fierce, so we can clear you guys up later!

The big guilds were satisfied. They started to secretly distribute players, preparing to start at any time. Take over the boss, to attack other guilds that planned on taking over the boss too, avoiding other guilds messing them up. They have much to do! How could they not assign each of them tasks?

At this moment, everyone noticed that something was wrong.

Yes, wrong, it was very wrong! When the three guilds leapt ahead, why did the health of Ocean Returner Galiya decrease even faster?

One seventh, one eighth…… one ninth…… Enraged!!!

F*ck, you guys should get rid of players of Parade before taking over the boss. Who would snatch it so impatiently like you guys. Would you even be able to take the aggro at this point? If you fight like this, the boss will fall before the players of Parade. They would have taken up majority of the damage output so this boss would definitely go to them! Bunch of idiots, pigs, do you know how to snatch a boss?

The big guilds fumed. They hadn’t thought that these guys from the small guilds would be so incapable and end up ruining everything instead. They hastily prepared to make their move, preparing to give a lesson to these small guilds who didn’t know how to snatch a boss properly.

But they were too late. Before they could rush to the front, the system came out with the announcement: Guild Parade has killed Ocean Returner Galia.

F*ck, these idiots!!!!!!!

The big guilds would never think they would end up with this situation. Everyone nearly died of rage. But luckily, this was only a level 60 wild boss so everyone’s sentiments were easy to digest. At this time, the big guilds really wished to see the expressions of those three idiotic guilds! Are you snatching the boss? You were merely supporting Parade’s attacks. You stupid birds, now you know? Are you stupefied?

Players of the big guilds didn’t plan to let out their sentiments through physical force. They believed that the three small guilds must be mourning with tearless grief at the moment. They must be having mixed feelings of remorse and shame and having unresistable emotions to run into the wall. However, who would have thought that when the boss fell and the announcement came out, the players on that side stopped immediately. The three guilds withdrew their players as if nothing happened. Then there was Parade, who finished clearing the battlefield with cheerful laughter and just walked across in front of the big guilds.

“What’s…… going on?” Everyone from the big guilds noticed that something wasn’t right, the leading core members gathered again for a small meeting. As they gazed at the silhouettes of the four guilds that had left…… these four…… why did they seem as if they were one guild when walking together?

“It seems as if not many people from Parade died?” Someone mentioned.

“What’s with this?”

“Those three guilds…… they didn’t attack the players of Parade at all?”

“Don’t tell me that they concentrated on the boss the moment they made their move and planned to snatch the boss this way? Do they have any common sense?”

Blue River didn’t express his thoughts. He was still staring at the people walking farther and farther away. He immediately saw that among the characters was a silhouette, his appearance was unbalanced, the proportion of the head equipment was clearly unequal to the legs. He walked among the group with many people clustered around him.

Blue River couldn’t read the person’s ID clearly but he already had some sort of hunch. He promptly let his Blue Bridge Spring Snow rush out and quickly closed up the distance. When he saw the person’s ID, it perfectly matched his dreaded hunch.

Lord Grim!

“Blue Bridge……” A few from the big guilds watched strangely as Blue Bridge Spring Snow sprinted ahead for a section before halting suddenly and walking back slowly.

“Those guys…… They’re supporting the attack……” Blue River said.

“What?”

“They’re working together! Do you understand? The four of them are one, Parade deals with the boss. The other three made their moves to help defeat the boss quicker, not to snatch it. We’ve been fooled.” Blue River said.

“......”

Everyone was speechless, but they had to admit that what Blue River said was highly probable. Otherwise, it was against common knowledge to just fight the boss without clearing other players. Even though they often called those guilds “small guilds”, were they really small guilds? Of course not, they were guilds working under professional teams and had the same aim and working direction as them. How could they not have common sense? Why would they commit these kind of mistakes?

The fault was with the big guilds. They underestimated their opponents. They had never even viewed the opponents as equal. Instead, they were planning on how to deal with the guilds beside them. As a result, all their plannings were for naught. The four “small guilds” had gotten rid of the boss magnificently under everyone’s gaze and left with a low-profile……

Chapter 681: A Day of Harvest

“How did these four guilds suddenly become allies??” The core leaders began discussing this question. Blue River didn’t participate. He told them farewell and left.

Why were they suddenly allies?

Even though Blue River didn’t have proof, he was certain that it was related to that guy. If he was the one who facilitated the creation of the alliance, with his status in Glory, it really would be possible for him to keep everyone under control…...

If everyone could be kept under control…...

Blue River thought of how the three guilds rushed forward to help Parade quickly kill the boss without any hesitation or scheming and then left together as one group. This sort of peaceful alliance without any in-fighting made him quite jealous!

Ye Qiu must be one of the main reasons for their alliance. Blue River had no evidence, but he was already certain. He may have realized it, but the other core leaders hadn’t. Blue River obviously wouldn’t share his knowledge of it with the others. After leaving the area with his group, he immediately reported it to Blue Brook Guild’s leader, Changing Spring.

“F*ck!” Changing Spring couldn’t help but curse, when he heard the news. As soon as he saw the name Ye Qiu or Lord Grim, his mood would always turn sour, no matter how good of a mood he had been in.

This person never seemed to bring good news.

Changing Spring recalled. He had done some good things, but he had done more harm than good. Anything good he did was easily erased by his bad deeds.

This time, he once again brought trouble. Four small guilds formed an alliance? What a problem! Changing Spring immediately wanted his spies to confirm this situation. Unfortunately, these small guilds usually weren’t their competitors, so even though he had a few spies in their guilds, no one kept too close of attention to them. Now, he suddenly needed these spies, but he couldn’t remember who these spies were. It made Changing Spring very frustrated.

The other guilds also heard their core leaders’ reports, saying that the four small guilds had formed an alliance to kill wild bosses. The big guilds wouldn’t ignore this kind of information and looked for their spies to confirm it.

Soon, spies from several guilds reported back. This sort of alliance wasn’t a secret. After fighting for wild bosses a few times, everyone would know anyways, so the guilds didn’t keep it a secret. Moreover, God Ye Qiu was participating. That wasn’t a secret either. As a result, everyone was certain about the reason for this alliance.

This news was like a strike of thunder to the big guilds. What’s going on? It was going so well! Why did this guy come out from his nest again? This time, his actions were on a large-scale. He directly brought along four guilds. Was he about to lead a peasant revolt?

The big guilds were uneasy.

In the beginning, they didn’t think much of the four guilds allying together. For this kind of competition, there would only be their own interests. How could there be lasting friendship? But once they heard that God Ye Qiu was leading the alliance, they could no longer stay calm anymore.

As soon as we stop paying attention to him, he stirs up trouble!!

The big guilds all cried. But the system wouldn’t care about their feelings! Wild bosses would still spawn.

Not long after Ocean Return Ganliya died, another boss spawned.

Except this time, it was a Level 55 one: Gale Gobi’s Buddhist Zhen Mo.

Level 55 bosses were naturally less difficult and Buddhist Zhen Mo was a pure Battle Mage. He wasn’t like other bosses, who could use skills from several classes. These types of NPCs were much easier to deal with.

The guilds, which received information of the boss, dispatched their troops. But after knowing about the four guild alliance with Ye Qiu interfering, they paid a great amount of attention to the situation.

But sending their elite groups over for a Level 55 wild boss felt a bit disgraceful!

Let’s wait and see! The big guild leaders thought similar things. This Level 55 boss was treated as a testing stone to observe things.

This time, they didn’t see the four guilds appear nor Lord Grim.

As for Ye Xiu and the others, they only found about the boss after its death was announced. None of the four guilds had encountered the boss. It wasn’t too unexpected. Level 55 maps were low-leveled. Not many players would be there. Even for players sent to look out for wild bosses, they couldn’t scout out every corner of every map.

Finding wild bosses depended on luck. More players simply lowered the influence of luck, but no guilds could reach every corner of the Heavenly Domain. When a boss spawned and when a boss was found all required time.

This time, Buddhist Zhen Mo spawned near a city, so it didn’t take long to gather everyone to attack it. Level 55 bosses were usually attacked as soon as one arrived. They wouldn’t wait. As a result, Herb Garden was the first to arrive and killed it quickly. The other big guilds had gotten into conflicts. But after the boss was killed, everyone quickly left. The alliance that deeply worried the guild leaders didn’t appear.

This boss went by just like this, but they couldn’t be calm yet. Everyone knew that the battle was just beginning…...

The morning passed. No boss spawned, so no one knew what their future battles would be like. At this moment, the world war erupted again.

The cause was once again because of the teams. However, the timing was different. Last time, the war began after the match and that batch of players started fighting. This time, it began in the morning. When the players logged on one after the other, they began discussing the match yesterday.As a result, they started arguing and fighting. More and more players participated, so a few players from last night and the players this morning from the big guilds once again started a war in order to show their support for their team.

The wars of fire this time wouldn’t stop so easily. Players increased as the day went on. As more and more players logged on, more and more would enter the war. Many players from last night, who had been stripped naked of their equipment, had their spirits reignited when they entered this kind of environment again.

Wei Chen came to the practice room in the afternoon. After receiving the news, he cursed out loud and began fighting.

The alliance took advantage of the bosses again. And no Club guild didn’t know of their alliance at this point. During their boss fights, they encountered several other small guilds, but Ye Xiu didn’t add them into the alliance this time.

Four guilds was enough. More guilds meant less materials for each of them and it would be sort of pointless. Killing the wild boss was just the method to getting the materials! If they split all of the items among every guild, no one would be able to grow.

Right now, the loot was being split between five parties. Each party received three to five materials from a boss. It was low enough already. Any less materials and no one would be happy.

That night, when Ye Xiu logged off, they had killed seven bosses: three Level 70, two Level 65, one Level 60, and one Level 55. All of them landed into their alliance’s pockets. In this process, the other small guilds clearly couldn’t compare. They weren’t any threat at all.

The four allied guild leaders were overjoyed and excited.

They were excited because they had gained so much these two days and overjoyed because they had been able to join this alliance, especially for Radiant and Parade, who had hesitated initially. Now, they were thanking the gods for making the right choice. Seeing how pitiful the other small guilds were, was it because they were weak? No. Their strength wouldn’t lose to any of the four guilds, but the difference was that they weren’t in an alliance.

Seeing how these small guilds were still struggling like before, the four allied guild leaders felt deeply moved. When they competed for the wild bosses against the big guilds in the past, they had been pitiful too. Even so, they weren’t going to welcome anyone into the alliance just because they felt sympathy for them.

Plainly speaking, their alliance was purely for their mutual interests. There wasn’t any kindness or hatred when fighting for wild bosses. It was purely a competition. Even though there were different methods for doing so, the competition was fair. Some guilds were stronger than others, but if you were strong, you were strong. The big guilds were bigger because of the many years of accumulation. They had spent great efforts and seized many opportunities to get to where they were today.

Their monopoly over the wild bosses was painful for the smaller guilds, but it didn’t have anything to do with right or wrong. If the small guilds had the ability, they could also conduct a monopoly.

This was the cruel nature of competition.

Apart from killing wild bosses, Ye Xiu also had Tang Rou and Steamed Bun go scrap picking again. There were accidents, of course. In this kind of intense war, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had died once. Steamed Bun had died three times. Ye Xiu hadn’t died, but he didn’t dare to bring his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella with him.

They lost some, but they gained much more. They only aimed for the elites and picked up countless equipment from them until their inventories were full.

These pieces of equipment were put into Happy’s guild storage. Chen Guo went over to admire all of it and knew that their guild’s starting point was very very high. The elites from the big guilds! Their equipment was much more difficult to get than common equipment. These were all items that the big guilds especially prepared to win popularity. And these now belonged to Happy. Scrap picking….. maybe it really is a fast way to get rich? Chen Guo thought to herself.

Chapter 682: Dispatching Troops

They were only able to get so many drops from scrap picking because of this particular occasion and their superior skill. In these intense battles between elite groups, every player was expert player. If a normal player tried to scrap pick, the player would simply end up as a cannon fodder.

It had been a fruitful day. Of course, it could have gone better. Deception never logged on.

The night passed.

The next day, while the big guilds were still busy killing each other, they continued to scrap pick and sweep through any remaining wild bosses that week. When night came, the game gradually calmed down.

The second round of Glory’s season eight championship finals would take place tonight. This match would also be the final match of the entire season and the season’s conclusion. This season’s champion would also be decided by the end of today.

As for the individuals excited about killing wild bosses, whether to continue paying attention to any wild bosses or watch the final match of the year was a difficult choice. In the end, Ye Xiu displayed the air of a God and simply said: “Let’s watch the match. There will be bosses in the future.”

“Ahem…..” Loulan Slash coughed. For the previous round, if he recalled correctly, God Ye Qiu told him to take this chance and grab a few more bosses. How come he changed his mind this time? It seemed like he didn’t feel too confident of their future with just the two of them cooperating. Now that five parties had allied together, he was very confident of their future!

Everyone wanted to watch the finals very much. When they heard God Ye Qiu give his opinion, they tossed the game to the side and began waiting for the finals to begin.

For the final match, the broadcast arranged about an hour of time to show some highlights and give some introduction.

Such as the first round’s highlights, their viewpoints on the current circumstances of each team, what the two teams had prepared during these two days of rest, and even the war going on in the game.

Overall, they did everything they could to hype up this match and gave their thoughts on what might occur.

After the first round of the finals, Team Samsara led Team Blue Rain with 7.5 points to 2.

In the two rounds of the finals, a total of 19 points could be won. As long as one side was able to win 10 points, that side would be the victor. As a result, in the second round, as long as Team Samsara won the group arena or team competition, they would win. The individual competition didn’t matter too much for Team Samsara.

Of course, if Team Samsara won all three rounds in the individual competition, they could also win. Otherwise, they would only win one or two points, which was completely pointless because they would still need to win either the group arena or team competition. As a result, it was quite obvious how Team Samsara would approach this final match.

As for Team Blue Rain, if they wanted to win, they had to ensure that they didn’t lose every match in the individual competition. They also needed to sweep through the group arena and team competition. Their situation was rather grim. How Team Blue Rain’s players handled the immense pressure would be very important.

Glory’s competitive format using points was very fitting in the regular season. Because the winner would be decided on the total number of points obtained, each team would try their best to win every point in every match, so every match could be enjoyed. However, in the playoffs, where every match would be spectacular, the elimination formation made people worry not just about who won or lost.

For example, in the finals, Samsara had a huge lead. If Team Samsara actually swept through the individual competition and beat Team Blue Rain three to zero, the winner would already be decided. The following group arena and team competition didn’t need to be played.

Thus, there would instantly be two fewer confrontations. How could the Alliance bear that?

When the competitive scene was still beginning, no one cared too much about this issue. But now, every single confrontation was worth a lot of money. For a high-level match like the finals, two fewer matches was a significant loss, so the Alliance was thinking of changing the tournament format to keep the suspense going all the way through. However, they clearly hadn’t been able to come up with a satisfying answer this season, so the finals continued to use the old format. The streaming platform and the advertising companies had already specially asked for a condition: if the winner was decided in the individual competition or the group arena, the price that they paid would be drastically reduced. If the team competition needed to be played out to decide the winner, then they would pay the full price.

The Alliance couldn’t do anything about it because it wasn’t their first time encountering this awkward situation. Since it had happened before, how could the advertising companies and stream platforms ignore this? As a result, the two sides had put in clauses in their contracts specifically to counter these issues. And because of this reason, the Alliance finally decided that they needed to change the format. It affected their revenue!

They said this, but the competition still needed to be played, so everyone was worried. The streaming platform and advertising platforms may have come up with specific clauses to deal with this issue, they’d rather not have to save that chunk of money. Otherwise, why would they even bother spending money in the first place?

Amidst all of the clamor, the second round of the finals grew nearer and nearer. The stream had already switched to a view of the stadium. The individual competition would begin in ten minutes. The two sides had publicly announced their list of players before the match started. Right now, the commentator and guest were analyzing their possible arrangements. As soon as Team Samsara lost a round in the individual competition, the other two rounds could be considered as a waste of energy. If Team Samsara emphasized the individual competition and stacked their players there, if they couldn’t sweep through it, it would affect the group arena because players couldn’t play in both the individual and group arena competitions.

“So I think, Samsara will emphasize the group arena more. That is where the match will be decided.” The guest confidently stated.

“Your analysis is spot on! Then what do you think Team Blue Rain will do?” The commentator asked.

“Team Blue Rain is in a more difficult situation. They need to correctly guess Team Samsara’s possible arrangements. However, my guess on what Team Samsara would do is quite likely, so Team Blue Rain probably won’t invest too much into the individual competition either. They will also emphasize the group arena. However, they might still need to place one strong player into the individual competition for safe measure.” The guest speaker continued to analyze.

“Ha ha, do you think this strong player will be Yu Feng?” The commentator asked.

“Possibly!” The guest smiled, but his confident look said: yes, exactly.

In this tournament format, even though it was possible for a match to be decided early on, nothing was absolute. The strategic arrangement of which players to send out was something that was very important. An arrangement that countered the other side’s arrangement could be the deciding factor in a match.

Ten minutes of their chattering soon passed. The players sent out from the two teams came out and the individual competition started. The players were announced. For the away team, the first player to come out from Team Samsara was like a slap to the honored guest’s face.

Emphasize the group arena instead of trying to sweep through the individual competition?

He was wrong.

Samsara wanted to directly crush Blue Rain in the individual competition. Their ace player Zhou Zekai being announced for the individual competition was proof. A team’s ace player would usually be the anchor in the group arena. The ace player could win a large advantage in the group arena, but in the individual competition, the ace player would only be able to win one round at best.

Unexpectedly, Zhou Zekai was the first to come out in the individual competition. Samsara’s confidence and spirit could be seen from their arrangement.

The second player in the individual competition would be Lu Boyuan and his Grappler Chaotic Cloudy Mountain.

The third player was vice-captain Jiang Botao and his Spellblade Empty Waves.

Outsiders couldn’t be certain, but Team Samsara knew very well that these three characters were the three characters with maxed skill points. Cloud Piercer and Empty Waves were All Star level characters. Their equipment was mighty as well. As for Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, because of his skill points, his strength had improved a lot. Even though his equipment wasn’t outstanding in the competitive scene, the player Lu Boyuan was in his peak condition.

The character wasn’t everything. The player controlling the character was more important. A player’s outstanding performance could make up for a character’s lacking stats. Lu Boyuan was currently in his best condition, so Samsara naturally gave him the responsibility of winning.

When Samsara’s line-up came out, the commentator said a long “Oh”. Who knew what that meant. The guest’s expression paled. His analysis being off by a bit wasn’t anything. More importantly, he had been too confident. He wanted to go back in time. His requirements weren’t large, he just wanted to go back ten minutes…...

After being slapped in the face, the guest wasn’t able to say anything for a moment. Afterwards, Team Blue Rain’s line-up gave the honored guest light up a bit because Team Blue Rain had done what he analyzed.

Team Blue Rain didn’t dare invest too heavily into any one competition. They valued stability. They invested one strong character in the individual competition, which was Yu Feng. They obviously hoped he would be able to take one point, so they wouldn’t just lose before the group arena even started.

Now that the line-ups of the two teams had come out, everyone fell silent.

Team Samsara’s intentions were clear. Team Blue Rain’s line-up was at gun point.

Correct, gunpoint!

Glory’s Great Gunner, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer!

Yu Feng, who Team Blue Rain needed to win a point, was up against Team Samsara’s ace player, Zhou Zekai…...

Chapter 683: Crushed

Usually, in the Glory competitive scene, before the tournament ended, no one dared to speculate who would win. However, all of this changed when Zhou Zekai appeared during the playoffs. He left a deep impression that he was unbeatable.

Everything stemmed from his incredible performance in his matches. Zhou Zekai didn’t speak much out of stage, but he was someone who could speak with his actions.

Team Blue Rain’s original plan was to be on the defensive by sending out Yu Feng, they but didn't expect Yu Feng to be matched up with such a strong opponent. Although Yu Feng was an All Star level player, no one favored him at the moment.

Silence fell upon the stadium. The fans, who were cheering hard for their home team, suddenly stopped after seeing the matchups between the two teams. It was as if the whole place had become a funeral service.

“Coach Li? Coach Li?!” The commentator called out continuously to his partner Li Yibo, but he couldn’t get any response out from him. Li Yibo seemed to have lost his soul, when he saw the team line up.

To resume the pause in their commentating, the commentator called the absent-minded Li Yibo back to the conversation.

“Ah? Oh….” Li Yibo finally snapped out of his daze and hastily responded.

“This team line up, how interesting…” Li Yibo continued.

With the battle commencing soon, Li Yibo immediately began to analyze it: “Team Samsara has surprisingly come out with an extremely formidable arrangement. Zhou Zekai and Jing Botao are the two best players in Team Samsara without a doubt. Following behind them is Lu Boyuan. He can’t be considered as someone on their level, but his performance in the first round of the finals was very outstanding. So naturally he would be the third player to come out in this competition.”

“Does this mean that Team Samsara is determined to finish off Team Blue Rain in this individual competition?” the commentator asked.

Li Yibo laughed and displayed his usual confidence: “Ha ha… I have to admit that I ignored a huge advantage in this sort of arrangement.”

“Oh?”

“This arrangement, aside from attacking, can also be used for defending. With this arrangement, it is very likely that Team Samsara will win at least two rounds in this individual competition. With their current points, if Team Samsara can obtain the points for the following two battles, they would be in a situation, where they cannot lose. Even if Team Blue Rain managed to win the remaining competitions, their points would be tied 9.5 to 9.5 and there would be a need to fight another round to decide the winner. If we look at things from this perspective, their decision to go all out in this individual competition is an extremely strategic move!” Li Yibo explained.

“Your analysis is truly insightful!” The commentator praised. In the meantime, the first

Zhou Zekai VS Yu Feng.

Cloud Piercer VS Brilliant Edge.

Anxiety seeped into everyone’s hearts. Team Blue Rain’s safe guard had been thwarted by Team Samsara’s powerful line-up. Was this really a coincidence?

Taking advantage of the fact that both sides had yet to fight, Li Yibo quickly squeezed in a few more comments, “By placing Yu Feng in the first battle, Team Blue Rain was probably thinking of reducing the pressure on him. If he were placed in the third round and Team Blue Rain lost the first two battles, the pressure would be very great because his round would be the deciding round. As such, putting him in the first or second round is a fairly good choice. However, I think that this has exposed an important piece of information.”

“What is it?” The commentator asked.

“Team Blue Rain is putting hopes on Yu Feng to win the first battle. If he wins, he would have completed his mission and the following two contestants can relax. If that happens, they might even have a better chance at winning the match, provided that one of their other player wins their round, to avoid the possibility of a tie. So in my eyes, putting Yu Feng first is Team Blue Rain wanting to win two rounds of the individual competition. They don’t want to decide the win through a tie-breaker.” Li Yibo said.

“I see…” The commentator replied, “In any case, they’ve hit a brick wall. Now then, everyone. Let's focus on the match. Brilliant Edge is now closing in on Cloud Piercer and is within Cloud Piercer’s attack range. Will Zhou Zekai start attacking?”

“Oh, he didn’t. Both sides are still approaching each other as if they were both melee classes. Of course, Brilliant Edge is a Berserker, so close combat would be his main form of attacking, but Cloud Piercer isn't… He could have started attacking when he was 10 units away, but instead he’s closing in on his target.”

“Ah, the attacks have started! Fellow friends, now marks the start of the second match of the Season 8 Glory Pro Alliance Finals. The first round of the individual competition is between Zhou Zekai of Team Samsara versus Yu Feng of Team Blue Rain! The characters on the battlefield are Cloud Piercer and Brilliant Edge! Someone has finally made their first attack, but the attack wasn’t made by Cloud Piercer, who has the long range advantage, but Brilliant Edge! Even though Berserkers mainly use close-ranged attacks, those who are familiar with this class would know that they have several mid-range skills too. That's right, Sword Draw! It's a shared skill before the level 20 Swordsman job advancement!”

“Zhou Zekai didn't retreat. Instead, he used a Slide Kick. Cloud Piercer slid underneath Brilliant Edge and immediately counter attacked!”

“Head-on attack! To think Cloud Piercer would fight a Berserker in close combat…”

“Punisher… evaded… whirl kick, knee attack… hit! Wow, beautiful!! Cloud Piercer’s sequence of attacks was so quick! Yu Feng reacted fast, but in the end, he wasn’t able to dodge the chain of attacks….”

“Gatling Gun…”

“Wow, everyone look! Zhou Zekai is using Knee Attack and Gatling Gun to produce his own version of BBQ. Ha ha, the shared skill BBQ has a chance at being a grab and deals moderate damage too, so it’s a must-have skill for all gunners. Many players might even skill it up to a high level. However, those who are familiar with Cloud Piercer knows that he has only put in one point into the skill because Zhou Zekai only desires the grab chance. As for the damage or other effects, he can use Gatling Gun to produce the same effect!”

“Grenade! Oh, Mechanical Seeker was also thrown out! All of them are low leveled skills. Low leveled shared skill have short cool downs, so they are very important for continuing combos.”

“

“Wow, Random Firing!!”

“Brilliant Edge in midair is being attacked by Cloud Piercer’s Random Firing… He can't land because of his incredible execution of Delivery Gun… all of his attacks hit!!”

“Thunder Snipe! Headshot! Double damage!! While Brilliant Edge was tumbling in the air due to Random Firing, he managed to hit a headshot, dealing double damage. Zhou Zekai! This is Zhou Zekai and the Great Gunner, Cloud Piercer!!”

The commentator chattered excitedly as the battle continued. On the other hand, Li Yibo was depressed. At first, he had been preparing to explain the reason and purpose for why Zhou Zekai didn’t start the battle from a long-range, but the battle moved too fast for him to make a comment. Even so, the commentator was able to follow along smoothly as if he were reading a textbook.

In terms of speaking speed, the commentator was definitely faster than him.

The purpose of the guest was to use his professional insight and analytical skill to analyse the actions of the players, helping the audience understand the meaning behind their actions. Unfortunately, this time, the battle moved too fast and the commentator’s rapid talking didn’t give him any time to make a comment. When the attack on Yu Feng’s Brilliant Edge finished, he was still waiting to talk about the initial exchange….…

Good, he got the chance to speak out now. But would there be any meaning in explaining the previous attack now? How many people would still remember that?

Fine. None of that mattered now. He needed to show that he existed though. As soon as the commentator stopped to take a brief respite, he immediately followed up with his analysis:

“Under normal circumstances, Gunners will try to keep their distance and kite the enemy until they found a chance to follow up with some burst damage, But Zhou Zekai did the opposite. He started the fight by closing in on his opponent. Everyone saw what happened afterwards. He started a burst of attacks! A Sharpshooter winning in this sort of situation will certainly affect Yu Feng’s mentality. Sharpshooters have long-ranged attacks. Once Yu Feng’s Berserker was closed in on and lost the exchange, in order to escape, he would need to run very far. Everyone, look at how Yu Feng’s Berserker has pulled quite some distance away from Cloud Piercer, yet Cloud Piercer can still deal damage to him. There’s nothing he can do. That’s how far a Sharpshooter can shoot.”

“For Zhou Zekai to play like this, is he that confident in his ability to win? Even though Sharpshooters have close combat skills, they still can’t compare to an actual melee class, right?” The commentator voiced out his doubt.

“Of course.”Li Yibo nodded his head, feeling accomplished for having able to finish his explanation.

“Alright! After both sides exchanged attacks, Yu Feng's Brilliant Edge attempted to approach Cloud Piercer again, but…… this time, Zhou Zekai changed his mind. Instead of fighting with Yu Feng’s Brilliant Edge in close combat, he starts to use his range advantage to attack Brilliant Edge…..”

“Yu Feng might be in trouble this time…” Coach Li sighed.

He finally guessed correctly this time. In the first round of the individual competition, Yu Feng was completely crushed by Zhou Zekai.

Chapter 684: Champions

Brilliant Edge fell.

In front of Zhou Zekai, even an All Star player and character was thoroughly defeated. Yu Feng hadn’t made any obvious mistakes. It was simply because Zhou Zekai was better.

Such a brilliant performance was enough to move anyone. Usually, even if this was Team Samsara’s away game, even if Team Blue Rain’s fans made up the majority of the audience, such a splendid display would still win an explosive applause.

However, the entire stadium was silent.

Those who weren’t fans of Team Blue Rain held back their polite applause because this fight was too crucial. Team Blue Rain’s strategic arrangement was very obvious. Yu Feng had been sent out specifically to win them at least one round of the individual competition. With Yu Feng defeated handily, how would Team Blue Rain fare against Team Samsara’s remaining line-up?

Under this situation, how could any of Team Blue Rain’s fans cheer for their opponent’s beautiful performance?

The fans of Team Blue Rain looked at their two remaining players on the screen and their hearts fell. These two players couldn’t even be considered as part of Team Blue Rain’s main force. Team Blue Rain’s captain, Yu Wenzhou, rarely appeared in the individual competition. Xu Jingxi’s character was a Paladin. Even though Paladins excelled at defense, their offense was weak. Healers like Paladins rarely appeared in the individual competition or the group arena.

Thus, of the six main Team Blue Rain players used in the team competition, only four remained.

Yu Feng had been put in the individual competition as insurance. The remaining three would naturally be participating in the group arena. As for the individual competition, the other two players could only be considered as second-string substitute players.

And these two substitute players would be facing Samsara’s Lu Boyuan, who was at his peak condition, and Samsara’s vice-captain and All Star, Jiang Botao.

When the second round of the individual competition began, the fans were even somewhat distracted. The commentator and guest had talked for a while, before the audience refocused. They just remembered that this was when their team needed the most encouragement!

Everyone began cheering.

GLORY!!

This single word popped up on the big screen and the stadium once again fell into silence.

Lu Boyuan’s Grappler Chaotic Cloudy Mountain finished his opponent with a throw into the air. When his opponent crashed into the ground, his opponent was killed. Team Samsara now lead 2-0.

The third round of the individual competition suddenly became match point.

If Team Samsara won, they would directly be named the season eight champions. If Team Blue Rain won, they still had the possibility of winning. If they won both the upcoming group arena and team competition, they would catch up to Team Samsara. In the first match of the finals, Team Samsara had beaten Team Blue Rain in this third round. Originally, people thought that Team Blue Rain had the ability to fight tooth and tooth with Team Samsara, but now that the competition had reached this step, very few people favored Team Blue Rain.

Team Samsara’s following player was their vice-captain and All Star, Jiang Botao.

As for Team Blue rain? The player’s name was Lin Feng, a Thief. It’s said that top teams have no weak players, so even a second-string player like Lin Feng couldn’t be considered bad, but against a formidable adversary like Jiang Botao and his Spellblade, Empty Waves, it truly was difficult to compare the two.

“Lin Feng! You can do it!!!” This time, the fans of Team Blue Rain didn’t hesitate. It was their final chance. Thinking too much would be meaningless.

Would Lin Feng become Team Blue Rain’s saving grace?

The commentator and guest began a lengthy discussion. What pressure? What critical moment? The audience was starting to get angry hearing them speak. They knew that these two were speaking the truth, but their words only made them aggravated. The audience was cheering harder and harder. The commentator and guest were speaking into a mic, but their words were drowned out. Fortunately, the round soon began. The noise gradually lessened. Many of the nervous fans forgot to cheer.

Even the audience was feeling nervous from the pressure. What were the players feeling?

Lin Feng was a second-string player on Team Blue Rain. He probably never thought he would one day be the focal point in the finals. Victory seemed to be entirely in his hands. His opponent, Jiang Botao, didn’t receive as much attention. Most people clearly hoped the competition would continue and Team Samsara wouldn’t just win at this point.

Pressure!

As the focal point of this round, the commentator and guest analyzed how this pressure might affect each player.

As for Lin Feng?

He didn’t tremble because of the pressure, but he was still affected by the pressure. He played extremely carefully. He knew his loss would end their chance at becoming champions this season, so he always wanted to be in a strong position. Defense first and always pay attention to his retreat path.

Was that the correct choice?

No one could say. Winners were praised and the losers were vilified. If he won, people would say he was being calm and collected. If he lost, he would be criticized for being too conservative.

The guest Li Yibo was an experienced old fox. In the beginning, when he talked about Lin Feng’s playstyle, he just casually said a few surface words like an advisor who said nothing of importance. As the battle continued and he saw Jiang Botao seize the upperhand, Li Yibo began taking the side of whoever was winning and bravely spoke: “Tsk, Lin Feng is being too conservative! But I can understand where he’s coming from. He has too much of a burden on him. A second-string player like him rarely has to handle such pressure. Team Blue Rain originally tried to relieve this kind of pressure, so they sent Yu Feng out first. However, the heavy burden is now on Lin Feng’s shoulders.”

Li Yibo was originally a pro player and was now a famous commentator. Even though he would occasionally mutter something incomprehensible, not look at things thoroughly enough, say incorrect things, for Li Yibo to be sitting there right now, he had the matching ability. He could see that Lin Feng’s situation was not looking good.

Everyone’s hearts thumped loudly and wouldn’t relax.

This fight couldn’t be considered as great. There weren’t any flashy or intense moments. The audience as well as the commentator and guest were mainly focused on Lin Feng. In truth, Lin Feng’s opponent Jiang Botao was also playing this fight carefully. As long as he didn’t lose, they would be the champions. He was also under a lot of pressure.

There was a famous saying amongst the players called the nameless round in the finals.

Because in these crucial and decisive fights, most people would be very careful. They didn’t want to make any mistakes. Completely ignoring everything and playing with vigor required bravery and courage.

This third round of the individual competition definitely wouldn’t be a famous one.

Both players were playing very carefully, but Jiang Botao still had the advantage.

The pressure on him was less. His skill level and his character were higher than Lin Feng’s in the first place.

If Lin Feng wanted to win, he needed to play explosively and surpass himself. If he continued to carefully play without any sudden surprises or tricks, victory would go to whoever would win on paper.

In the end, Lin Feng’s Thief couldn’t hold on. When he was down to the last few hitpoints, Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves bravely attacked. Perhaps it was because the two had been fighting each other cautiously the entire time. Lin Feng had gotten used to this careful rhythm, so Jiang Botao’s courageous attack caused Lin Feng to stumble.

He originally wasn’t as good and now, he was panicked.

Jiang Botao quickly took advantage. His magic formations covered the field and the magic undulations from his attacks finally ended Lin Feng’s Thief.

Lin Feng wasn’t able to create a miracle. The word GLORY appeared on screen and Li Yibo sighed: “He was playing too passively!”

“How insightful……” The commentator said.

The match ended. In the individual competition, Team Samsara beat Team Blue Rain 3-0; With a total point tally of 10.5-2.5, the champion had been decided.

An early end to the finals had actually happened.

The majority of the stadium was silent. There were a few cheers and applause too though. Team Blue Rain’s home stadium wasn’t entirely made up of Team Blue Rain’s fans. Many of them were neutral and some were Team Samsara’s fans. The people, who were happily cheering, were Team Samsara’s fans. Only they wouldn’t mind an early end to the finals.

Because this meant that Team Samsara was that much more superior.

“If I’m remembering correctly, this is the first time in Glory history that a finals has ended early…..” The commentator said. He had obviously prepared this beforehand. With this being a possibility, he must have made preparations to say, when this possibility occurred.

“Yes, you’re right.” Li Yibo nodded his head: “This is the first time.”

“Let’s give our congratulations to Team Samsara for Glory’s season eight champions! This is also the fifth team in the Alliance to win a championship. There were previously four teams, which had won the championships before. One of them is Team Excellent Era, which won the first three championships in a row. Unfortunately, we won’t be seeing them next season.”

“Team Tyranny broke Team Excellent Era’s streak and became the season four champions. Those who are familiar with Team Tyranny back then would know that the person sitting next to me, Li Yibo, was one of Team Tyranny’s former members. He retired the summer after Team Tyranny won the championships.”

“Haha.” Li Yibo laughed in modesty.

“Team Tiny Herb made it into the finals three years in a row. They once had the opportunity to establish their own era. Unfortunately, they were usurped in season six by Team Blue Rain, who stopped them from becoming the champions three years in a row.”

“Now, let’s congratulate our season eight champions, Team Samsara!!!”

Chapter 685: Commemoration

After the commentator introduced the champions of each season, he pushed this season’s champions, Team Samsara, into the spotlight.

The players on Team Samsara were already celebrating amongst themselves as they walked onto the stage.

The award ceremony began directly after the match ended. For Samsara, the only flaw in this near perfect scene was that this wasn’t their home stadium, so the applause and cheers weren’t as loud. Team Blue Rain’s fans still gave a polite applause, but they couldn’t empathize with Team Samsara’s joy nor did they want to.

As a result, the congratulations for Team Samsara seemed subdued. This was also a form of respect towards the home stadium audience. Every time the champion was named in their away stadium, it would always be done in this way. The true celebration ceremony would take place, when they returned to their home city.

But no matter the situation, the award ceremony still needed to take place. At this moment in time, the stage didn’t belong to Team Blue Rain, but rather the entire Alliance. Team Samsara was the main character and the atmosphere on stage belonged to Team Samsara as well. No one would talk too much about Team Blue Rain’s loss. As for Team Blue Rain, they stood quietly off stage. They could choose to leave and rest, but all of Team Blue Rain stood neatly in order off the stage.

“Tsk tsk tsk tsk……” Ye Xiu felt very moved by this scene.

“It’s a good thing Yu Wenzhou replaced you as the team captain. Team Blue Rain’s changed so much. If you had been the one leading the team, eighty percent of the team would probably be standing together off stage, pointing their middle fingers at Team Samsara, no?” Ye Xiu said to Wei Chen.

“Tch……” Wei Chen replied weakly. Ye Xiu glanced at him and noticed that while Wei Chen’s expression appeared calm, he could tell that he wasn’t very happy. Wei Chen had come from Team Blue Rain, so he still favored one team in this confrontation. He obviously wouldn’t favor Team Samsara, even though they had spent twenty million RMB for his guide. He used to be Team Blue Rain’s former team captain. He used to be someone who cherished Team Blue Rain more than anyone else. Even if he wouldn’t admit it with his own mouth. Even if he said his reason for playing in Blue Brook Guild after retiring was just for the stat points. Even if he once lost to Yu Wenzhou and retired because of it.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything more. On stream, the Professional Alliance’s chairman Feng Xianjun marched vigorously on stage. He took the microphone and officially announced Team Samsara as the season eight champions of Glory to all of the audience as well as the stream.

Afterwards, every player in Team Samsara received specific rewards: a champion mouse and a champion keyboard. These were specially made with large gold letterings with the words Season 8 Champions. Because of the special meaning attached to these items, most wouldn’t sell these for money. Every Team Samsara player received one with excited expressions on their faces.

Afterwards, the championship cup was awarded to Team Samsara. Feng Xianjun personally handed it to Team Samsara’s Zhou Zekai.

This was an away game. Zhou Zekai was also a quiet person. The Team Blue Rain fans laughed a little, when they watched him hold up the championship cup into the air. Feng Xianjun appeared to be very kind and gentle. He seemed to be saying something to Zhou Zekai. These whispers wouldn’t be picked up by the stream. They only saw that Zhou Zekai was still nervously smiling, even when he was conferred the award by the chairman. He only said a few words as usual.

Or perhaps he knew that the audience wasn’t very interested in this scene, so he wanted to hurry past this step and save time.

The commentator and guest were in front of everyone though. They obviously didn’t need to share the same feelings as the home stadium. They laughed loudly and chatted happily. Seeing that the award ceremony was about to be over, Li Yibo humorously expressed: Perhaps it was because the majority of people in the home stadium wanted the home team to be the champions or perhaps it was because Zhou Zekai liked to win in away games so that there wouldn’t be too many moments, where he needed to speak.

“Ha ha, you’re right. If this was at their home stadium, I don’t think he’d be able to go off stage so easily. Who knows how many people would have forced him to say something.”

Even though the second round of the finals was short, it ended in a thorough manner. The streaming platforms and advertising companies might feel a bit dissatisfied, but there was no need to let the fans and audience know of that. The audience members, who bought tickets to watch this match, would also receive an appropriate compensation, but none of this was important.

The stream had already begun showing Team Samsara’s path to becoming champions starting from the regular season to the playoffs to the finals. A beautiful highlight montage was displayed. This had been prepared beforehand for both Team Samsara and Team Blue Rain. However, since Team Samsara had become champions, the only highlight montage shown would be Team Samsara’s.

“To think Team Samsara actually swept Team Blue Rain 3-0 in the individual competition. I don’t think many people could have predicted that would happen.” The commentator’s and honored guest’s work wasn’t overy et. The finals may have ended at the individual competition, but their schedule time slot still had a lot of time remaining. The commentator and guest could only find stuff to say until it was over. This wasn’t anything new to them, except this time, they needed to do so for a long period of time.

“Yes, Team Samsara was able to win because their players performed outstandingly, but don’t ignore the fact that the deciding factor for Team Samsara winning the individual competition was their strategic player arrangement……” Li Yibo had wanted to say this right after the finals ended, but at that time, there wasn’t any room for any analysis. Li Yibo waited for a long time and now he finally had the chance to reveal his insight.

“You’re right. I don’t think Team Blue Rain thought Team Samsara would be so bold and place so much importance on the individual competition.” The commentator said.

“The weakness that Team Blue Rain has in their potential line-ups for the individual competition and group arena must have affected Team Samsara’s decisiveness.” Li Yibo said.

“Oh?” The commentator was a bit puzzled, but he quickly understood and followed up: “You’re saying that Team Blue Rain’s captain, All Star, and Master Tactician, Yu Wenzhou, often don’tparticipate in the individual competition or the group arena. And we also know that their first-string players, who participate in these competitions, are often the ones that make up the six-player team in the team competition. The healer classes often don’t appear in the other events. This means that in Team Blue Rain, two of their six first-string players won’t appear in the individual competition or the group arena.”

“Thus, it is truly difficult for Team Blue Rain. They don’t have another strong player to participate in those two events. I don’t think any good player in the Alliance would want to only appear in the individual competition.” Li Yibo said.

“Yes. And no matter how good a player is, it isn’t possible for them to replace Yu Wenzhou or a healer like Xu Jingxi.

“In the end, Team Blue Rain suffered because of the competitive format!” Li Yibo said.

“It seems like Team Blue Rain needs to find some way to deal with this problem.” The commentator said.

“Do they need to though?” Li Yibo smiled.

“They don’t?” The commentator was puzzled. Isn’t that what you were saying? Is that not what you mean? However, seeing Li Yibo’s smile, he suddenly realized: “Oh, I heard that next season, the playoffs format will be changing.”

“Yes, even though we don’t know what it is exactly yet, but they’ve been working on it for a year now. I think that’s enough time for the Alliance to think up a good format that will keep the playoffs competitive and suspenseful.” Li Yibo said.

“But the competitive format in the regular season won’t change, right?” The commentator said.

“Ha ha, this isn’t a problem for Team Blue Rain in the regular season. Their standings in the regular season is more than enough to prove it.” Li Yibo said.

“That’s true. Team Blue Rain led the regular season the entire time. They came into the playoffs as number one in the regular season.”

“Ha ha, this time’s finals might have been short, but I feel like it’s enough to call it a match that will be remembered.” Li Yibo said.

“Yes. After all, it’s the first time a finals has finished early.” The commentator said, “And with the change in format next year, it’ll be the last time as well.”

“And this time, it showed the importance of strategy in arranging which players to send out for which competition. Team Samsara relied on their bravery and drive to beat Team Blue Rain. I think this is a perfect commemoration for the last time this competitive format will be used.” Li Yibo said.

“You’re all too right.”

It has to be said that Li Yibo was truly experienced in this line of work now. A finals, which had ended early, lost a lot of potential revenue, and disappointed countless people, was described as a finals to be remembered. His analysis and reasoning for it was completely sound too.

“I believe that this year’s finals will remain as a match to be remembered for years to come, especially for those out there, who have been watching the Alliance since the beginning. It will certainly be a lasting memory.” The commentator gave a brief summary. And at this moment, the break given to the two teams was over and the press conference began. The stream switched over to the press conference.

Even though Team Samsara had displayed a dominating victory, off stage, Zhou Zekai was as taciturn as ever. It was too hard to hate him though. Team Blue Rain didn’t forget themselves either. As the losers, Yu Wenzhou had to give his apologies. He never covered up his weaknesses and blamed his own weakness for giving trouble to the team. Li Yibo’s analysis was reasonable. Yu Wenzhou talked about this issue a lot.

Team Blue rain’s ace player, Huang Shaotian, didn't have an opportunity to appear on stage today. His gloominess could clearly be seen on him. When the reporters asked if he wanted to say something, he rolled his eyes and gave a response that others found hard to believe that it came from his mouth.

“I don’t want to say anything.” Huang Shaotian said.

Chapter 686: Happy While Suffering

Huang Shaotian said he doesn’t want to say anything!

The reporters were immediately excited. What a powerful way to express his emotions! If it had been someone else, he or she would have to use an immeasurable amount of words, expression, and even tears to express how sad and disappointed they were at the result. Huang Shaotian just needed one sentence, “I don’t want to say anything.”

This was a true instance of “ silence spoke for itself.” Many reporters had already decided that tomorrow’s reports were going to be mostly revolving around this sentence of Huang Shaotian. Indeed, when even Huang Shaotian had no words to say towards this defeat, was there a need to describe how angry and disappointed Team Blue Rain felt towards this match?

On the other hand, the intensity of Team Blue Rain’s emotions only illustrated the brilliance of Team Samsara’s victory.

This was the first final match in eight seasons to end early. Yes, this result may disappoint many, but to the reporters who were writing the reports afterward, this made a very good topic. Although the topic was good, because the match ended early, there wasn’t much material for the reporters to work with. Therefore, they had to dig deeper into the inner emotional world of the players.

No matter what, the focus would still be on the final champions: Team Samsara. In that moment, any reaction from Team Blue Rain would only be used to emphasize the strength of Team Samsara.

Of course, some Team Blue Rain fans among the reporters might draft up reports that favored Team Blue Rain and pointed out their merit. Even if these kind of drafts were accepted, they would only appear in some unnoticeable corner.

This was how the competitive scene worked.

The halos of glory would only be bestowed upon the victor. Second place? Silver medal? They sounded like good results, and they did acknowledge these teams’ strength. However, they would never be seen as a glory. In fact, because of the glory showered upon the victors, the mark of the losers only seemed more noticeable on these teams.

Team Hundred Blossom is a good example of this. They had lost three finals. Did anyone mention that Team Hundred Blossom was the second best team that beat many of the top teams? No. Their three second-places were often mentioned as a joke. They were the pitiful sacrifices to the glory of the victors. They looked even worse than the no-good teams that became cheerleaders after finishing the regular season without getting relegated or getting into playoffs. .

The competitive scene was cruel in this way. No wonder the media was so easily swayed. No wonder that they approached Team Blue Rain with wicked intentions during the press conference.

Nonetheless, Yu Wenzhou took over all the responsibilities. After Huang Shaotian’s “I don’t want to say anything.”, the reporters threw out more questions. Facing the media’s attempt to dig deeper, Yu Wenzhou smiled, “Even Shaotian doesn’t want to say anything, what is there for us to say?”

This...

While the reporters were still spacing out, the Team Blue Rain team members had gotten up and quietly left under the lead of their team captain.

After their thoughts ran off wildly in every directions, the reporters quickly pulled their thoughts back and surged forward with their equipments like cheetahs towards the main characters of today: the champions, Team Samsara.

The final was an away match for Team Samsara. After they attended all of the necessary events, Team Samsara only celebrated a little bit. The next day, when they returned to City S, their homebase, their club already had a huge celebration in place. Thousands of fan crowded the Club’s stadium to welcome their heroes’ return.

Champagne, flowers...

To Team Samsara and its fans, this day was indeed a very happy day.

Their team captain and ace player, Zhou Zekai, finally welcomed his personal final coronation after winning the championship. All throughout the regular season, playoffs, even the finals, his performance was unquestionably worth of all the glory he received.

In the eyes of the fans, he could do everything besides heal.

In the eyes of his teammates, he was undoubtedly reliable and victorious.

In the eyes of the League and sponsors, he was the grandest source of money. He had unmatched popularity and handsome looks. The only problem he had was his shy personality and the fact that he didn’t speak much. However, that was no big matter. Even if he didn’t say much, there were more than enough ways to package a star. With his looks, it was easy enough to make the fangirls scream at posters for awhile.

His value as a player and in the advertising field had both reached a peak. This was an achievement that no one had done before.

Ye Qiu’s competitive success was still an unreachable summit, but his commercial value had always being non existent. Although the other God-level players did not reject commercial activities as much as Ye Qiu did, none of them had reached a height like Zhou Zekai had.

The title of number one in the Alliance became his from this day on. During the entire summer, Team Samsara and Zhou Zekai would be sought after by many.

On the night when the champions were decided, war erupted out in the game. At least this time it was no longer a world war. It was just between Blue Brook Guild and Samsara. The fans and guilds of the other teams took to the sidelines the moment that the war started. Although there were a few fans that ended up on one side or the other, the guilds would never let themselves be involved in such meaningless fights. After the champions were announced, no one bothered to argue over the events that took place during the knockout stage before the playoff. All the fights and arguments were coming from the two teams that made it to the finals. Therefore, the other clubs enjoyed the show quite happily.

As for the start of this war, the reason behind it was no longer findable. No one know if it was the continuation of the previous wars or if there had being something new. But everyone knew that it had to do with Team Samsara’s strong performance and the fact that they beat Team Blue Rain during the individual match.

On the battlefield, Team Samsara was indeed very strong. However, Team Samsara’s style was just like their ace Zhou Zekai. Although they were rather forceful on stage , but down in front of the press, they still used words like “the opponents performed well. We were just better.”, just like most professional teams would do. As the old saying goes, ‘No arrogance in victory, no despair in defeat!”

As for Team Blue Rain , no matter what Team Samsara’s reaction was about the victory, they would still respond respectfully and not belittle Team Samsara in the slightest. This was also Team Blue Rain’s manner.

Unfortunately, teams were teams; fans were fans.

A team would act as a whole. The members would help each other out, move together, and take the same stance. The fans wouldn’t. Their numbers were too big. Despite being bonded together by their shared love for the same team, to say that they would all coexist peacefully was still ridiculous.

Therefore, after the results were released, many people jumped out.

On Team Samsara's side, most of those troublemakers surfaced to show off. On Team Blue Rain’s side, there were quite a number of people who shouted out for no reason. It was simply because they could not stand the crushing defeat.

The finals had ended, but the battles in the game were just beginning. With the help of certain individuals, the flames of war easily ravaged across the whole server. Although there were many logical people like the team members among the fans, but who would listen to reason amidst such chaotic times? On top of that, facing those who had trashed Team Blue Rain to the ground and praised Team Samsara into the sky just because the match ended early, even the logical people would feel the rage roaring within.

Despite the efforts of the two Club guilds, the fans of those two teams still waged a war of their own. After all, fans are fans. The words of the guilds, teams, and even players only hold so much weight. There was no way for the fans to carry out the will of the club perfectly. All that the Clubs could do was suggest, advise, and hope.

If others won’t listen, what could you possibly do? Hurry up and grab as much toilet paper as you can hold to wipe the asses of your own fans!

When the war erupted, the two guilds of the two Clubs got involved forcibly. If they just let their fans do whatever they liked and ended up causing their fans to blame themselves, that would truly be a headache to deal with.

There was no time for the two Clubs to take a breather. As loving as they were for their fans, they kept on emphasizing that they needed to stay logical, they needed to face the results maturely, and that was just how competitions were like. However, all their efforts were ignored. Even the Clubs could not trash talk themselves while praising others. There was simply no way for Team Samsara to say. “Exactly! Team Blue Rain is garbage. We should not be wasting our time on such trash!” Following the same logic, Team Blue Rain could not possibly say that, “Screw it! Team Samsara is just a group of bastards who stole our victory! However, as civilized people, we should not be arguing with those bastards!”

As a result, both ended up saying that there is always a victor and a loser in any match and we should respect our opponents. Unfortunately, such words were uttered by every team after every match. Everyone got tired of them a long time ago. Such pleading had no effect to speak of. Even those really moving speeches might stop some players, but it would not stop all. The flames of conflict would not be put out so easily. These kinds of wars were waged after every finals. This year’s was just more intense because Team Samsara ended the match early.

The excitement was expectedly high for this first time championship victory . On top of it, Team Samsara won by a landslide. No matter who it was, the fans all wanted to show off somewhat.

Overall, it was still because Glory was different than any other sports. Because it was based in a game, it gave its fans the room to vent.

If it had been any other sports, after the results are out, all the fans could do was just have some verbal arguments. Even if actual conflicts were to take place, it was still be relatively of small, since even if they wanted to make things bigger, they would have to organize everything. In addition, there was public security to prevent such occurrences.

Glory was another thing altogether. The Heavenly Domain gathered all the fans in the same place and let them carry out their conflicts the most direct way. Without any rules to abide by, the battle escalated without limits. Even if you lost all your equipment, you can’t take revenge by calling the police.

This kind of war obviously harmed the guilds.Samsara was slightly better since their team won the finals. They saw the losses as sacrifices for the championship victory. In a way, they were happy while suffering. Blue Brook Guild had gotten themselves into a total tragedy. They didn’t win the finals and still had to pay for the satisfactions of their own fans. As of now, tears were streaming down the cheeks of Blue Brook Guild’s guild master Changing Spring: Who did I offend?

Chapter 687: Scrap Pick Transporter

Samsara celebrated without restraint.

In the early days of Glory, champions like Team Samsara could log into the game and interact personally with their fans. However, in these recent years, the competition had become fiercer, and this type of activity had already died away. The game was equal to everyone. If pro characters like Cloud Piercer or Empty Waves appeared, would they be able to parade on the streets? The fans of the other teams would help them celebrate by gifting them with their flashy attacks…..

There was only killing in the game. Even celebrating looked the same. It was currently the weekends, right now, so there were more players online than in the weekdays. Even though only two guilds were fighting, it seemed even more intense than in the past.

The fans might be fighting fiercely, but the guilds exercised restraint. They knew that this time, the other guilds would definitely be watching the battle from the sidelines. They had to preserve as much of their strength as they could because this battle could only result in losses. There was no winner or loser in this battle.

Blue Brook Guild was stronger than Samsara, but it wasn’t by so much that Blue Brook Guild would be able to wipe Samsara out.

In particular, for Club guilds, the word “wipe” couldn’t really be used. As long as the team still existed in the pro scene, the guild would survive. If the team left the pro scene, you wouldn’t need to actively try and wipe out that guild; it would quickly fade away on its own. These kinds of occurrences had happened before in the past.

The two guilds carefully moved about. They had a tacit agreement not to let their elite forces collide. Thus, the war this time appeared less real. Ye Xiu’s group was originally going to run around scrap picking, but when Ye Xiu heard Wei Chen describe the situation, he immediately lost interest.

。

If the elite forces would avoid direct conflicts with each other, wouldn’t they just be going around bullying normal players and showing off their might? Both guilds were very well aware that they needed to participate in this war. The two guilds wouldn’t be provoked by their surroundings. The core of the guilds were professionals. They would calmly survey the situation to see how they could win just like the pro players.

Of course, this was only limited to the core circle. Whether it was the main guild or the branch guilds, the vast majority of players were purely fans, who could be rational or impulsive. Some would listen to the guild’s advice, while some thought right now was the time to stand out.

The guild couldn’t care about everyone. In any case, the elite members strictly followed orders. In addition, they tried to avoid putting in as much resources as possible. As a result, they did a good job preserving their strength.

In reality, even the non-elite players still had fairly good equipment. After all, they were all members of Club guilds. Even if they weren’t able to buy or obtain the items that they wanted from dungeons or marketplaces, they could still obtain them by contributing to the guild and trading contribution points for items in the guild storage. Club guilds were able to keep so many players together, relying on this method.

However, Ye Xiu’s group was only focused on picking up items dropped by the elite teams. The equipment dropped from these elite members were all top equipment in the game. Picking up second-rate or third-rate equipment felt meaningless to them now.

But then again, wasn’t getting equipment this way faster than running dungeons? Wasn’t the equipment for the guild storage? In the end, Ye Xiu’s group still went scrap picking. It wasn’t like they had anything else to do. Normal players would try and get their equipment properly through dungeons, but like Wei Chen said: Think of your status! You’re going to stoop to their level and do the same? Why not just buy or steal?

In the past, running dungeons could be considered as practice for Tang Rou and Steamed Bun to get used to controlling their characters. However, half a year had passed. The two of them had grasped the basics a long time ago. Running dungeons wasn’t very meaningful to them anymore. Even though they could still do some training through the dungeons, these past few years, the pro scene had already developed more efficient and specialized training methods. They had their own programs that allowed them to create all sorts of simulations. The technology department of the various Clubs weren’t just for creating equipment. They were involved in a lot of projects.

Many of these training methods were secrets of the Clubs. Those that could be downloaded publicly certainly wouldn’t be these. Even though Ye xiu was very familiar with the training methods that Team Excellent Era had, the problem was getting or creating the programs used for these training methods. How could he know about any of that? Team Excellent Era wasn’t going to provide those programs for him, so he didn’t have any.

Team Happy didn’t only lack talented players. Compared to the Clubs, they were still at a very crude level. If all a team needed was a practice room, it would be the same as eight years ago, when a few players could just register and join the pro scene.

If even the Club guilds needed to be personally managed by the pro players, how could the Glory Alliance have grown this big? Any established team nowadays had strong funding backing them. How could they resort to scrap picking for equipment? Just look at Loulan Slash did things. He just needed to throw his money and sweep the market.

Thinking about this made Chen Guo feel a little sad.

Did Ye Xiu like to go scrap picking? No, of course not. He just didn’t have any other choice. Chen Guo didn’t like this method, but it’s not like she had a ton of money either. If she didn’t let him go scrap picking, how would they get a huge amount of equipment? How would they establish their guild storage?

Sayings like “There’s always another way” or “As long you try hard” were all nonsense. Chen Guo wasn’t a little kid. She wasn’t so innocent. There are many things in this world that can’t be accomplished through hard work alone. There were 20 teams in the Alliance. Which team wasn’t trying hard? There was only one champion every season though.

Chen Guo had enough money to buy some equipment and the money Wei Chen earned from the skill points guide could be used to develop the team too. Their current capital would have been considered exceptional eight years ago, but this wasn’t eight years ago. The scene had developed rapidly during these eight years. Their capital wasn’t considered much in the Pro Alliance nowadays. They were still at the level, where they needed to split a bill in half before using it.

As a result, even if she looked down on scrap picking, she didn’t raise any objections. She even went along with them to pick up scraps. If a God like Ye Xiu was going to stoop so low, she didn’t have any excuses.

However, Ye Xiu refused because her skill level was too low. “Are you planning on picking up their equipment or having them pick up your equipment?” His honesty made her furious.

Without any other choice, Chen Guo could only be a transporter. Ye Xiu’s group was too efficient. The war this time was even more intense. There was equipment everywhere. The three went back and forth. Their storehouses were about to be full. Chen Guo immediately grabbed their alternate accounts and used those as storages. After thinking things from a long-term perspective, she ordered another set of Heavenly Domain accounts. She listened to Ye Xiu’s advice and got one of each class.

Today, their work didn’t seem like scrap pickers, but transporters. They had to save some energy to defend themselves, when scrap picking in the elite battles. But now that they were scrap picking with normal players, they didn’t need to use as much effort. They went about round and round. Even Loulan Slash’s eyes were red, when he heard of it. But no matter how red his eyes were, he wouldn’t go and scrap pick. Around three months later, he would be standing on the pro stage. Loulan Slash was looking forward to this very much. He clearly looked down on taking advantage of this situation to scrap pick.

But seeing how God Ye Qiu was scrap picking so calmly, Loulan Slash could only feel inferior: a God really is a God. He’s so high-profile in anything he does. This scrap picking….. f*ck, he’s going back to the city. Is his inventory full already?

Because it was the weekend, the wild bosses this week had all spawned. The four guilds in the alliance had benefited greatly. As a whole, it was the biggest harvest in history. The big guilds usually competed for these wild bosses exchanging wins. No single guild had ever monopolized so many bosses in a single week! After killing all of these wild bosses this week, each party in the alliance looked at their accounts. They discovered that even though they split each boss five ways every time, because they killed so many bosses, their profits surpassed the amount a big guild usually got.

This alliance is too amazing!

Each party in the alliance praised. Although the big guilds hadn’t participated in the competition for most of the wild bosses this week, their future looked sound. Even if their harvest decreased in the future, they definitely hadn’t lost out this week. Just think, if they didn’t have such an alliance and they took advantage while the big guilds were fighting to get a few wild bosses, it would just be the small Club guilds competing with each other instead of the big guilds. No one had a monopoly. In the end, the drops would have been split between numerous guilds. Their harvest then certainly wouldn’t be as good as their current harvest.

This satisfying result made these guilds hopeful for the future. They wanted Monday to hurry up and come, so they could begin killing next week’s wild bosses. They understood the importance of God Ye Qiu in this alliance and placed great importance on what God Ye Qiu asked for them to do. Loulan Slash was currently watching the two big guilds fight it out. He noticed Lord Grim’s group nimbly entering the battle, run around, and run out slowly. The weight in their inventory must definitely be slowing down their feet. Soon afterwards, he received a message from his guild: Deception has been seen.

Yes. This was what Loulan Slash and the others were helping God Ye Qiu do. When Loulan Slash received this news, the other three guild leaders, Yue Ziqin, White Stream, and Martial Awareness also received this message. Just like Loulan Slash, they cared very much about this task!

As a result, Ye Xiu quickly received the news from the four guild leaders: Deception is on.

“Ah!” Ye Xiu hastily called out to Chen Guo: “Hurry up and take this load off me!!”

Take this load off me…… was he really regarding scrap picking as transporting? Chen Guo silently cursed as her character went over. She also asked: “Is there something that came up?”

“That’s guy’s on again.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 688: Coming and Going

Chen Guo knew who they were talking about. She had interacted with and learnt from Deception, so she knew he was very skilled. Of course, Chen Guo welcomed skilled players, so when she heard that he was online, she quickly logged onto her account to take the load off Ye Xiu.

“Where are you all? Chen Guo asked as she hastily turned on two more computers. She was planning to log on and unload the goods of the three characters at once. She knew that the movement speed was crucial when dealing with Deception. Every time these three went out for scrap picking, their movement speed would always be hugely affected by their heavy inventories, which wouldn’t be enough to deal with Deception.

“Unload mine first, then unload those two. Opening three computers at once…… it’s not like you can use Shadow Dance.” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo ignored him as she quickly logged onto Chasing Haze and rushed to Lord Grim’s position and traded away everything on Lord Grim.

“Alright, I’ll leave first.” Ye Xiu said before running off. Lord Grim’s features were no longer unbalanced. After these past several days of fruitful labor, he naturally had high-end equipments he could use instead, even if Ye Xiu didn't change his principle of prioritising the equipment’s stats over the physical appearance. However, his random matching of clothing was more civilised this time and it didn’t look as absurd and ridiculous as before.

After asking Loulan Slash about Deception’s current whereabouts, Ye Xiu was a little gloomy. Judging from the information he received from the allied guilds, the direction Deception was sprinting towards might be the teleport formation . Once he teleported, who would know which city he would head towards? Furthermore, there was still a distance between Lord Grim’s current position and the teleport formation. It would be impossible rush there and kill Deception before he teleported, no matter what method he used.

“Can you send someone to stall him?” Ye Xiu asked the four guild leaders.

“About this, I’m afraid we won’t make it in time……” The four guild leaders had also determined Deception’s direction judging from the reports they were given. They wouldn’t be able to arrange enough people to stop him before he reached the portal.

“Sigh……” Ye Xiu felt regretful. Just when an opportunity came, that guy still managed to escape. Ye Xiu only focused on the places good for scrap picking and neglected the matter that Deception might try and teleport the moment he logged on.

“I won’t make it in time, too, sigh.”

“Don’t worry, God. Once my message is out, no matter where that guy teleports to, as long as he’s seen by our people, we’ll know at once.” All four guild leaders replied.

“That would be great!” Ye Xiu was relieved. There was strength in having a number of people!

As he was thinking, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim run towards the teleportation portal. He prepared to immediately pursue Deception the next time Deception was discovered. At least this guy was online. Based on the foundation of the four guild’s players, it might be possible to run into him.

Lord Grim only travelled for a short distance before all information on Deception was lost. Deception’s movement speed was too quick. Normal players weren’t able to keep track of him for a long time.

While he was still on his way, he soon received another message. It came from Yue Ziqin of Conquering Clouds. Someone in their guild had noticed Deception.

“Where?” Ye Xiu hastily asked.

“Oak City.” Yue Ziqin replied.

Oak City!

Ye Xiu was startled. What a coincidence!

Oak City was currently the closest city to Lord Grim. In this way, he didn’t even have to go to the teleport formation. Why did Deception coincidentally choose to go there out of all places?

After a brief moment of thinking, Ye Xiu immediately understood. Deception targeted here because this place was the main battlefield of Blue Brook Guild’s first and second elite groups. It didn’t matter whether you were in a group. It was hard to be in their league. Even fans of Blue Brook Guild would consciously avoid going here. After all, the maximum limit of a group was a hundred players. Players that went over the limit wouldn’t receive damage exemption. Fans of Blue Brook Guild were worried that they would be killed under the valiant bombarding of their own guild’s elite group, instead of their opponents’ attacks.

Such a place was undoubtedly an excellent place for scrap picking. Ye Xiu’s group came here to scrap pick, so it was natural that a scrap picking veteran like Deception would also make such a judgement. However, the way Deception rushed there the moment he logged on made Ye Xiu remember Deception’s situation during his first encounter with him. Ye Xiu was now even more certain that this guy had alternate accounts. Even though Deception wasn’t on these past few days, that didn’t mean his alternate accounts were idle.

However, Deception finally appeared again, so it was a given to keep an eye on him and give him a lesson.

After knowing where Deception was headed, Ye Xiu immediately made a rough prediction of his route. Yue Ziqin also continued to update Ye Xiu with more information. Ye Xiu saw the direction Deception was advancing towards and confirmed his prediction. Deception was definitely headed his way.

“He’s saved us a lot of trouble!” Ye Xiu was excited. Lord Grim ran back and waited. Why would he be in a hurry to run into him? It’d be better to give Tang Rou and Steamed Bun a chance to unpack and guard the revival point.

Because Lord Grim had emptied his inventory, Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion couldn’t keep up with his pace. They were currently struggling to transport their items. Chen Guo had just switched accounts to trade with the two, but before she could meet with them, Deception actually arrived first.

Deception’s movement speed was too quick. The players of Conquering Clouds soon lost track of him. However, Ye Xiu was confident. He was certain Deception would pass by here.

“I need to find a place to hide.” Ye Xiu checked his surroundings. He wasn’t planning to mount a sneak attack. He was just afraid that Deception might see him from the distance and take another path. Wouldn’t it be troublesome if he had to pursue him all over again? After looking around, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim hide behind a tree. He would reveal his head to peek out from time to time.

“Oh, Loulan you’re also here……” Ye Xiu didn’t see Deception, but he caught a glimpse of Loulan Slash.

“Ah…… yeah……” Loulan Slash originally came here to watch the scrap picking. After the three finished scrap picking and ran off, he also left. Then, he received the new information partway through, so he wanted to follow Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim to watch the fun. In the end, he just saw Lord Grim hiding on the side of the road, preparing to mount a sneak attack…..

If it were someone else, a sneak attack would be normal. However, Ye Qiu was a God, Loulan couldn’t bear the fact that even he needed to ambush a player. He sympathised with Deception. He wouldn’t think that he would have been caught by God.

“Oh, I was just passing by, passing by.” Loulan Slash said.

“Oh? Are you here to scrap pick as well?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Ah…… No, I‘m just walking around……” Loulan Slash said. He wouldn’t stoop so low as to scrap pick, but since God was scrap picking, he obviously couldn’t reveal his disdain towards scrap picking, so he explained his actions in this way.

“Oh oh, if you have nothing to do, then why don’t you help us? Steamed Bun and Soft Mist are in the back. They’re really slow because of their heavy inventories. Since we have business to do, why don’t you help us carry these items back! Help share some of the burden.” Ye Xiu said.

This was an effortless favour. How could Loulan Slash say no? But the problem was…… he was a great guild leader! He would soon be the captain of a pro team and the team’s boss. Now he had to do this? What was this? This was lower than scrap picking! He needed to help a scrap picker transport goods…… Loulan Slash felt that he should have said he was scrap picking and was going back from a successful run!

Even though Loulan Slash thought of this in his mind, he still did the favor. He just felt regretful because he wouldn’t be able to witness the scene of a God ambushing someone.

Even though Deception’s movement speed was quick, he was quite far away, so Tang Rou and Steamed Bun arrived first.

“Hey, boss!” Steamed Bun greeted warmly.

“Hm? Loulan Slash helped you transport the goods, right?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Yeah! That guy could carry a lot!” Steamed Bun sighed.

“Of course, he’s a Berserker, so his strength growth is very high. His equipment also has a lot of strength increases too.” Ye Xiu said.

“I don’t think my strength is inferior to anyone’s.” Steamed Bun spoke.

“I was referring to the strength stat in the game……” Ye Xiu said.

“What a pity. If I had strength that high, I could move a lot of things.” Steamed Bun said.

“When our equipment improves in the future, you’ll have lots of it…..” Ye Xiu said. Even though Brawlers mainly dealt physical damage, very few emphasized strength. Brawler’s skills had a lot of additional effects. In order to strengthen these effects, spirit was essential. As for the specifics, that depended on the person. It was like how a Battle Mage chose between strength and intelligence. The current, most players emphasized strength and put spirit as their secondary stat. However, high-end players usually found their own specific stat allocations to match their styles. As for Steamed Bun…… for such a crazy guy like him, could he care about these details?

Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t go anywhere after that. Deception dashed this way the moment he logged on and didn’t switch accounts either. After reviving, he would return to the main city. It was too far to have the two go and guard the revival part. Besides, Ye Xiu reckoned that Deception was smart. He would probably log off as soon as he died and wouldn’t revive again.

The three hid and waited. Soon, Deception could be seen. He was moving very fast towards them.

“Let me jump out and scare him.” Steamed Bun was eager to give it a try.

“Don’t kill him too fast, I need to ask him some questions!” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh……” Tang Rou answered.

The three waited. They originally thought that Deception would appear now. All three were straining their ears to hear his footsteps, but none of them could hear anything. Ye Xiu felt that this wasn’t normal. He poked his head out to look, but Deception had disappeared.

“Huh? Where’d he go?” Ye Xiu said.

“Did he see your head sticking out?” Chen Guo was very concerned about this matter.

“Impossible.” Ye Xiu overruled the idea firmly. He knew how the game worked very well. Judging from the distance between them, it was impossible for Deception to see half of his head from behind the tree.

Ye Xiu turned around to look at Steamed Bun Invasion and wondered if Steamed Bun had left any traces behind. But when he turned around to have a look, Steamed Bun was well-behaved as he hid there!

“That’s strange. I’ll go out and have a look.” Ye Xiu had no other choices. Had Deception logged off again?

Chapter 689: Here to Ambush

The three came out from their hiding place. They looked around, but didn’t see any signs of Deception.

“Let’s go over and take a look.” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim walked forward. Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion followed covering his left and right.

“Maybe he went to use the restroom?” Steamed Bun guessed. Even though it would be another escape, it really was a possibility.

“In any case, he logged off here, no? Should we stay here and camp this place then?” Tang Rou asked.

Steamed Bun had experience in other games. Tang Rou couldn’t really be considered a noob anymore. She began playing Glory in December of last year. It was now June, so half a year had passed. Games were usually pretty easy to get into, but difficult to master. Glory was the same. Otherwise, there would be no difference in skill levels between pro players and normal players.

Tang Rou had played for six months already. She spent most of her time in the game too. If she were still a noob after all that time, she’d be laughed at to death. It just took a long time to level up in Glory. In half a year, most players wouldn’t be able to enter the Heavenly Domain. From this perspective, the Heavenly Domain players might think people, who had only played for a half a year, were still beginners, but Tang Rou clearly didn’t belong in this category. Her skill level had already been enough to crush most normal players before she had even started playing the game. It was mainly her lack of knowledge and game sense that made her a noob. Now that half a year had passed, how could she not have more knowledge and game sense compared to before?

“Waiting won’t do…..” Ye Xiu said. They were just three people. If they were going to wait, they couldn’t be the ones doing it. Should he allow the big guilds to continue helping him?

Just when Ye Xiu was thinking about this, he saw something flash. He immediately turned his camera and saw Deception jump out from who knows where. Deception quickly formed a seal, which Ye Xiu recognized as Shadow Dance, but he was a bit at a loss: why did this guy suddenly take the initiative to attack them? Was his brain broken?

Around ten shadow clones pounced towards them. Ye Xiu could tell that this was an attack. What trump card had Deception grasped? He clearly saw all three of them, yet he actually dared to attack?

Ye Xiu didn’t understand, but Deception had already arrived. How could he be polite? He swiped his mouse and his cursor hovered accurately on a shadow clone. With a beautiful swing, Lord Grim switched his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella into its spear form, which pierced through a clone. Then, he switched forms again, changing it into its gun form. He leapt backwards, while firing. The same time that the shadow clone was hit, Lord Grim quickly Aerial Fired backwards and escaped from the encirclement of shadow clones.

“Retreat first.” Ye Xiu said to Tang Rou and Steamed Bun. Deception’s unusual boldness puzzled Ye Xiu. Unable to predict what strange method Deception had in store, it was best to be on the cautious side.

Tang Rou and Steamed Bun wanted to retreat, but they weren’t able to do so as easily as Ye Xiu could. Ye Xiu just looked like he had killed the nearest shadow clones and then leapt back with an Aerial Fire. But in reality, he had looked around to clearly see where every shadow clone was arranged to see the focal point of Deception’s attack and to figure out the most optimal direction to break out of the encirclement. Most normal players wouldn’t have the awareness to do all of that.

When Tang Rou and Steamed Bun tried to retreat, they did it in a more forceful manner. They weren’t being completely brainless though. They each took off in opposite directions. This way, unless Deception could push both of them back to their original spots, if the two rushed forward, he wouldn’t be able to deal with both sides. Shadow Dance had a limited range!

When Ye Xiu looked at the situation, he knew that if Deception wanted to have both of them stay within Shadow Dance’s range, it wasn’t going to be a possibility.

Tang Rou was so fierce!

Her spear danced about with light, dark, fire, ice, and neutral chasers circling behind her. Deception threw all of his shadow clones at her to keep her, but this only gave her more opportunities to create chasers. Chasers were a huge feature of Battle Mages. Even though they mainly dealt magic damage, because of the buffs given by the chasers, even a strength-oriented Battle Mage like Tang Rou couldn’t ignore their importance.

Tang Rou had played Glory for so long already. She was extremely familiar with chasers at this point. Right now, she was using all sorts of methods to create chasers in order to break out of this encirclement. Every time she hit a target, a chaser would also hit the target. At the same time, another chaser would be created. This loop continued. For Battle Mages, this was called Chaser Flow. There were players, who specifically geared their skill levels towards this playstyle. They would give up on using a spear and battle staff. Instead, they chose to use magic wands. Magic wands had high attack speed, high magic damage, and gave intelligence bonuses. Battle Mages, who specialized in Chaser Flow, stacked intelligence to increase the damage of their chasers. This sort of extremely specific playstyle didn’t exist in the pro scene because there were quite a lot of restrictions to chasers. For one, chasers could only be produced by hitting the target with a certain skill. The chaser also had to hit the target. The amount of damage that a chaser could do, even when stacking intelligence, couldn’t compare to a powerful high-level skill, so the burst it did wasn’t enough.

As a result, in the pro scene, Chaser Flow was just a technique. It was rarely used as a main playstyle. Ye Xiu had obviously told Tang Rou about this before. However, using Chaser Flow to break out of the Shadow Dance encirclement was a very good choice. Chasers continuously flew out. The colors of the five different types of chasers were all different. Their explosions made a colorful mess out of Deception’s shadow clones. The most terrifying part was that chaser damage was added in the combo count. And combos activated the Battle Mage awakening skill: Battle Spirit.

A faint golden glow soon emerged around Soft Mist. As her combo count increased, the golden color grew more and more prominent. The shadow clones from Shadow Dance actually became helpers for Soft Mist to accumulate combos.

“What is he doing?” Ye Xiu was puzzled. He was waiting for Deception to come out with some sort of big move, but all he did was use Shadow Dance, giving Soft Mist the opportunity to build up Battle Spirit. If this continued, how was he going to run? His shadow dance was being ripped apart by Tang Rou. No….. ripped apart was being too polite. He was practically assisting Soft Mist!

Tang Rou clearly understood this point. She felt like there was no need to run from this Shadow Dance. In the end, she was just pretending to break out of the encirclement. She stood there, killing the shadow clones coming at her.

Finally…...

The shadow clones all disappeared. They hadn’t been killed, nor had the skill duration passed. Deception cancelled the skill himself. He was clearly aware that his Shadow Dance was a mistake. How did things turn out like this? Ye Xiu really wanted to interview that guy.

When Steamed Bun saw the annoying clones disappear, he was even more brave than Tang Rou and threw a brick at him.

How could Deception be hit by such a simple and crude move? He stepped to the side and used a Shadow Clone Technique. His character instantly moved a distance away. It seemed like he wanted to run now?

What was this guy doing? Ye Xiu chased after him with Lord Grim, while wondering.

Steamed Bun chased after him enthusiastically, while shouting: “Punk, don’t run! To think you’d actually hide and ambush us!!”

Hide and ambush us!?

Ye Xiu suddenly came to a realization after hearing Steamed Bun’s shout.

Lord Grim chased after him. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun also followed along. Their equipment had gone up a tier again. Deception’s movement speed was no longer anything amazing to them. Lord Grim kept on pestering him with long-ranged attacks. Steamed Bun Invasion threw a brick at him from time to time too. Deception was greatly impacted by their combined efforts. He couldn’t run straight and had to zigzag around. In the end, the three caught up. Lord Grim stabbed forth with a Circle Swing, when “hu”, his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella didn’t even hit yet and Deception was launched into the air. Soft Mist had used a Circle Swing first.

“No need to fight over him!” Ye Xiu urged. He didn’t want to kill Deception. He was afraid Tang Rou would instantly kill him again.

Circle Swing was completed and Deception crashed into the ground. Soft Mist’s spear pulled away. Deception immediately tried to get up, when Steamed Bun Invasion grabbed a brick and slammed it into his character’s head.

“To think you’d be so fierce and actually attack us!” Ye Xiu said and had Lord Grim shoot at Deception twice. Ye Xiu had figured out Deception’s intentions.

That guy had actually tried to ambush them.

These past few days, Deception hadn’t been online, but how could a scrap picker like him not be busy during this opportune period of time? He clearly had more than one account. He had used those alternate accounts to scrap pick. They were all scrap picking experts and picked areas good for scrap picking. Today, Deception had seen Ye Xiu and the others in this Blue Brook Guild battlefield on his alternate account.

Every time the three of them scrap picked. They would come out with their inventories full. With such heavy weight, their character’s movement speed, attack speed, and jump stat would be heavily impacted. Deception was aware of this point, so he switched accounts to try and ambush them.

He had run over, not to scrap pick. He had the same idea as Ye Xiu. He wanted to ambush them. Hadn’t he been hiding there, waiting for Ye Xiu’s group to come, so he could attack? It was just that after awhile, Deception quickly realized that something wasn’t right. How could these guys be so nimble, if they had such full inventories? When Deception realized his mistake, how could he not try and run?

Ye Xiu didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. He had been planning on letting that guy know their might. Who would have thought that he would be so brave. As soon as he saw that there was an opportunity, he ran over alone to mount a sneak attack.

Unfortunately, if he wasn’t alone and had friends that could give him updates, he might have known that Ye Xiu’s group had quickly unloaded their inventories shortly after he had logged on.

Chapter 690: Do You Have Any Willpower?

“How bold!” Ye Xiu praised. The three arranged themselves into a triangular formation with Deception in the center.

“Yeah, extremely daring.” Steamed Bun Invasion threw a handful of sand at him.

“Confident too! Did you actually think that you could beat all three of us, even if we were weighed down by all the stuff in our inventories?” Ye Xiu said.

“You made a mistake. A very big mistake.” Steamed Bun remarked.

“That’s why I say that playing an MMO on your own is very difficult.” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s common sense. Don’t you even know that?” Steamed Bun said.

The two chattered and chattered, but Deception wasn’t listening. He turned his viewpoint slightly, examining their positions. With the two talking so much, it felt like there was an opportunity that he would be able to exploit. It was hard to avoid losing focus when talking.

Charge!

Deception formed the hand seals for the Underground Tunneling Technique to hide underground. However, Lord Grim and Soft Mist reacted quickly using their spears. Practically the moment he dug into the ground, their spears stabbed him, fishing Deception out and throwing him back above ground.

“You still dare to run!” Steamed Bun was furious as he threw a brick at him.

While Deception was in a dizzy state…..

“Have you been busy scrap picking recently?” Ye Xiu asked.

“......” Deception didn’t say anything.

“How was your harvest?” Ye Xiu asked.

“.....” Still no answer.

“Last time, I wasn’t able to finish talking by the time you died…… have you given any thought to what I said over the past few days? What do you think about joining our team?” Ye Xiu asked.

“......” Deception still didn’t reply.

“He’s asking you a question!!!” Steamed Bun Invasion’s Brick was off cooldown, so he threw another one.

“Is he even there anymore?” Ye Xiu mumbled. Lord Grim smacked him with his umbrella. Deception fell to the ground.

“Sigh.” Ye Xiu sighed, “He’s not a coward. Why does he have so little willpower though? He gives up so easily.” Lord Grim began attacking Deception.

Deception simply didn’t make any movement. He hadn’t actually left his computer this time. He really felt quite depressed at Ye Xiu’s comment. He had no way of beating them! What was he supposed to do? To say he had no willpower... He frequently had to lay low in hiding places, waiting until an opportunity presented itself, restraining himself from making any impulsive moves. How could that be called having no willpower?

Deception, who had given up resisting, was quickly killed. From start to finish, he hadn’t said a single word. After reviving, he decided to log off and switch accounts. He took up his cover and began to scrap picking again, but that disappointment in his heart…… he thought he would have been able to take revenge with that ambush. Instead, he was surrounded and killed. Apart from disappointment, what else did he be feeling?

‘This guy……” Ye Xiu was a bit helpless. It was hard to communicate with Deception.

“Talk nicely! Every time you see him, you kill him.” Chen Guo said.

“I don’t even know if he’s still logged in or not. If he logged off, if I don’t kill him, he’ll disappear after awhile. If he realized that had happened, wouldn’t he laugh at us and call us idiots? I can’t allow him to be so happy.” Ye Xiu said.

“Then how are we going to do this?” Chen Guo asked.

“We’ll just have to slowly wear him out!” Ye Xiu said. He was clearly prepared for a long drawn-out battle. Deception was too different from normal players. He wasn’t interested at all in the professional scene. He wasn’t different in a simple sense like Steamed Bun was either. Pulling him into the team was very difficult. Why else had so many guilds given up? Deception was an incredibly skilled player. He wasn’t like Little Cold Hands who needed someone like Ye Xiu to dig out his hidden potential. A talent like Deception was someone the big guilds certainly wanted to recruit. He wasn’t just someone useful to the guild, but a potential recruit for a pro team. Even so, he still wandered around alone. It could be seen that whatever recruiting methods the guilds attempted towards him didn’t work. Deception was truly a difficult person to deal with.

The three players continued their scrap picking. With Blue Brook Guild’s elite group sweeping the field, the equipment piled up like a mountain. More and more scrap pickers gathered. Beggars can’t be choosers, but Ye Xiu’s group was more picky. They wouldn’t even look at normal equipment and only picked up the best equipment they could find.

After scrap picking for a while, Lord Grim suddenly stopped. Ye Xiu adjusted his viewpoint and looked ahead.

Amidst the fierce battlefield, a lone Assassin was nimbly moving about, dodging all sorts of attacks, while choosing which equipment to pick up. Yes, choosing. This person was actually the same as Ye Xiu’s group. He only picked the most outstanding equipment. Common equipment wouldn’t enter his eyes.

And the way he picked up equipment was very bold. In a fierce battlefield, very few players dared to charge through the field. There was a limit to not being afraid of death. Rushing into the battlefield like that was practically the same as rushing to your death.

That Assassin ran around and quickly traveled through the field. From the number of times, he crouched down to pick up an item, it seemed like his harvest was quite good.

“Is it that guy?” Ye Xiu thought to himself. Deception’s alternate account must be scrap picking in this area. If not, he wouldn’t have known their whereabouts. Bumping into him here was a possibility,.and his scrap picking skills were very outstanding. Even if this person wasn’t Deception, he was still quite an expert!

Ye Xiu thought about it and had Lord Grim head over. After that Assassin ran out of the battlefield, he suddenly saw Lord Grim running towards him. His footsteps suddenly haltered.

This small detail didn’t escape Ye Xiu’s eyes. He was now certain that this person was Deception’s alternate. After failing his ambush, he decided to switch to his alternate account and keep scrap picking.

“Steamed Bun, Little Tang!!” Ye Xiu shouted as Lord Grim began sprinting.

Those two were having a very fun time, picking up items, when they heard Ye Xiu call out to them. They turned to look and saw Lord Grim rushing towards an Assassin called Not White.

Tang Rou immediately understood the situation. It was hard to know if Steamed Bun did or not. In any case, he followed Soft Mist and ran over.

Chasing after someone in a chaotic battle was much harder. Ye Xiu didn’t hurry and act. He just made sure to keep the Assassin within his field of view. Deception’s Assassin had much worse equipment compared to his Ninja. His movement speed wasn’t as fast. He was only able to not get caught by relying on his surroundings.

Deception clearly understood this, so he didn’t run outside of the battlefield and stayed inside. Ye Xiu said he had no willpower. Now this guy seemed to be refuting, saying that he would persevere. It would be hard to shrug his pursuers off by running around like this, so it would be a test to see who would lose their patience first.

Let’s see who can persevere longer!

Deception thought, when a sword light suddenly flashed towards him.

A random attack coming at him wasn’t anything strange amidst this type of battlefield. Deception played his Assassin quite well and immediately jumped up. He jumped again in mid-air, using an Assassin’s unique Air Jump to dodge the sword light.

Scrap pickers like him had no relation with the battle. Even though they were annoying, the battle was so fierce that no one paid attention to them. Usually, if someone noticed a scrap picker, he would attack, but if he didn’t hit the scrap picker, then he wouldn’t bother trying again .Very few people would continue chasing after one.

As a result, Deception didn’t pay too much attention to this attack. After dodging it, he continued to run. Who would have thought that as soon as he landed, another sword light would fly towards him? The other side actually attacked him after missing the first time.

Usually, Deception wouldn’t be afraid, but there were three scary people chasing after him from behind! A second of hesitation could carve his death in stone.

Thus, Deception didn’t dodge it. He took the attack and attacked to try force the opponent backwards in an attempt to create a gap for himself to escape.

Who would have thought that the opponent would have the same thoughts as him? The opponent didn’t block his Double Stab and ate the attack. This guy was planning on sticking to him, whether he died or not!

Deception panicked. He didn’t have the time to fight with this guy! This opponent was quite skilled too! His opponent wasn’t someone who could be shrugged off that easily, especially since he was being so shameless and running at him without regard for his life.

This brief delay was enough for Lord Grim to catch up. Deception still hadn’t been able to escape from his current entanglement yet!

“Thanks! Go on with your work!” Ye Xiu thanked the Blade Master for helping him as he closed in on Deception’s Assassin.

“What did this guy do to offend you?” Blue River asked.

“Ha ha, he caught my attention!” Ye Xiu laughed, as he entangled Deception. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had the equipment advantage over Deception’s Assassin. How could he not win this fight? Without Tang Rou and Steamed Bun needing to help, Deception was beaten up. By the time the two arrived, the fight was already about to end. This was under the situation, where attacks would occasionally fly towards them too.

“Did you think that switching to an alternate account would make a difference?” Ye Xiu grinned. He was certain that his person was Deception. Why else would he run? Even if they were foes as people of the same trade, scrap pickers wouldn’t go so far as to run as soon as they saw each other.

“Don’t scrap pick! Come with me and play in the Professional Alliance!” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Shut up!” Deception didn’t log off this time. He clenched his teeth and struggled. He even activated Life-Risking Strike.

But the attack didn’t hit. The fight ended without any suspense. Lord Grim easily killed him. With a crash, a bunch of items dropped as if a boss had died.

“You got quite a lot of stuff!” Ye Xiu was moved. It was as if he had killed a boss as he picked up all the equipment on the ground. The equipment on Deception himself wasn’t anything noteworthy. He had come to scrap pick, so he had a lot of stuff in his inventory. This time, he dropped a lot of equipment. They were all high quality equipment that Deception had specifically chosen. Now, Ye Xiu took it all.

Amidst the fierce battlefield, Blue River wasn’t able to clearly hear what the two were talking about. All he saw was Lord Grim kill him off and pick up all of the equipment that dropped.

F*ck…… he’s stealing from people of the same trade? The scrap picking business is really cruel…….

Chapter 691: That’s Not How You Scrap Pick

Blue River’s Blue Bridge Spring Snow was one of Blue Brook Guild’s Five Great Experts. Him being a part of Blue Brook Guild’s elite group wasn’t anything unusual. Even though he hated how the guilds were always trying to deceive one another, Blue River was still a loyal Team Blue Rain fan. This was something that had never changed.

Team Blue Rain had been crushed by Team Samsara in the finals. Blue River also needed some way to vent his emotions. PK war? In the minds of guild leaders like Changing Spring, this was something that would only result in injury. It was best to avoid it if possible. However, in Blue River’s heart, he wanted to participate in this unnecessary war.

There were no schemes or planning required. All he had to do was curse at Samsara and start hacking away. As a result, Blue River was very eager to fight. His original reason for taking up heavy responsibilities in the guild was to support Team Blue Rain, but he had since become tired of such work. Fighting mindlessly was an activity that he happily welcomed. He didn’t need to consider things from a long-term perspective. He didn’t need to consider the guild’s interests when he fought like this. He didn’t need to think about whether this was good or bad for the team. By releasing his pent up emotions, he could show his passionate support for the team.

However, he still had to go along with the elite group, so he hadn’t encountered any troubles during the fighting. Their group swept away everyone in their path. And from their group chat, he knew that Samsara’s elite group was doing the same on the other side of the battlefield. Blue River impatiently wanted to fight them, but in his heart, he knew that the guild wouldn’t allow for such a confrontation to happen.

The much more dedicated Changing Spring kept his rationale. He set an example as the leader of the guild, while avoiding real confrontations to preserve the guild’s strength. Samsara clearly had the same thoughts. Blue River didn’t know whether Changing Spring had kept in contact with Samsara’s Three Realms Six Paths. In any case, the elite groups of the two guilds seemed to not know that the other existed and focused on exerting all their strength to bully the normal members of the opposing guild.

How boring…...

Blue River thought to himself. Once one became a core elite member of the guild, could that still be considered as playing the game anymore? Truthfully, Blue River felt like he had been bound because of his support for the team. If he didn’t do these tasks, it felt like he wasn’t doing enough to support his team. Blue River’s support for the team had never changed, but he really didn’t like that feeling.

I’m not suitable for playing in a guild…..

Blue River was killing Samsara fans to vent his anger, while sighing to himself in sorrow. At this moment, he saw Lord Grim’s group chasing someone. Their target just happened to pass him. Blue River saw that he wasn’t from Blue Brook Guild, so he attacked him. Lord Grim soon caught up, ended that person’s life, and picked up all the equipment that dropped. This scene made Blue River speechless.

“Not White….. Remember this name.” Ye Xiu said to Tang Rou and Steamed Bun. Blue River’s Blue Bridge Spring Snow hadn’t even left yet. He shuddered when he heard these words. How did this guy manage to offend God Ye Qiu? Because he was scrap picking? What a deep grudge! They were going to imprint his name into their minds just because of that?

Ye Xiu also messaged the four allied guild leaders to help him take note of this character. When he turned around, he saw that Blue Bridge Spring Snow was still standing there.

Blue Bridge Spring Snow was currently located in the midst of the Blue Brook Guild elite groups. Quite a few Blue Brook Guild players noticed Lord Grim, including their guild leader, Changing Spring.

“What’s he doing here?” Changing Spring began to feel fearful. For Changing Spring, nothing ever good happened whenever Lord Grim appeared.

Seeing Blue Bridge Spring Snow talking with that guy, Changing Spring didn’t hesitate to ask Blue River.

“He’s just here to scrap pick…..” Blue River replied to his guild leader.

Scrap pick…… Quite a few people were waiting for an answer, most of which were experts like Ice of Dawn and Chilling Nightfall. They were like their guild leader. Whenever they saw Lord Grim’s name, the first thought that came to mind was: not good!

As for what was not good, wasn’t that being asked right now? But this answer made them think deeply. How would scrap picking affect their guild?

Blue Brook Guild clearly had a bad impression of Ye Xiu. In any case, whenever they saw him, they were certain that he was up to no good. As for how exactly this was bad for them, they needed to go find out.

“Scrap pick?” At this moment, a witness, who saw that scene, began speaking, “How is that scrap picking? Isn’t he just stealing?” This witness quickly described the scene that he had just seen.

F*ck! All of the experts were alarmed. He wasn’t picking up scraps, but directly stealing instead? The old experts with top quality equipment immediately became uneasy. How could they be opponents for God Ye Qiu? Who could actually stop him?

“It’s just three people! They can’t be looking to attack us, can they?” Someone said.

“We can’t be careless!” Changing Spring said in a solemn voice.

There were two hundred elite players, who could be considered peak experts of the Heavenly Domain, facing Ye Xiu’s group of three, yet they were the ones who were actually worried. They felt that their worries were completely deserved too. They weren’t ashamed at all. Blue Brook Guild had been completely eaten up by the shadow in their hearts.

But after Ye Xiu spoke to Blue River for a bit, the three characters left. Everyone in Blue Brook Guild heaved sighs of relief, but they soon discovered that he hadn’t gone far.

Of course Ye Xiu’s group wouldn’t go far. They were here to pick up scraps. Blue Brook Guild’s elite group swept away everything in their path, killing people and littering the floor with equipment. Of course, scrap pickers would hang around nearby. However, most scrap pickers picked up equipment when the other side wasn’t paying attention. They would rush over to pick up the equipment, run, and perhaps die. No one was as arrogant as Ye Xiu’s group. They just calmly followed the elite group from a short distance away. They didn’t think that their movements would put Blue Brook Guild under a huge amount of pressure.

He still hasn’t left!

He still hasn’t left!

Why isn’t he leaving?

Blue Brook Guild would fight for a bit and then turn around to check. All they saw was Lord Grim’s group following them closely, which added to their fluster. Everyone was worried that the other side had targeted them. The other side was probably waiting for them to get low before attacking, right? As a result, the healers were very busy. Everyone was shouting “HEAL HEAL HEAL!!!” But when the healers went to heal, what was there to heal? Their had only health dropped five percent and they were crying for their life! What was wrong with them?

“What’s going on? Why has Blue Brook Guild suddenly slowed down?” Ye Xiu had no idea what was happening, so he criticized them for being so slow. Little did he know that it was because of him.

It’s over. They’ve definitely locked onto us! Look. They’re even following us wherever we go!

Blue Brok Guild’s elite group kept on killing, but those three kept following them like ghosts.

This was similar to the saying: death is nothing to be afraid of. Waiting for death to arrive was what was scary. Right now, Blue Brook Guild’s elite group felt like they were waiting for death to arrive.

“Why are they bullying us!!” Changing Spring couldn’t bear it. He had to endure a lot over these past two days. He was Blue Brook Guild’s leader and a huge fan of Team Blue Rain. How could he be happy seeing Team Blue Rain lose so tragically? He wanted to let out his emotions too, but he had to control himself. He had to consider things from a management perspective and couldn’t give in to his heart’s desires. After all, he wasn’t purely a fan anymore.

Changing Spring couldn’t bear having Lord Grim’s group of three following them around like ghosts. Isn’t he just a God? What’s there to be afraid of? It’s just three people. We have two hundred. Why should we be afraid of you?

“Everyone, up!” Changing Spring grinded his teeth and gave the order.

Many of the people in the guild were still afraid, but with the order given, they had to follow the order as the elite group, even if they were afraid.

As a result, Blue Brook Guild’s players turned around and charged at Ye Xiu’s group.

“Huh? What’s this…..” Ye Xiu stared blankly. Why was Blue Brook Guild suddenly charging at them? What were they trying to do?

“Careful!” Ye Xiu had his suspicions about the other side’s intentions, but he couldn’t understand why. Ye Xiu’s thought the process was a bit wrong. He thought that he was scrap picking like everyone else, but who scrap picked with such high profile? This type of scrap picking put Blue Brook Guild under a lot of pressure!

Bang!

When Blue Brook Guild’s first attack came out, their intentions were completely exposed.

“What?” Tang Rou was puzzled, but she was excited, hearing this. This girl didn’t like to scrap pick, but a fight was good. Blue Brook Guild’s players, equipment, and skill were all at the top of the game. They could be considered as powerful opponents. Tang Rou really wanted to fight them to see how much she had progressed.

“Hurry up and run!”

But instead, she heard Ye Xiu order for a retreat. Tang Rou didn’t have the experience to examine the other side’s strength, but Ye Xiu did though. Three people against two hundred elites was impossible. Breaking through an encirclement or accomplishing some other purpose was still possible, but a fight to the death wasn’t.

“Let’s just fight for a bit….” Tang Rou didn’t want to leave.

Ye Xiu thought about it again. Right! Fighting shouldn’t be a problem. At worst, they would die and lose some of the equipment they had picked up and some experience. Their opponents were all experts in the game. They would be good practice targets.

After thinking about it, Ye Xiu replied: “Mm, then you guys go and fight. I’ll transport your equipment. Hurry up and trade with me.”

Blue Brook Guild was closing in. Ye Xiu’s group ran, while completing the trade. The two gave the equipment on themselves and the ones in their inventory to Lord Grim.

“Okay, go ahead! Good luck!” Ye Xiu encouraged them. He felt a bit distracted too. This sort of feeling was like sending his team members off onto the stage!

“Senior, you go ahead first. We’ll protect you!” Steamed Bun shouted heroically. As expected, he had the completely wrong idea.

Ye Xiu didn’t try to explain to him. His Lord Grim continued to run away, while Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion turned around after completing the trades and charged resolutely towards Blue Brook Guild’s two hundred players.

Chapter 692: Did I Scare You Guys?

Lord Grim’s group looked as if they were planning to run, which allowed Blue Brook Guild feel more at ease. Blue Brook Guild wasn’t dead set on killing them, so forcing them to run away was good enough.

Who would have thought that their moment of ease wouldn’t even last five seconds. After running for a bit, Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly turned around and charged at them. As for Lord Grim, he simply glanced at them for a brief second. Then, he turned tail and ran, appearing cold and indifferent towards the situation.

Are we screwed? Blue Brook Guild began to panic again…..

In the end, Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion died. Two players beating two hundred wasn’t even a remote possibility. Especially since one of the two came looking for a fight, while the other was there to “protect senior”. They charged forward in a very direct manner without any sort of tactics. In the end, the two were swallowed up by the sea of Blue Brook Guild players.

When Blue Brook Guild saw the two corpses, they were shocked. They looked all around them and even checked the sky too.

That’s it? There were no reinforcements? No ambushes? No follow up? No trouble was brought to them? They just got killed like that?

While Blue Brook Guild was at a loss, Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion revived at the city, waiting to meet up with Lord Grim.

Both of them had lost experience as well as a piece of equipment. These were all trivial matters though. When the three convened, Ye Xiu laughed out loud and asked: “How was that?”

“Senior, as long as you’re fine, it’s okay!” Steamed Bun still thought it had all been to protect Ye Xiu.

“There were….. A bit too many opponents.” Tang Rou had to admit it. Against so many opponents, no matter how skilled you were, it wouldn’t be possible. When she charged over, her chasers flew around everywhere, showing their might. She was in such a frenzy that Blue Brook Guild seemed like they didn’t dare to get close to her. Her Battle Spirit quickly reached the seventh stage.

But following afterwards…… they just kept their distance. Blue Brook Guild had long-ranged classes. All of them open fired and Tang Rou’s Soft Mist couldn’t even get close to them before she died.

Steamed Bun Invasion was pretty much the same. He charged forward and then died soon afterwards. In the end, the two weren’t even able to kill a single Blue Brook Guild player.

“Trying to fight against so many people in a head-on collision obviously isn’t possible. In that sort of situation, you have to use everything you have, utilizing guerrilla warfare, and finding opportunities to kill them off one by one.” Ye Xiu said.

“Mm.” Tang Rou nodded her head. After trying it once, she now knew that it definitely wasn’t possible to beat them in a head-on fight. She didn’t plan on trying again either. She didn’t like losing, but that didn’t mean she was stupid. Tang Rou could clearly distinguish between what was possible and what wasn’t.

“There’s a prerequisite for using this method to deal with two hundred players though. They have to be willing to play with you.” Ye Xiu said, “Originally, they were very willing to do so, but now, it seems like they don’t plan on concerning themselves with us anymore. Their sudden attack today was quite unexpected.”

Ye Xiu was aware of the change in attitudes from the guilds. When he had first entered the Heavenly Domain, they pursued him without any hesitation, but after a few tries, the thunder and rain lessened until it became peaceful. Ye Xiu knew that the guilds hadn’t done any negotiations or anything. Their attitudes just eventually shifted to their current one.

Ye Xiu had friended Blue Rain’s character just moments ago. He sent a message over to ask: “What’s going on with you guys?”

“You guys kept following us. It put us under a lot of pressure.” Blue River replied.

“Nonsense. We were just there to scrap pick. If we don’t follow you, who do we follow?” Ye Xiu replied.

“Is shooing away scrap pickers anything weird?” Blue River felt a bit speechless. When had scrap picking ever been something righteous?! Did he not know that scrap pickers were even more annoying than flies? Why is he accusing us as if we’re in the wrong?

“You’ll regret it.” Ye Xiu said.

“Is that a threat?” Blue River asked.

“No. I’m just giving you a heads up. Just wait for it!” Ye Xiu said.

Blue River suddenly became a bit nervous. It wasn’t a secret that God Ye Qiu had created a four guild alliance. Right now, Samsara and Blue Brook Guild were fighting because of the finals. The other guilds and fans weren’t participating. Hearing these words from him, was he planning on bringing the four guilds into the fight to wipe them out? Was he actually planning on stealing from us?

F*ck. Is another calamity going to befall us? If he had known earlier, Blue River was certain the guild would let the three scrap pickers follow them and endure the pressure. Their elite group didn’t want to suffer too many losses, now they had offended someone, who was about to forcefully rob from them…..

Blue River didn’t dare delay. He immediately notified Changing Spring. When Changing Spring heard his words, he also started to panic. Their elite group only had two hundred players. If the four guild alliance gathered all of their troops, they definitely wouldn’t be able to resist! Even more so with someone like God Ye Qiu leading the enemy troops.

“Hurry up and call for help!” Changing Spring ordered. Big guilds had a huge numbers of players. Changing Spring hastily called for reinforcements. Originally, there were only two elite groups fighting. Now, there was a third, fourth, fifth, sixth…… all the way until there were ten groups. Changing Spring still felt uneasy. Who knew how many troops the four guilds could muster?

Samsara suddenly received information about Blue Brook Guild gathering a huge number of troops. They suddenly felt uneasy too.

Both sides had been avoiding each other, but that was just a tacit agreement. They hadn’t made any concrete agreement. Was Blue Brook Guild suddenly amassing troops to fight us? Samsara obviously felt worry. They were Blue Brook Guild’s only enemy right now!

“We can’t be careless right now! Call for reinforcements!” Samsara’s guild leader Three Realms Six Paths hastily gave the order. Samsara started to gather troops too. One, two, three, four, all the way until ten groups were called.

“Something big’s about to happen.” Wei Chen’s expression turned serious.

“What’s wrong?” Ye Xiu asked.

“We’ve suddenly started gathering our troops together. It seems like we’re planning on fighting a huge battle with Blue Brook Guild?” Wei Chen may have held the title of the second elite group’s leader, his rise had been abrupt. It was because of his talent that he was able to rise to the step so quickly. Samsara still didn’t place too much trust in him. As a result, even though he lead an elite group, Wei Chen wasn’t a core member of the guild yet. Every day, he received messages telling him what to do. As for what the purpose was, he had no idea.

“Is that so? How amazing. Where are you planning on fighting? We should get ready.” Ye Xiu said. The guild elites had been avoiding each other, leading to worse profits compared to the last few days. Now that a huge battle was about to erupt, Ye Xiu wanted to seize this opportunity.

“I don’t know yet. I’m still waiting for orders!” Wei Chen said.

“Really? Then should I ask Blue Brook Guild?” Ye Xiu said.

“Huh? You can do that? Then go ask.” Wei Chen was surprised. He thought that Ye Xiu was a devil in the guild’s eyes. It was quite unexpected that he could get his hand on such important information from the higher ups of the guild. As he said this, he went over to look at who Ye Xiu was messaging.

“What’s going on? You’re about to start a huge battle with Samsara?” Ye Xiu asked Blue River’s Blue Bridge Spring Snow.

“What?” Blue River was puzzled.

“What? You don’t know? Samsara’s started gathering their troops!” Ye Xiu said.

“WHAT?!” Blue River jumped up in fright. He immediately informed Changing Spring. Changing Spring already knew: “Yes, I already got the news. Samsara’s gathered around ten groups together. They seem to be making a move.”

What are they trying to do? Blue Brook Guild was fervently discussing with one another. Samsara was fervently discussing this question too.

This situation made Blue River feel like something wasn’t right. Even though he detested this sort of fight, the fight had once again come to him. After thinking about it for a bit, he suddenly thought of something: “Could this be some sort of scheme that Ye Qiu came up with?”

“F*ck!” When this came out, many people suddenly became frightened.

“Not only is this guy gathering troops from the four guilds, but he’s also pulling Samsara into this? No wonder Samsara suddenly became so confident and actually started to gather troops to fight us.” Blue Brook Guild’s core members were discussing with each other.

“This is going to be difficult to deal with! Sh*t! That b*stard. He wants to loot a burning house!” Changing Spring cursed. The onlookers weren’t sure if he was cursing at Ye Qiu or Samsara. Then again, both of them should be cursed. Both of them were b*stards!

This deduction had come from Blue River’s guess, but Blue River felt that something still wasn’t right. If this was Ye Qiu’s doing, then his message was a bit strange! It didn’t seem to make any sense.

Right when he was thinking, Lord Grim messaged: “Are you guys going to make a move?”

“Make what move?” Blue River asked back.

“Aren’t you going to make a move against Samsara?”

“What are you talking about?” Blue River was becoming more and more confused.

“It seems like Samsara took the initiative.” Ye Xiu felt like he had grasped the situation as he told Wei Chen.

“The two big guilds have around the same level of strength. Blue Brook Guild should still be a little bit stronger though. For Samsara to take the initiative, it definitely can’t be that simple. Maybe they’re hiding some helpers?” Wei Chen started thinking.

“For a huge confrontation of this scale, if any other guild was going to come and help, they would have needed to make preparations beforehand. It isn’t possible for neither of them to have noticed such a gathering of troops!” Ye Xiu said.

“Maybe it’s just us who hasn’t discovered it? It’s not like we have a huge information network.” Wei Chen said.

“Who says we don’t? Bro, we’re in a four guild alliance. Don’t underestimate them.” Ye Xiu said. He messaged the four guild leaders to ask them to take note of any movements from the other guilds.

At this moment, Blue River organized all the information he had with him, especially the records of his conversations with Lord Grim. Finally, he still felt something wasn’t right and asked: “Could it be that you’re not scheming anything?”

“What scheme?” Ye Xiu was puzzled by Blue River’s sudden question.

“You said you’d make us regret it.” Blue River said.

“Oh, that was just something I said randomly. What? Did I scare you guys?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chapter 693: Award Ceremony

Blue River wanted to die. How could he have known that someone with the status of God would bluff like a third-rate player? Blue Brook Guild had panicked at the slightest threat and made a big fuss out of nothing. Since God didn’t have any intention to make good on his threat, the four guild alliance and Samsara weren’t anything to worry about. Why did Samsara make a move? Blue River was an experienced player. After thinking about it for a bit, he guessed.

This made him feel even more ashamed. There originally hadn’t been any issues. He had regarded God Ye Qiu’s words as truth and nervously notified his guild leader. How could he have known that this would create such a huge misunderstanding? How was he supposed to explain this to Changing Spring?

In any case, he had to say what he had to say. Blue River could only muster up the courage and explain to Changing Spring.

Changing Spring felt depressed at the explanation too, but he didn’t blame Blue River. After thinking about it for a bit, if he had been in Blue River’s position and God Ye Qiu said something like that, he would have also been nervous like Blue River. Now that they discovered that it was all a misunderstanding. From this point of view, it was Samsara who had reacted to their movements. Blue Brook Guild should hurry and disperse their teams to prevent Samsara from taking the initiative and attacking them. After winning the championships, Samsara must certainly be very excited. Who knew what they might do.

When Changing Spring thought about how he had to order everyone to disperse, he felt a headache coming. He had roared at everyone to hurry up and gather together. Without doing anything, everyone suddenly needed to disperse. Was this a joke or something? Changing Spring couldn’t think of any excuse to make. In the end, he could only say it was a misunderstanding and had everyone scatter.

Samsara had already fallen for the misunderstanding. Changing Spring was afraid that having everyone scatter wouldn’t be enough of an explanation to the other side, so he gave Samsara’s guild leader Three Realms Six Paths a message: “It’s a misunderstanding. Don’t make this a big deal.”

Three Realms Six Paths was just about to give a speech to everyone, when he suddenly received the message from Changing Spring. He suddenly froze. Changing Spring was so annoying. His messages were always so short, making it difficult to make things clear. Three Realms Six Paths didn’t ask him for further details and instead asked Blue Brook Guild’s Flying Brushstroke. He was a core member of Blue Brook Guild and one of the Five Great Experts. Three Realms Six Path reckoned that if Changing Spring knew about it, the other core members would know too.

Flying Brushstroke obviously knew about it, but it was so embarrassing! They had panicked at some casual words from God Ye Qiu. How could that be anything glorious? Of course, it wasn’t. As a result, Flying Brushstroke didn’t want to say the truth. He just said they had a misunderstanding with someone, not towards Samsara. If Samsara had gathered their troops to defend against them, they didn’t need to!

He didn’t want to talk about the details.

Three Realms Six Paths obviously didn’t want a huge battle with Blue Brook Guild. Their guild’s strength was weaker than Blue Brook Guild by a bit! However, Blue Brook Guild wasn’t explaining things clearly, which made it difficult for him to relax. Thus, he didn’t mobilize the troops, but he had everyone stay, just in case…...

However, since Samsara didn’t disperse, Blue Brook Guild became nervous. Their players had all left! If Samsara didn’t, were they planning on attacking them? As a result, Blue Brook Guild continued to ask Samsara.

The two guilds went back and forth all because of a few words that Ye Xiu casually said. He had no idea though. He was just waiting for the elites to start fighting, so he could pick up equipment. Seeing that there weren’t any movements, he lost his patience and pestered Blue Bridge Spring Snow: “Are you fighting or not?” “Are you fighting or not?” Blue River wasn’t in the mood to answer him anymore. He just pretended like he was dead.

While the two guilds were talking, the elites were just standing there. They weren’t even bullying normal players, right now. Then again, Samsara had gathered a thousand players together. Normal players weren’t so stupid as to provoke such a huge army. A perfectly good opportunity to scrap pick had become something the scrap pickers could only sit and wait for.

“F*ck. What’s going on?” Wei Chen was completely puzzled. He was a group leader, but he had no idea what the higher-ups wanted. It made feel very awkward.

Ye Xiu was helpless. He handed over a cigarette to Wei Chen and glanced at his screen. He saw a figure flash by his Warlock.

“Hey hey hey!! Turn to the left!” Ye Xiu hastily cried out.

“What?” Wei Chen was currently lighting his cigarette. Hearing Ye Xiu’s cry, he put the cigarette in his mouth and swiped his mouse to the left.

Ye Xiu looked at Wei Chen’s screen and immediately discovered something.

“That punk! Keep an eye on him for me!” Ye Xiu pointed.

Assassin, Not White.

Deception knew that Ye Xiu was scrap picking at Blue Brook Guild’s side, so he didn’t dare go over there again. There were two hold lands for scrap picking at the moment, one at Blue Brook Guild’s side and one at Samsara’s side. Since he couldn’t go to the Blue Brook Guild one, Deception ran over to Samsara.

But because of this incident, there wasn’t anything to scrap pick for now. Deception patiently waited for an opportunity. When he saw so many Samsara players gather, he knew that something big was about to happen. The bigger the battle, the better the scrap picking. How could Deception bear to leave? After wandering around the nearby area, Ye Xiu happened to notice him on Wei Chen’s screen.

“Who’s this?” Wei Chen asked.

“That’s Deception’s alternate account.” Ye Xiu said. Deception was a talent that Ye Xiu wanted to recruit, so Ye Xiu had introduced him to Wei Chen before.

“Oh oh, that guy. Perfect. I’ll go see how good he is.” Wei Chen said.

A few minutes later, Wei Chen let out a sigh: “F*ck, he really does have some skill. He almost escaped.”

Ye Xiu looked at Not White’s corpse as well as Samsara’s elite players moving about on Wei Chen’s screen. He couldn’t help but sigh: “You really are a brute. Was there really a need to call for so many people…..”

“I’m a group leader. I have a group around me, why wouldn’t I use them? You want me to run over and duel him? That doesn’t follow the game’s rules!” Wei Chen said righteously. He said he wanted to see how good Deception was for himself. Instead of having his Warlock face him head-on, he called his entire second elite group to take the on the task.

It was a hundred players versus one, but this time, it was different from Tang Rou’s and Steamed Bun Invasion’s situation. Tang Rou and Steamed Bun charged forward to fight them, but Deception wanted to run. However, Wei Chen was still able to lead his team and kill him off without much suspense. He could still tell that Deception wasn’t simple though.

“This guy’s worthy of being recruited. Keep whittling him down. I’ll help you keep a lookout for him.” Wei Chen said. Ye Xiu had talked to him about Deception’s circumstances. Recruiting someone who wasn’t interested in the pro scene was a difficult task. It was as if football club went to an NBA player and said: “Hey, why don’t you come with us and win the UEFA Champions League?” The NBA player would think the club was insane, no? In addition, Deception didn’t have a good understanding of the pro scene either. He didn’t want to talk either. Their only choice was to whittle him down until he did by killing him over and over again.

“He might have other alternate accounts. Take note.” Ye Xiu said.

“Mm, for a player like him, hiding his alternate accounts is difficult.” Wei Chen nodded his head.

As a result, Ye Xiu brought Tang Rou and Steamed Bun over to Blue Brook Guild’s side. Wei Chen continued to sit at Samsara’s side. If Deception wanted to continue scrap picking, he would have to give up on these two locations.

“We’re here to scrap pick again. Don’t make this a big deal!” Ye Xiu led Tang Rou and Steamed Bun over to an area near Blue Brook Guild’s elite group. But this time, he gave Blue River a heads up.

Changing Spring felt his hands shake at the information. Scrap pickers didn’t have a good name. Usually, they wouldn’t bother with them and kill them if it was in the passing. To think a scrap picker would actually give them a heads-up…...

Endure….. Changing Spring endured it. Even though the previous incident had been a misunderstanding, he was aware of this God’s abilities. However, letting him scrap pick without any worries was too shameful. Changing Spring gave the order to pay attention and pick up any dropped items. He didn’t want Ye Xiu to have it so easy.

The day passed by like this. In the end, Samsara and Blue Brook Guild didn’t fight. A misunderstanding was a misunderstanding. As long as no one took advantage of it, it was easy to resolve. Blue Brook Guild didn’t gather everyone or make any ambushes. Samsara also dispersed their army and continued to display their might by bullying normal players.

Ye Xiu’s group scrap picked for the entire day. Blue Brook Guild saw it clearly, but pretended to not notice. But they still listened to their guild leader’s orders. They picked up equipment like crazy, especially when they saw those three come over. They immediately stopped what they were doing and pick up anything around them. Oftentimes, those three had to leave with nothing to show for it, making Blue Brook Guild’s players very happy.

After this day passed, the week officially ended. As the curtains fell, season eight of the Glory Pro Alliance was also put to rest.

Team Samsara was this season’s champions. Their team captain and ace player, Zhou Zekai, was proclaimed the MVP of the regular season and the MVP of the finals. At the same time, he also won the Team DPS Star and Most Reliable Player in the Group Arena. All of these came from the statistics gathered in the regular season.

There were other awards as well.

King of Duels, which was based on the number of wins in the individual competition, was awarded to Team Tiny Herb’s Liu Xiaobie and his Blade Master Flying Sword.

One Hit One Kill, which was based on the finishing blows in the team competition, was awarded to Team Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian and his Blade Master Troubling Rain.

Best Sixth Player, which was based on the achievements of the sixth player in the team competition, was awarded to Team Misty Rain’s Lu Yizhu and his Sharpshooter Worse Coverup.

Team Void’s Li Xuan and Wu Yuce won Best Pair for their Ghostblade Duo. Team Hundred Blossom’s Tang Hao won Rising Star. There was also the Best Rookie award. This award was given based on evaluations of the matches throughout the year. Season eight wasn’t as spectacular as Sun Xiang’s rookie year last season. Sun Xiang had played a leading role in his team and was a fierce opponent.

Team Thunderclap’s Dai Yanqi, Team Wind Howl’s Zhao Yuzhe, Team Royal’s He Weitang were often mentioned. In the end, Team Wind Howl’s Zhao Yuzhe won Best Rookie.

Team Wind Howl ended in ninth this season and failed to make it to the playoffs. Their team captain and ace player Lin Jingyan’s condition was declining due to age. After the duel between him and Tang Hao at the All Star Competition, which he lost, the title of Number One Brawler was no longer his. Their team’s other All Star, Fang Rui, had a strong start, but a weak finish this season. The All Star Competition was the start of his decline. On the other hand, Zhao Yuzhe’s performance was steady all throughout the year, so he won the Best Rookie award.

After the season eight awards were given, the two relegated teams had to be mentioned.

Team Excellent Era and Team Mysterious Fantasy. Because these teams placed second-to-last and last in the regular season, they were relegated.

Chapter 694: First Summer Transfer

Although these results were officially announced after the finals, the outcome had already been decided and known weeks ago. Everyone had already been discussing it for a while now, especially with one of the relegated teams being a former powerhouse. Relegated teams rarely attracted this much attention. Only the fans of that team would be grieved.

After everything had been decided, Excellent Era gave a public statement. While the eyes of everyone were focused on the champions, Excellent Era wanted to give their fans a little bit of hope.

Club Excellent Era’s boss, Tao Xuan, personally accepted an interview. In the interview, he said that, although Team Excellent Era had been relegated, it was far from being over, especially after seeing this year’s finals. From Samsara, he ascertained that his choices for the players in the team were correct. This was an era, which required stars, and that his team had a star as brilliant as Zhou Zekai.

“Are you talking about Sun Xiang?”The interviewer could easily guess who Tao Xuan was talking about. Sun Xiang was a God-level player and his appearance was quite good too. He had everything Zhou Zekai possessed and he also wasn’t as quiet as Zhou Zekai. If he continue to grow, he would be worth even more than Zhou Zekai. From Tao Xuan’s words, it seemed like he was very confident of this.

With a popular player like Su Mucheng on the team, Excellent Era wasn’t any stranger to promoting a player’s business value. It could be seen from Tao Xuan’s attitude that although Su Mucheng was outstanding, she still couldn’t compare to Zhou Zekai.

No one would argue about such a notion. In a competitive environment, victory was still the main factor. Beauty was beauty, but the audience wasn’t watching the competitive scene to look at pretty girls. Zhou Zekai’s stunning performance pumped up the players. Appearance was just a little flower to top things off. Su Mucheng wasn’t a bad player. If her skill was garbage, no matter how beautiful she was, it wouldn’t have been possible for her to be so popular. The pro scene wasn’t such a place, where one could eat just based on their looks. Even if one were promoted as someone who was skilled, one’s performance on stage would reveal everything anyways.

Since one’s performance on stage was the main factor, the content of the match mattered too. It’s like in football, how the forward always brought more attention than the rear guard. The performance in a match, the playstyle, and the importance of the match all decided a player’s popularity. From this point of view, Zhou Zekai stood out the most.

In Tao Xuan’s eyes, Su Mucheng wasn’t someone who could reach that level. Her performance on stage wasn’t outstanding enough. Her popularity would at best stay the same. It would be good if it didn’t decline. As for Sun Xiang, he was someone who could stand next to Zhou Zekai. He was young. He had drive. He had good looks. His potential was limitless. Zhou Zekai’s success was a living example, which seemed to be a stimulant for Tao Xuan, who dared to announce it to the media.

His praise for Samsara’s success didn’t indicate his love for the team. It was simply because they were proof that his way of thinking about the team was correct. Praising Samsara only allowed the fans to know: even though we were eliminated this season, by following the correct path, we’ll rapidly grow. Look at this season’s champions Samsara. That will be us in the future. They have Zhou Zekai. We have Sun Xiang!

“However, from how this season went, it doesn’t seem like Sun Xiang and Team Excellent Era are fitting together too well.” The interviewer obviously wouldn’t blindly flatter Tao Xuan. He still had to be incisive when he needed to be.

However, Tao Xuan remained calm when faced with such an embarrassing question. He admitted that there had been problems between Sun Xiang and Team Excellent Era, otherwise, they wouldn’t have been relegated, but he once again emphasized that Team Excellent Era had great aspirations and that things needed to be looked at from the perspective of the future. Their previous glory was now part of the past. The team needed to turn a new leaf. As for how they were going to deal with the issues between Sun Xiang and Team Excellent Era, Tao Xuan delightedly threw out a huge bomb: Team Thunderclap’s captain, All Star, and Master Tactician Xiao Shiqin would be transferring to Team Excellent Era next season.

“I don’t think I need to explain Xiao Shiqing’s achievements do I? I believe that he’ll be able to beautifully incorporate every one of Team Excellent Era’s members into his tactics.” Tao Xuan confidently expressed.

This was definitely a huge bomb dropped.

Xiao Shiqin had already announced his departure from Team Thunderclap in the playoffs. Many people guessed that he would be transferring to Team Excellent Era. It was very reasonable. However, this had just been a guess. Team Excellent Era was simply one of many possibilities. Although it was logical, Team Excellent Era had been relegated, which was a very vulnerable weakness. Would an All Star like Xiao Shiqin still want to join a team that needed to go through the Challenger League next year?

Team Excellent Era had now confirmed it. The Glory Pro Alliance’s summer transfer window started from July 1st to August 31st. It was still June right now, but the season was already over. Xiao Shiqin had stated his intentions earlier and Tao Xuan had released the news. Although it didn’t conform to the rules exactly, no one really minded.

Tao Xuan was also anxious. Their team would not be participating in the regular season next year. They would certainly lose a lot of popularity. He had to do everything he could so that the fans wouldn’t give up on them. Announcing Xiao Shiqin’s transfer early was a good move.

Because everyone knew Xiao Shiqin wasn’t transferring to Team Excellent Era to play in the Challenger league, but was instead thinking about the future. He would sacrifice a season, return to the Pro Alliance with a stronger Team Excellent Era, and win the championships. If even an All Star like Xiao Shiqin thought highly of Team Excellent Era’s future, wouldn’t others also be patient? Tao Xuan’s message was mainly used for this effect.

The first transfer for the summer had already been announced. This sort of news was certainly delightful news for the fans during the break.

After the finals ended, the official break period for the teams began. This was only a break for some people. For the owners, managers, logistics, team captain, etc, it wasn’t a vacation.

In order to prepare for the upcoming season, every team would still be operating. Whether it was player transfers, character transfers, or equipment upgrades, all of these were the main tasks during the summer. The diligent players would even return to practicing after a short rest. There might not be any matches to play, but they would still play in the game, assisting their Clubs in killing wild bosses.

Ye Xiu obviously knew about this situation. This was all voluntary for the players though. The Clubs wouldn’t require it. Conquering Clouds, Radiant, and Parade didn’t make it into the playoffs, so their break had started earlier. However, none of their pro players were willing to use this break to contribute to the team, which made Ye Xiu quite sad. Helping out in the game during their break was more of an old player habit. In the early days of the Alliance, pro players weren’t solely responsible for the matches that they played in. In-game activities such as killing bosses for materials and other forms of competitio, were tasks that pro players frequently participated in.

As for the later generation players, they only needed to focus on practicing and preparing for their matches. The in-game tasks were given to a separate specialized game department in the Club. As a result, the number of pro players who helped out in game during the break became fewer and fewer. Those three teams had already been on a one month break, yet none of their players had the conscious to help out their guilds in game. Ye Xiu felt like there wasn’t any hope.

After a fierce showing between Blue Brook Guild and Samsara, the fans gradually calmed down and the game became peaceful again. Snatching bosses was something that always needed to be done, but this time, everyone knew a new opponent had come: God Ye Qiu and his four guild alliance.

Last week, everyone was busy fighting with each other, so they never actually faced them, but now, everyone would be facing this new challenge. The guild core members were all somewhat uneasy. Their opponent was no small fry.

Early Monday morning, three wild bosses spawned across the Heavenly Domain. The four guild alliance made an impressive showing, but weren’t able to take any of these three bosses in the end. However, this was because God Ye Qiu wasn’t there. The four guilds were relying on their own abilities to fight. It was a big difference without God Ye Qiu’s leadership and support.

Later in the morning, Ye Xiu’s group logged on. Loulan Slash and the other guild leaders were eagerly awaiting for him to come online. Even though different players could cycle through the guild characters, in their group, Ye Xiu himself was important, not his character. When Ye Xiu wasn’t online, they could only pray that no bosses spawned. Last night, three had spawned. The four guild alliance had attempted to contest them, but they failed. The top guilds were on their utmost guard against them. All of the top guilds seemed to be together too in this, as if the four guild alliance was their number one enemy.

It had to be said that this was because of Ye Xiu’s terror. After knowing that Ye Xiu was behind this, the top guilds couldn’t help but gather together in fear. It wasn’t like before, where they would discuss with each other for a long time before coming to a conclusion .

Now, two words came out in their discussion group: “HE’S HERE!” The enemy Ye Xiu had arrived.

Another two words: “BE CAREFUL!!” And with this, an alliance was formed.

The four guilds’ attack didn’t go well for them, so the four guild leaders revised their sleep schedule to match Ye Xiu’s. In the morning, they sighed: “Sure enough, God Ye Qiu is very important. Without him, our four guilds are nothing!”

Because of God Ye Qiu’s addition, they became the target of everyone, so the difficulty in snatching bosses changed. This was something that they had failed to realize.